Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk!
Regarding your letters,
I'm Minori Suzuki, voice of Kanade Yoisaki from Nightcord at 25:00.
In this ProSeka AfterTalk, we'll look back at the event
while covering messages you, the fans, have sent in.
That's what this stream is all about.
So, this time...
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I kinda want the staff to secretly show me all of them, you know,
I'm really curious about everyone's thoughts.
So,
we'll be introducing the letters we received during the program, so please look forward to it.
Also, please post your thoughts on the event and this broadcast with #ProSekaAfterTalk.
I'm also watching the YouTube chat, so if you have anything,
I'll pick up any interesting comments.
Yes.
Oh,
like 'It was a good story,' or 'Kon-Niigo,' right?
Yes, it's Kon-Niigo!
And today, there's also an AfterLive from 10 PM,
and at 10:05 PM, this event's 3DMV
will be released, so I want to watch it with everyone.
So, I want to proceed strictly on time, but...
However, I want to watch the story video a bit longer than usual,
because I was a little selfish
and asked for it.
So the story is a bit longer,
and I hope you'll all watch it.
Well then, let's get right to it.
I'd like to talk about the story of "Colors of Pure Sense"
this time.
Everyone, how was this story?
Let's look back at it together while introducing your letters.
This is my first time doing ProSeka AfterTalk since it was renewed.
It's been about a year, and a year ago it was probably before the renewal,
so this is my first time weaving words from everyone's letters, and I'm a little happy.
So, this is a letter from Amelia Time-san.
They said, 'This is my first time sending feedback.'
Thank you very much!
The scene that left an impression on me was Ena deleting her selfie account.
I felt growth in Ena, who had been running away from facing her art, deciding to face it.
Also, like Ena, I was scared to face myself and ran away,
but Ena's positive attitude encouraged me,
and I thought I should also do my best.
Minori Suzuki, what feelings did you put into Ena's performance this time?
Thank you for that question.
Amelia Time-san, thank you for your wonderful letter.
Well, I'd like to talk about it later
while watching the story, but...
For Ena this time, and when singing N25's recent songs, what I was conscious of as Ena,
and as a cast member, was that I personally made sure
Ena wouldn't go back to
her old self. Because even if slowly,
Ena is steadily
moving forward, little by little.
N25's songs, due to their type, often have negative or backward-looking words,
or a certain atmosphere.
But I tried not to be pulled too much by that, and also,
well, perhaps if it had a bit of a
sad or negative nuance,
honestly, as a song or a line,
it might resonate more with everyone, making them think 'Oh,' or 'I want to hear that,' or
'This phrase is nice.' I think there are many things that catch your
ear and
stick with you.
But that's just Suzuki's desire for recognition,
wanting to show something.
So I try to convey that Ena is slowly but surely looking forward, through her songs and lines.
So, even with the same words, I try to make sure you can feel that she's moving forward.
I'm conscious of that, and I gradually increase that
'forward-looking' aspect based on the story.
That's how I approached playing her
this time.
And,
yes, for this event and recent songs, Ena understands that the world is warmer than she thought,
and people around her will help her more than she thought.
I believe Ena truly understands that now,
so I was conscious of that when performing.
I made sure to keep that in mind.
Well then, next, I'd like to introduce one more letter.
This letter is from Sudachi Udon-san.
Minori-san, good evening.
Good evening.
I watched "Color of Pure Sense."
Thank you very much.
What left an impression on me was in Episode 7, the scene where Ena
is so happy drawing that her emotions soar.
Ena, who could only boost her self-esteem through others' evaluations or selfies, finally realized, 'It's okay to be myself,
My world
and my expression can be as free as I want it to be.'
As Ena's world gradually became more colorful, and she found joy in drawing,
the way her eyes sparkled more and more was powerfully conveyed through Minori-san's voice,
and it brought tears to my eyes.
I want to continue watching over and supporting Ena, who has resolved not to give up on her dreams and her art.
Minori-san, the colors of Ena's heart... Oh, what a wonderful message!
Thank you so much for portraying them so vividly through your vocal performance.
Thank you very much for that.
No, thank you for receiving it so well.
What I always think is, you know, I hope Ena's feelings reach everyone,
Of course, she's a game character,
and a 2D one, but Ena is truly alive.
She's truly living,
Ena's future,
no one knows what it holds yet.
So, I hope I can convey
that raw, living feeling of hers.
Thank you for the wonderful feedback.
Yes.
So, I have a lot I want to talk about,
but if I talk too much here while watching the story,
we'll run out of time in 5 minutes, so I want to move quickly.
This time too, I've picked out scenes I personally want to talk about,
so let's watch them together.
Today, I made a selfish request, and when I say 'I made a selfish request',
the staff members shake their heads a lot.
Thank you, staff.
I was really conflicted.
I was so tempted to watch episodes 7 and 8 together,
but I think we'll just watch
episodes 7 and 8.
This is an AfterTalk, so it's a talk show, you know.
If Minori (me) talking too much
bothers you,
please rewatch the story in the game.
Okay,
let's get right to it.
Episodes 7 and 8.
Here we go.
That's amazing.
Dad's painting, it's sparkling somehow.
It's like it's not the same world
I'm seeing.
How can he paint
like this?
Oh.
What's wrong?
Hey,
why did you just paint it red?
This leaf doesn't have any red on it.
Hmm.
I thought it looked better that way.
Is that how you see it,
Dad?
Not really.
No,
maybe it's not wrong.
Huh?
I don't really get it.
The colors you see might be different,
I just wanted to draw it this way.
Just to draw.
Is that okay?
Even though the colors are completely different?
Ah.
Art is freedom.
It's your own world, after all.
So,
you should draw however you like.
Wow.
My own world.
Then,
is this painting Dad's world?
It's so
beautiful,
and mysterious.
What color will you paint next?
What will that bird perched on the branch look like?
Huh, good evening.
Back then,
Dad's hands, drawing pictures,
looked like magic, I remember.
Time's up.
Those hands from back then,
those very hands—
Please put down your brushes.
Ah.
Because I was always watching, I...
Good job, everyone.
Please bring your works to the front.
I admired painters.
It's over.
The hands I saw back then were so big and sparkling.
It was fun.
But,
drawing it exactly like that might be a bit different.
Because it's like magic, creating a world on a large canvas.
Good morning.
Oh, Ena-chan, good morning.
How did it look
to me back then?
It seems the competition results are out.
Those hands...
I haven't seen them yet, though.
How would I express them?
Big, filling the entire canvas.
Oh, really?
Ah, I got a bit sidetracked.
Then, why don't we go see them together?
Well, I guess it's okay.
That's more my style.
And I'm curious what kind of paintings everyone else drew.
The sparkling colors,
the sunlight,
Yeah, I'll go with that.
I'll add the color of the tree my dad painted back then.
This is it.
Not green,
It's fine.
but red running through it.
This painting...
Oh,
the colors got mixed.
But I think I was able to express it.
But,
this is my touch.
This might actually be better, giving it a magical feel.
The world I saw.
Painting is...
...freedom, after all.
So,
I'll paint it however I like.
I'm sure...
That's right.
I'll intentionally layer many colors, letting them mix.
Oh,
scoring and evaluation.
Right.
I should paint even more,
so it sparkles with all sorts of colors.
I see.
It's a bit hard to talk, but it's kind of...
...fun.
Natsuno-san,
I'm just going to say it.
It's so much fun.
Since it's a game, wait.
For everyone,
I don't want it to be finished.
I want you all to enjoy it.
Forever,
my whole life,
I want to keep painting.
More.
Yes, I'm consciously performing it.
Ena,
you seem to be having fun.
Ah.
It seems she's found her own answer.
What kind of painting it will be...
It's exciting, isn't it?
Have you seen Yoisaki-san?
Huh? Ena-chan?
Um...
Oh, she's not here.
She was here just a moment ago.
Hmm.
Yoisaki-san.
Oh!
Huh, Sensei,
why are you here?
It was time for our meeting, so I was looking for you.
Oh, right.
Oh,
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to get some fresh air outside.
What were you thinking about?
Um,
I was just thinking
about the competition.
Ah.
That painting, right?
Yes.
For me,
it was really enjoyable.
Until now,
drawing has often been
a struggle, but this time,
it was truly enjoyable.
Thanks to you, Sensei, I was able to give it my all,
and I feel like I painted a picture I'm truly satisfied with.
So,
I'm very satisfied.
I see.
Yes.
But,
still,
if that was
everything I had.
And even then,
if it still doesn't reach P,
then maybe it's impossible
after all?
Impossible, you say?
I had always
wanted to go
to Toubi.
I wanted to study art
at Japan's best institution.
But...
But the people aiming for Toubi can draw much better than me,
so I thought I had to be good enough to get results in competitions.
Even if I gave it my all,
I still only got a C.
But...
But even then,
even with all that,
I still want to go to Toubi.
I know it's impossible,
and I feel like someone like me shouldn't even aim for it,
but I don't want to give up.
Indeed, your skill is insufficient to aim for Toubi.
However,
your world was undoubtedly depicted in that painting.
I told you that all art techniques can be explained by theory, didn't I?
I also mentioned that there's an appeal in art that can't be measured by theory.
While evaluations are based on theory, how much a painting touches people's hearts is a different kind of assessment.
And for the Toubi entrance exam, evaluations beyond theory are also important.
In other words,
if Shinonome-san can further hone her strengths,
the possibility of passing the Toubi exam is not zero.
That's what I believe.
Huh?
Of course, the current Shinonome-san lacks too many things.
The current C grade indicates that.
Nevertheless, if Shinonome-san wishes to proceed, I will teach you what you need to reach your goal.
Sensei.
Well then,
what will you do?
But...
Please take care of me.
I ask for your guidance.
Akihiro-sensei got a voice, didn't he?
I wanted to go to Toubi,
but I could never bring myself to commit.
I kept making excuses, saying I wasn't skilled enough yet.
But...
I've decided.
I will...
aim for Toubi.
I'm sure...
I'll face many setbacks.
My lack of skill...
will become even more frustrating.
But...
I want to face art more seriously than ever before.
That's why...
Oh,
I guess I still can't quite break the habit of escaping
to selfies when things get tough.
Even this time, it almost happened so many times.
But now that I'm going to be
more serious than ever,
it's time to
put an end to it.
It's already
gone.
When I look at it like this,
it feels like an instant.
But it
was good.
Now I don't have to
run away anymore.
Thank you for
everything until now.
She bloomed.
It's almost time, so I guess I'll start working on Niigo stuff.
It's Ena-chan's birthday.
Are you already here?
Ena, Ena, Ena!
You're noisy.
What?
Calm down.
I think I've always known.
Has your account been hacked?
Be careful.
Ena probably made various decisions and resolved herself,
but somehow,
her account, the one with the selfies,
she still ended up relying on them,
using them as an escape.
But she couldn't escape, and she still wanted to go to Toubi.
She didn't have enough confidence to tell others, or to truly resolve herself,
but this time,
she was able to properly quit and make a decision.
So, from here on, it'll be tough, but it's like the fog in her heart cleared, bringing a sense of relief,
and also the feeling that there's still
more to come.
With all those mixed feelings, somehow,
there was also a relieved Ena, and that's what I felt strongly towards the end.
I was thinking about that while acting.
And the reason why I chose episodes 7 and 8
is because of her father. There were many things that happened, and times when she couldn't face him,
but she really
admires him. Probably, after puberty and various events,
her father also wasn't very good with words,
and she realized that the respect she secretly held for her father, despite her frustration,
was still there. As Ena took a step forward as an artist,
she remembered that feeling.
That's why I also got to play young Ena.
But because she was a child,
she was pure, and everything she saw was new and sparkling.
And in that world, her father was there, and that
father was an even more amazing person to Ena, someone she admired, someone who created incredible things,
like a block of light.
It was like she was talking to such a figure, or the amazingness of the paintings her father created,
all of it
in her head.
Because I acted while feeling all of that, I was able to maintain that sparkle
and return to that scene where she's drawing, without really breaking
character. So, holding onto that sparkle and the scenery she saw with her father,
being able to go into the scene where she happily draws was personally very
significant. And she was able to truly say "fun" for the first time. That was probably very significant for Ena too,
even though it's still in the middle of the path she's finally reached, she finally made it here.
That's how it felt. Ah, I'm about to cry.
That's also why...
Ah, this is bad.
When I first saw the script,
I cried so much at home.
I thought, "It's finally good, isn't it?"
Oh no, a broadcast mishap.
Well,
you know, for five years... well, not five years in Ena's timeline, but
I think there are so many different feelings, and I think many of you can really relate to Ena's
story. I also understand her feelings very well because I'm in that world of art, where there's no single right answer.
That's why I understand her feelings so well.
But it's not just that; it's also that Ena's hard work, somehow,
her efforts are finally being rewarded, or rather, 'rewarded' might be too simple a word, but thank you.
Ah, but I was so happy about that.
When I first read the script, even I
cried with a feeling of 'Congratulations, Suzuki!' And while reading, it was Ena's 'Ah, I finally made it this far!'
that simple feeling she achieved, that
something that had been tense from all her hard work finally loosened. Ah, excuse me, there are a lot of tissues here.
Yes, so, with those feelings, naturally,
while shedding tears, there were parts where my words got choked up, but that's
acting, and it's truly the good part about playing Ena, that
if I cried as Ena, Ena would cry with me, and
of course, they adjusted to my pace,
and the lines move forward when you press a button, but until that button is pressed, they truly
do everything carefully without cutting anything. I'm just so grateful and moved.
And the feedback for this event was that it was a really, really good
story, and I received many comments saying that. And also, it wasn't about Suzuki-san's
acting being like this, or Suzuki-san's
voice being like that. Instead of me, everyone truly accepted Ena's way of life, and somehow
they were happy, or felt encouraged, or
thought 'Let's do our best together,' or simply those who had always supported Ena,
those people were
like, 'Oh, that's good,' or 'But it's still just the beginning,' and they expressed various emotions towards Ena,
the fact that they did that...
I was really happy that I could pour all of my current effort
into Ena, and I'm glad I did.
That's how I feel.
Right.
Yes.
Well then, let's take a look at the illustrations.
By the way, for Ena, who kept facing art and suffering because of what she loved,
it was the moment she saw a glimmer of hope,
and that's why I chose it, apparently.
Right.
So, in about four quick minutes, I'd like us to take a look at the card illustrations together.
Before we look at the illustrations, we've actually received comments
from the illustration production team about the outfits, so I'd like to share them
with you.
This time, Ena struggled to get into art school,
almost gave up when she couldn't reach her desired level, but didn't give up.
This story was the central theme, and we created the design with an art apron over a school uniform as the motif,
imagining Ena's style as a student preparing for exams.
That's the design.
While there are aprons in existing outfits for an artist style,
for this event's outfit, only Ena has a patched-up apron,
which represents her perseverance despite repeatedly facing setbacks.
This design incorporates unique arrangements for this event.
That's the design.
Also, while retaining strong elements of a school uniform like the sailor collar and pleats,
we've consciously added shape arrangements to enhance the costume feel.
That was our intention.
So, here are the illustrations.
And also, the untrained version. Everyone gave this one a great response.
She's drawing happily, her hands are dirty.
It's absolutely wonderful.
And then, this is the wonderful untrained version of everyone who watched over and supported Ena this time.
This was the untrained and trained version.
You know, Kanade is, after all, someone who creates things,
so even though the genre is different, she understands Ena's feelings.
And KAITO-san. KAITO-san also gave Ena many important words.
And they're all eating ice cream together,
so please take a look if you'd like.
So, I'm calling it 'yogurt ice cream'.
Because I like yogurt ice cream, you know.
Oh, it's me again, huh?
And Miku-san.
So cute.
Lots of wonderful art.
They're eating ice cream.
Look, ice cream.
Cute.
And finally, Mafuyu-chan. Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, I can't long-press!
Right.
She's holding an apron.
Yes.
So cute.
Thank you very much.
And with that, you've seen the illustrations before and after training. Ugh, how many times am I going to do this?
Right.
You've seen them.
Oh, I still have a few minutes to talk about the story, so I will. The previous story wasn't really about Ena's art,
you know?
But the one before that, the one where I sang "I am the Rain"—
that song was also about Ena's art. I don't like saying "Ena's drawings."
Anyway, for that story about her art,
I happened to go to a museum.
So, I was able to portray what it means to look at art, based on my own experience,
and I got to know Ena better. This time,
I happened to be walking along, humming to myself, and I saw Ena walking by. There was probably a school for art students,
people aiming for a career in art,
on that street. I thought, "Oh, so this is what it's like." Just observing from the side, I felt such intense tension,
and realized how incredibly strict that world is.
I went into the recording session with that renewed feeling.
I hope I can convey even a little bit of the atmosphere,
the "texture" of Ena's world, to all of you.
That's what I strive for every day when I perform.
Thank you.
Yes.
So, yes,
there are still
a few tens of seconds left.
By now, some of you might have already watched the AfterLive, right?
Since it's content that takes place after the story,
Ena's refreshed expression—though she still has many challenges ahead—
her determined expression,
and her singing voice, I hope they're reaching you all right now.
I'd be so happy if they are.
Yes.
Indeed.
It's such a good story.
Ena is truly loved.
To receive such a wonderful story.
So, with that, after watching the 3DMV that was created for this event,
I'd like to talk about the song.
Here it is.
Please enjoy.
A body that can't become anyone,
breathing within a borrowed life.
If I dive deep inside,
even now, my past self
is still smiling.
Looking back, what clearly remains
are fragments of a dream that sprouted in my heart.
Cast into two shadows,
that past eventually turned into dislike.
There's no point in dwelling on
a past that has changed like that,
is there?
A truly small,
gentle
light…
The feelings I believed in
still haven't reached.
Even so, remaining parched,
I want to draw more of the future with these hands onto the pure white scenery before my eyes.
Even if it's not
beautiful,
I want to do it in my own way.
I want to keep drawing
this world reflected in my eyes.
And so, excuse me, my screen... pardon me.
The song written for this event by Choucho-P,
its title is...
It's the first time the title is revealed, isn't it?
The name of that picture is... a 3DMV.
Uh,
First, uh, oh, is that right?
For a moment, I thought my own notes were Choucho-P's comments,
and I was like 'huh?', but they weren't.
These are my notes that I sent to the staff beforehand. Okay, I'll read them now.
Uh, just by listening, I can feel Ena's journey, and it makes me tear up.
The title contains 'e' and 'na', her name,
and I felt it was truly a song that depicted Ena.
Regrets, frustrating feelings, painful feelings—
rather than just being pessimistic, I sang it with the resolve to turn them into strength,
and with the positive feelings of her having made that resolve.
That's what my past self emailed to the staff.
Choucho-P's comments are introduced on ProSeka Broadcast Station and such,
and I think they're also on Twitter,
or X, so please check them out.
Right, with those feelings,
uh, there are lyrics that feel like she's looking back at the past,
but, well, it's like the Ena of today
is truly looking back.
So, I mean, Ena probably definitely has regrets, but she's also a girl who understands
that she is who she is because of those experiences.
So, even the phrases looking back at the past, I didn't want to sing them
with the full intensity of past Ena's suffering.
Uh, I sang with that in mind,
and as I mentioned earlier, in the story, her resolve was made.
So, I sang with a sense of relief and the bright feelings
of finally understanding,
but this isn't the goal yet.
Since it's a start, I really focused on that,
that feeling of being in the middle, you know, that kind of sentiment.
I sang it with that in mind.
So, rather than a huge emotional outburst,
I really focused on quietly, internally, playing out the words,
encouraging myself, you know, like patting my own chest and saying 'I can do it!'
I sang it with that kind of self-encouragement in mind.
Somehow, I just end up crying.
I can listen to the full version, since I'm the one who sang it, sorry about that.
But, you know, I just cry.
It's no good.
This story and this song, they just make me cry.
What am I going to do? What should I do?
I thought I wouldn't cry this time talking about this, but I did.
Right?
So, for those of you out there who are a little jealous that I said I can hear the full version,
it's okay.
The 2DMV for this commissioned song, 'Sono E no Namae wa,' will also be uploaded
to the ProSeka official YouTube channel at 10:15 PM after this.
So, along with the 3DMV, please be sure to check
that out as well.
So, that means we'll probably be able to hear the full version, right, if the 2DMV is like usual?
Right?
I haven't even seen the 2DMV yet myself.
Oh, and speaking of the 3DMV, though it's a bit late, my thoughts are that even though it's filmed in full,
I know the vocal distribution, so I know which parts are Ena's.
That's what I mean.
And since the song starts with the three members of N25 in order,
my imaginary 3DMV, the one in my head,
I thought, 'Ah, not Ena, but the song...'
'How will it start?' I wondered if all four or five members
would suddenly appear, or if it would start with Mizuki's opening line,
but then...
Ena was featured prominently throughout,
and of course, for those who support other characters,
I'd be happy if their screen time was high too.
But this MV really put a lot of spotlight on Ena,
and it matched the story so well. I felt it was an MV that truly captured
Ena's way of life, and as a performer,
I was incredibly happy about that.
That's what I felt.
It was a really great feeling.
Ena being featured is always the case, but for the song during Ena's story,
the setting also felt like it was gradually rising to the surface.
And that, well, this is just a fan's theory,
but I was happy about that too.
It's like the location itself was moving upwards,
and I found that really heartwarming.
But I've only seen it a few times myself,
so I want to watch it carefully.
Oh, I'm really looking forward to the 2DMV.
Right.
I guess.
I don't think there's anything I've left unsaid,
but I've entrusted everything to Ena's voice,
to Ena herself. So, more than anything,
I hope you can feel Ena's way of life through the song
and the story.
Please continue to support Ena, everyone.
Thank you so much to everyone who supports Ena.
Although I'm not Ena, as someone who plays her,
I feel like I'm a close presence to her.
So, I'll continue to do my best every day as an actress
to properly portray her as she grows even more
after making this decision.
Please continue to watch over Ena.
Thank you very much.
And so, though it was a short time,
this ProSeka AfterTalk…