Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk: Colors of Pure Sense edition!
Good evening, everyone!.
I'm Minori Suzuki, the voice of Ena Shinonome from Nightcord at 25:00.
This ProSeka AfterTalk is a program where we look back on the event while sharing the messages we've received from all of you.
Today, we're covering the Colors of Pure Sense event.
Did everyone enjoy the story?
Thank you.
Between the fan festa and the movie stage greetings,
the real-life cast events have been quite busy lately.
And then right after that, we have this N25 event, an Ena's focus event.
I'm sure it's been a bit of a whirlwind for everyone,
but I hope you've been enjoying it all.
We've gathered your comments for this Aftertalk sent through email as well as the submissions channel on the Discord.
Thank you all for your letters.
I was so curious about what everyone had to say, I wanted to ask the staff to let me see all of them secretly.
We'll go over some of your messages in our program today, so please look forward to that.
Also, please post your thoughts on the event or this broadcast using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
We'll also be watching the YouTube chat, so please keep all the messages coming.
All right.
Some people saying "I liked the story",
I see some "kon-niigo"s too.
Yes, kon-niigo.
Also, there'll be an AfterLive for this event at 10PM, and the 3DMV for this event will be released at 10:05,
so I'd like to watch that with everyone.
We'll try to stick to the schedule,
but I did want to spend a bit longer watching the story this time.
I did ask staff if I could indulge myself on the story this time, so we'll spend a bit more time watching it.
I hope you'll enjoy watching it with me.
So with that, let's jump right into talking about the Colors of Pure Sense event story.
How did you like the story, everyone?
Let's look back together while going over some of the messages you've sent in.
So actually, this is the first time I've done an AfterTalk since they got renewed.
Last time I was here was a year ago, and that's around when the renewal happened,
so I haven't gotten a chance to bring your thoughts into the story talk yet.
I'm excited.
This letter is from Amelia Time.
"This is the first time I'm writing in!"
Thank you!
"My favorite scene was the one where Ena deletes her selfie account."
"Seeing her make the decision to stop running away and finally confront her art really showed how much she's grown."
"Like Ena, I was also afraid of facing myself and kept running away,"
"but seeing Ena's positive attitude gave me the push I needed,"
"and made me want to do my best too."
"Suzuki-san, what kind of feelings did you put into your performance of Ena this time?"
Thank you very much for the message.
That was a wonderful message, Amelia Time.
Let's see.
I'd like to talk more about it while watching the story later,
but something I'm more conscious of when acting as Ena, both in this event and when singing recent N25 songs,
is her resolve to not go back to the old Ena.
I personally kept that in mind because,
even if the pace is slow, Ena is moving forward bit by bit.
So while N25's songs often has negative or pessimistic lyrics,
and the music usually has a darker mood,
but I tried not to make that the main thing in this song.
Like, maybe if were to I add just a hint of tearing up or a regretful tone,
that might make a line, or the song as a whole, stand out more to the listeners' ears.
So people might say "Oh, I like this part," or "that was nice, let me play that again."
Those kinds of lines would probably leave more of an impression on people's ears.
But that would just be my own desire for validation as Suzuki.
I wanted to show Ena's gradual steps forward in both the songs and the story dialogue.
So even with the same words, I wanted to make sure you could feel that she's moving forward.
And so thinking of the story too, I sang more positively as the song went on.
That's what I kept in mind while performing for this time.
And so... yeah.
In this event and recent songs, she's realized that the world is warmer than she thought,
and she knows that the people around her will support her.
I made sure to reflect that in my performance.
Now, moving on,
Let's read another message.
This one is from Sudachi Udon.
"Hello, Minori-san."
Hello!
"I read through Colors of Pure Sense."
Thank you.
"What left an impression on me was the scene in Episode 7 where Ena gets so excited because she's having so much fun painting."
"Ena previously could only feel validation from others, like with her selfie account,"
"but she finally realized, 'I'm fine just as I am. My world and the way I express myself can be as free as I want them to be.'"
"See Ena's world is gradually becoming more colorful and her eyes start to sparkle,"
"all as she says drawing is fun. I connected with that moment thanks to your voice, Minori-san,"
"It moved me to tears."
"I want to continue watching over and supporting Ena, who has resolved not to give up on her art and her dreams."
From Niyori-san... "Thank you so much for..." Oh, what a lovely message.
"Thank you so much bringing the colors of Ena's heart to life so vividly with your wonderful vocal performance.
I'm the one who should be thanking you for appreciating it that way.
I always hope that Ena's feelings will reach everyone.
Of course, she's a character in a game, a 2D character,
but Ena is truly alive.
And no one knows what her future holds yet,
so I—how to say...
I really want to deliver something that feels real.
So thank you for such a kind message.
All right.
Anyway, I still have so much to talk about. If I just keep chatting here,
it'll already be 10:05 and we'll have to skip watching the story.
So let's move right along.
I've picked out some scenes I personally want to talk about,
so let's watch them together.
I was a bit selfish today with the selection.
The staff are shaking their heads when I say "selfish,"
But um,
I actually really wanted to watch from Episode 1 to 8 with you all.
But let's just watch Episodes 7 and 8.
This is an AfterTalk, so Minori will be be talking quite a bit.
Minori, uh, that's me.
So if you think I'm yapping too much, please go back and watch the story in the game later.
Let's get started.
Episodes 7 and 8.
Here we go.
I think she knew deep down all along.
Like, "I'm just avoiding it, aren't I?"
Ena's already made so many promises to herself,
so she knew she'd been using selfies as an escape or a crutch.
But she couldn't run away.
She wants to go to Tobi.
But she didn't have the resolve to tell those herself or those around her yet.
But this time, she's telling herself "no, I won't run away," and "I will decide."
She knows it's not a smooth road ahead, but it feels like the fog in her heart has cleared.
She feels that relief, but also there's a lot ahead for her.
I knew Ena had a lot on her mind about the road ahead,
but I also knew that she felt a huge sense of relief after all this. So I acted with this both feelings in mind.
The reason I chose Episodes 7 and 8 is because of her father.
They've been through a lot, and there were times she couldn't face him, but she really admires him.
As she grew up a lot happened between them,
and he isn't the best with words, so she butted heads with him a bit.
But as she grew as an artist, she started to remember those feelings of admiration for him she hid out of frustration.
That's why I got to voicing young Ena was so special.
As a child, she was so pure, and everything was new and sparkling.
And in that world was her father, and he was someone she looked up to.
Someone who creates amazing things.
I imagined Ena talking to him as just this mass of pure light.
I played that scene keeping in mind that feeling of wonder and delight Ena had for her father and the art he created.
And because of that, I could continue back into Ena's drawing scene keeping that same wonderful and sparkling feeling.
Being able to draw with so much joy while embracing that feeling was a huge moment.
And for the first time, she could clearly say, "It's fun."
This is such an important point for Ena to reach.
She's still on her journey, but she finally made it here.
And so— Oh, I'm gonna cry.
And so when— Ah, this is bad.
When I first saw the script at home, I cried so much.
I was just so happy for her.
Wah! This is a total broadcast accident.
It's been five years—well, not five years in Ena's timeline—
but there's so been so much building up to this.
I think many of you find Ena's story very relatable.
Since I'm also in a world of art where there are no "correct" answers,
I really understand her.
But more than that, seeing Ena's hard work finally start to pay off...
well, "pay off" is a simple way to put it, but...
Thank you.
I was so happy that I cried for her as Minori Suzuki. I was like "Good for you!"
And while reading, I felt Ena's relief that she finally made it here.
She could finally feel this simple feeling. She's worked so hard to come to this point and finally let go of all that tension and angst.
Ah, sorry... I have plenty of tissues here.
Yeah, I put all those feelings into acting and the tears just started flowing naturally.
There were parts where I got choked up and couldn't get the words out, but that's what acting is all about.
That actually helps get across Ena's feelings though acting all the more.
Since I started crying—
Since I started crying as Ena, I knew she was crying with me.
They actually adjusted to my timing—
So usually, you can click to advance the dialogue right as the line ends,
but they didn't cut any of the recording and let the pauses naturally hold before showing the next button. I'm so grateful.
I've received so many comments saying this was a great story.
And it wasn't just about how my acting was, or how my voice sounded as Suzuki Minori.
Instead of focusing on me, everyone really took Ena's attitude and determination to heart.
So many people were glad for here, some felt encouraged to work hard too,
and long-time fans were just so glad to see her payoff.
Even though her journey is just beginning, I'm so glad people care so much for Ena.
I poured my absolute all into portraying Ena and how far she's come for this, so I'm really happy with how it turned out.
That's right.
Yeah.
Now, let's take a look at the illustrations.
By the way, I chose this one because it's the moment Ena finally sees a glimmer of hope after suffering so much for her art.
All right.
Let's spend about four minutes looking at the card illustrations together.
Before that, I have some comments about the costumes to share from the illustration team.
"The theme of this story is Ena's struggle to get into art school,"
"becoming discouraged after not getting the grades she was hoping for, but ultimately deciding not to quit."
"Our motif this time was an art apron over a school uniform,"
"designed to capture Ena's look as a student preparing for entrance exams."
"While she's had had other apron outfits, this time we gave Ena a patched-up one."
"This represents her persistence through repeated setbacks, fitting the themes from this specific story."
"We kept strong uniform elements like the sailor collar and pleats,"
"but modified the overall form to give it more of a costume feel."
And this is the illustration.
And then the pre-trained version... everyone seemed to really like this one.
She looks like she's having fun painting.
Her hands are all messy.
It's so wonderful.
And here are the untrained and post-trained cards of everyone supported Ena through this.
Kanade is a creator herself,
so even though their genres are different, she understands Ena's feelings. And KAITO...
Yeah, KAITO gave Ena so many important words of advice.
There's also that scene where they're eating ice cream. So I named the team "Frozen Yogurt."
That's just because I personally love frozen yogurt.
My desires are leaking through.
And here's Miku.
So cute.
So many lovely paintings.
Look, they're eating ice cream!
So cute.
And finally, Mafuyu— wait, oops.
Ah, I can't long-press.
There we go.
She's holding the apron.
Yes, so adorable.
Thank you so much.
So, you've seen the pre- and post-trained illustrations...
Oh, come on—
Anyway, those were the illustrations.
I have a few more minutes, so I'll talk a bit more about the story.
So, in one of the previous stories—I'm trying to remember...
Which was it?
The last one wasn't specifically about her art,
So I think it was the one before that, where we sang "I'm the Rain."
During that story about Ena's drawing—"drawing" sounds a bit off.
About her painting, I happened to visit an art museum.
I got to understand how it felt to actually look at paintings, and through that, I was able to understand and act as Ena better.
But before this event story, I was just walking down the street,
and I passed an actual art prep school, the kind Ena would attend. It was just right there on the street.
I felt this intense tension just looking from the outside, and it reminded me how tough her world is.
And I put in those thoughts into the recording.
Every day, I try to act in a way that conveys the reality of the Ena's situation.
Thank you.
All right.
So...
Um...
I still have a few dozen seconds left.
Some of you might have already seen the AfterLive by now.
It follows the content of Episode 8,
so you can see Ena's refreshed expression. Things will still be hard for her,
but I hope her resolve comes through in her expression and her singing.
I hope it's reaching all of you right now.
Yes.
Right?
Man, it really is a great story.
Ena is so loved.
I'm so grateful we got such a wonderful story.
With that said, I'd like to talk about the music after we watch the 3DMV that was written specifically for this event.
Please, take a look.
Breathing inside a borrowed life, in a body that can't become anyone.
If I dive deep into the depths, the me from that day...
is still smiling.
Looking back, there were certainly fragments of dreams sprouting in my chest.
Pressed down by the weight of strings, they eventually turned into hatred.
There's no use in trying to stroke the past.
This small, gentle light... my belief still won't reach.
Even so, I want to draw more of the future with these hands on the white scenery before me.
Even if the past isn't beautiful, I'll be myself.
I just want to draw...
this world that reflects in my eyes.
And we're back. Sorry about that.
My screen just popped up there.
That was the 3DMV for the song Chouchou-P wrote for this event, titled "The Name of Your Drawing."
Wait, I got mixed up. That was the 3DMV for "The name of painting."
Uh...
Should I do this first? Oh, I see.
For a second, I mixed up my own notes with Chouchou-P's comments.
I was like, "Wait, what?"
Ok so, Let me read the notes I sent to the staff beforehand.
"Just listening to it evokes memories of Ena's long journey, and it brings me to tears."
"The title has her name in it, so I felt it was truly a song written for Ena."
"Embracing the regret and pain that she's felt along her journey, instead of just lamenting it,"
"I sang with the newfound optimism and determination she has to turn those feelings into strength."
That's what past-me sent in to the staff.
Chouchou-P's actual comments were introduced on the ProSeka News Station and such.
They should be on Twitter—I mean, X—as well, so please check them out.
But yeah, those were the feelings I put into the song.
Well...
There are lyrics that feel like she's looking back at the past.
But it really is like the current Ena is the one doing the reflecting.
I'm sure Ena has regrets,
But I think she's a girl who understands that those regrets made her who she is today.
So even for the phrases about the past, I didn't want to sing them with the pure regret of the old Ena.
So while embracing those feelings, I sang with her newer sense of resolve.
Like I said during the story part,
I tried to include that sense of relief and the brightness of finally feeling the joy in painting again.
But also that this isn't the goal; it's a new start.
I was very conscious of capturing that duality while singing.
So rather than a huge outburst or breakthrough of emotion,
it's more like quietly reflection within myself to cheer myself on.
Like patting my own chest and saying, "Let's do this."
That's the image I had in mind as I sang.
I just end up crying, though.
I've already heard the full version, you see.
Since I'm the one who sang it.
I'm sorry.
I just can't help but cry.
I'm just so hopeless.
Both this story and the song just make me tear up.
What am I going to do? What should we do?
I thought I wouldn't cry this time, but I did anyway.
Yeah.
To those of you who felt a bit jealous that I've heard the full version, don't worry.
The 2DMV for this new song, "The Name of Your Drawing,"
will be uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel at 10:15 PM.
Please check that out along with the 3DMV.
If it's like the previous 2DMVs, that means you'll be able to hear the full version too, right?
I haven't even seen the 2DMV myself yet.
Now, to give some belated thoughts on the 3DMV...
I sang the full song for the recording, but I knew how the lines were split,
so I knew which parts would be Ena's.
The song starts with the other three members of N25 singing one after another.
So in the 3DMV inside my head—my imaginary 3DMV—it didn't start with Ena.
I was wondering how it would actually begin.
Would all four, or rather five of them appear at once?
Or would it start with Mizuki, who has the first line?
But then I saw it was showing Ena for the whole opening.
Of course, I'm always happy when other characters get a lot of screen time for their fans, too.
But this MV put such a huge spotlight on Ena, and it matched the story so perfectly.
It really felt like it was capturing Ena's journey and current attitude.
As her voice actress, that made me so incredibly happy.
It's always been like this, but Ena's commissioned songs always feel like she's getting closer and closer to the surface.
Well, that's just my own otaku analysis.
But things like that make me happy too.
I've only seen it a few times myself, so I want to sit down and watch it properly.
I'm so excited for the 2DMV.
Yeah.
I think that's everything... I don't think I've left anything out.
Well, I've truly entrusted everything to Ena's voice.
More than anything, I hope you can feel Ena's thoughts and attitude through the music and the story.
Everyone, please continue to support Ena.
Thank you so much for watching over her.
Though I may not Ena herself,
but as the person who voices her, I feel like I'm someone close to her.
She's made a new resolution, and I'll work hard as an actress to express her growth, so please keep watching over her.
Thank you.
It's been a short time, but that's all for this ProSeka AfterTalk: Colors of Pure Sense edition.
To everyone watching the stream, how did you like it?
If you haven't finished the story for the Colors of Pure Sense event yet...
Did I look funny crying so much like this?
You can read the whole thing from the Event Story menu once the next event starts.
So please, give it a read.
We're always looking for messages for our AfterTalks.
You can submit them through the official ProSeka Discord channel or via email.
Please send one in when the next AfterTalk event starts.
Just make sure your messages are related to the event.
It'd be a waste if I couldn't read it because it was about something else.
Right.
In just about ten or twenty seconds...
the 2DMV will be out, so let's watch it together.
I'll watch it as soon as we close out here, so you should all check it out too.
So with that, see you next time.
Goodbye!