ProSeka AfterTalk: Colors of Pure Sense Edition
Hello, everyone. Good evening.
I'm Suzuki Minori, the voice of Ena Shinonome from Nightcord at 25:00.
In this ProSeka AfterTalk, we'll look back on the event while reading the messages you've sent in.
Today's episode covers the Colors of Pure Sense event.
I hope you all enjoyed the story!
Thank you so much.
Between the Thanksgiving event and the stage greetings for the movie,
things have been quite busy with real-life cast events lately.
And then this Niigo event, Ena's story event, started right away.
I'm sure it's been a whirlwind for everyone, but I hope you've been enjoying it all.
We previously asked for messages for this AfterTalk via the official ProSeka Discord and email.
Thank you all for writing in.
I honestly wish the staff would let me sneak a peek at every single one.
I'm really curious to hear what you all thought.
I'll be sharing some of those messages during the show,
so please look forward to that.
Also, please post your thoughts on the event or this stream using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
I'm also keeping an eye on the YouTube chat,
so I'll be picking out comments that catch my eye.
All right.
Let's see...
I see comments like "It was a great story."
And people saying "Kon-Niigo!"
Kon-Niigo to you all!
Also, we have the AfterLive starting at 10:00 PM,
and the 3DMV for this event will be released at 10:05 PM.
I'd love to watch those together with everyone.
I want to make sure we stay on schedule, but I also want to spend a good amount of time on the story video.
I was a bit selfish and asked to make the story segment longer than usual,
so I hope you'll stick around and watch it with me.
Now, let's start talking about the story
for Colors of Pure Sense.
What did you all think of this story?
Let's look back on it together while I read your messages.
This is actually my first time doing the renewed version of ProSeka AfterTalk.
It's been about a year, and back then it was the old format.
So, I'm really happy to be weaving this show together using your words.
This first message is from Amelia Time.
"This is my first time sending in my thoughts."
Thank you so much!
"The scene that left the biggest impression on me was when Ena deleted her selfie account."
"I felt her growth when she, who used to run away from her art, finally decided to face it head-on."
"Like Ena, I was also afraid to face myself and kept running away,"
"but seeing Ena's positive attitude gave me a push, and I want to try my best too."
"Suzuki-san, what kind of feelings"
"did you put into your performance of Ena this time?"
Thank you for the wonderful message.
Well...
Amelia Time, that was a lovely letter. Let's see...
I'll talk more about this while we watch the story later, but regarding Ena this time,
and also when singing recent Niigo songs, there's something I've been conscious of.
As her voice actress, I personally tell myself, "I won't let her go back to the old Ena."
Even if it's slow, Ena is moving forward bit by bit. Because of the nature of Niigo's music, the lyrics can often be quite pessimistic,
and the songs themselves have a certain heavy atmosphere.
But I try not to let her get pulled too far into that. Honestly, as a song or a performance,
adding a hint of tears or a negative nuance might make it more striking to the listener,
or make people think, "Oh, I love the way she delivered that phrase."
There are definitely parts that catch your ear because of that.
But I realized that's just my own desire for validation as an actress.
I want to make sure I put the fact that Ena is looking forward, even if just a little, into her songs and lines.
So even with the same words, I try to deliver them so you can feel her progress.
I've been gradually increasing that sense of positivity based on the story.
That's what I've been keeping in mind
while playing her this time.
And...
Yeah.
In this event and in recent songs, she's not as cynical about things anymore.
I think Ena now truly understands that the world is warmer than she thought,
and that the people around her are there to help her.
I made sure to reflect that in my performance.
Now, moving on,
I'll read one more message.
This one is from Sudachi Udon.
"Minori-san, good evening."
Yes, good evening!
"I've finished reading Colors of Pure Sense."
Thank you very much.
"The scene that stuck with me was in Episode 7, where Ena gets so excited because she's having so much fun drawing."
"Ena, who could only boost her self-esteem through others' praise on her selfie account, finally realized she's fine just as she is."
I realized that my world and my expression can be as free as I want them to be,
and as Ena's world gradually gained color and her eyes sparkled with the joy of painting, I could really feel it through your voice.
It moved me to tears.
I want to keep watching over and supporting Ena as she resolves to never give up on her art and her dreams.
Minori-san, "the color of Ena's heart"... what a beautiful way to put it.
Thank you so much for bringing that to life so vividly through your performance.
Thank you for that message.
And thank you for taking those feelings to heart.
I always think about how I want Ena's heart to reach everyone.
Of course, she's a game character, a 2D existence,
but Ena is truly alive, and well...
No one knows what the future holds for her yet.
So, how should I put it?
I really want to deliver something that feels raw and real.
I'm so happy to hear your thoughts. Thank you.
All right.
Moving on...
There's so much I want to talk about while watching the story, so if I get too carried away now,
well,
five minutes will pass in a flash.
So let's keep things moving.
I've picked out some scenes that I personally want to talk about,
so let's watch them together.
I was a bit selfish with my choices today.
The staff are shaking their heads like "no, you weren't," but...
well,
I really struggled to choose.
I felt like I could just watch from Episode 1 to 8 with you all,
but
we're going to look at Episodes 7 and 8.
This is an AfterTalk, so I'll be doing a lot of talking.
Since I'll be chatting away,
if you find me too noisy, please go back and watch the scenes in the game later.
Okay, let's get started.
Episodes 7 and 8.
Here we go.
She's... calmed down.
I think she knew deep down all along.
Wait, was her account hacked?
Oh, it's gone.
This is Ena after making so many resolutions and steeling herself.
...
What does this mean?
That account for her selfies...
Those selfies were a bit of an escape for her,
something she relied on.
But she couldn't run away anymore.
She even went to the Peach Garden.
But she still lacked the confidence to tell those around her or even fully commit herself.
In this story,
she was finally able to truly make up her mind.
That's why.
It's painful from here on, but there's a sense of relief, like the fog in her heart has cleared.
I put all those complex feelings into it,
and I acted the final scenes while thinking about how Ena must feel relieved too.
The reason I chose Episodes 7 and 8 is because of her father. They've been through a lot and there were times she couldn't face him, but she really does admire him.
Her father isn't great with words, and Ena had hidden her respect for him behind her own frustration. But as she grew as an artist, she remembered those feelings. I also got to voice young Ena, who was so pure and saw the world as something sparkling and new, with her father right there in the middle of it.
To her, her father was someone she looked up to,
someone who could create incredible things.
He was like a mass of light.
I acted while keeping that image of talking to someone like that in mind, feeling the greatness of the art he creates.
Because I performed with that sparkle in my heart,
there were many scenes where she's told she can keep painting.
I performed those scenes without many breaks, just letting the emotions flow.
The scenery she saw with her father, the voice of her father...
It wasn't just about being held; it was about Ena finally being able to enjoy painting. Seeing her way of life reach everyone meant a lot to me personally.
I'm so happy that people are pleased and feel like they've been given a push forward.
Some said it made them want to do their best too.
For those who have been supporting Ena all this time, she's finally reached a point on her journey.
I'm so glad she finally made it here. But it's only just beginning.
Still, there were so many emotions...
I'm so moved by Ena.
It makes me so happy that everyone could empathize with her feelings.
Truly.
Actually, when I first saw the script, I burst into tears.
While reading it.
I'm so glad I could give it my all in the performance.
I really am.
I'm just so glad it's out there now.
That's how I feel.
That's right.
...
Looking at the illustrations, the core of Ena's journey...
is that she's been facing her art for years. It's not just that she likes it; she's suffered and struggled with many emotions while continuing to paint.
I think many of you found it easy to empathize with the moment in the story where a glimmer of hope finally appeared for her.
That's how I feel, anyway.
...
Now, since we have about four minutes left,
I'd like for us to take a look at the card illustrations together.
Before we look at the art, the illustration team, who understands Ena's feelings so well,
provided some comments about the costume Ena worked so hard for. Let me introduce those.
This time, it's about Ena's struggle to get into art school...
Saying she's "rewarded" might be too simple, but it's about her moving forward through that struggle.
Thank you very much.
The theme of the story was about facing a setback when her skills didn't reach the required level,
but still not giving up. When I first read the script, I really felt that core theme.
The design motif is a school uniform with a personal apron for painting. Congratulations to Suzuki for the production!
The design was made to look like an art student's style during their entrance exams.
As a style for Ena as a painter, it feels like she's finally made it this far.
While the outfit for this event is simple, the apron is made of patchwork.
This represents her standing tall and persevering even after nearly giving up many times.
It's a design with unique touches,
almost like things are finally coming together. Excuse me.
I need a lot of tissues... Here's the sailor collar.
They kept elements of the school uniform, like the collar and pleats, to leave a strong impression,
but added a tear-shaped arrangement.
They were very conscious of making it feel like a proper costume.
Seeing that in the illustration and the acting... it really comes through.
It really does.
Playing Ena... and then seeing the Training After version... the reaction from everyone was huge.
I was crying while recording,
and Ena is crying while she paints too.
Her hands are all dirty.
It's so moving.
And to all of you who watched over Ena and pressed the button to support her,
helping her move forward to the next step...
The time leading up to that button press, both before and after training, is truly precious. Thank you for everything.
I'm just so grateful and moved. As someone on the creative side,
I had so many thoughts about this story.
Even though the genre is different, I felt I could really understand Ena's feelings.
And Kaito... Kaito-san gave Ena so many important words.
They even eat ice cream together, so please check that out.
I called it "Yogurt Ice Cream" in my head.
That's because I personally love yogurt ice cream.
So...
It's like, "Wait, it's just your preference?"
And then there's Miku-san.
...
What a lovely picture.
She's eating ice cream too.
...
So cute.
And Mafuyu...
If you long-press...
...
She's holding an apron.
Thank you very much.
So, we've looked at the illustrations for before and after training.
Oh man, how many times have I done this now?
Thank you for taking a look.
I can talk about the story for a few more minutes, so I will.
Regarding the previous story... well,
how should I put it?
It wasn't specifically about her art.
Before that, I sang the song "I am Rain."
When we had a story about Ena's art—I don't like saying "drawings"—
when we had a story about her art, I happened to go to a museum.
I was able to act while keeping in mind what it means to look at a painting.
To get to know Ena better... this time, I happened to be walking down a street,
and there was a school that people aiming for art school probably attend.
I thought, "So this is what it's like."
Even just looking from the outside, I felt a great sense of tension. I recorded my lines while realizing how tough of an environment she's in.
I try to act every day in a way that conveys the atmosphere of the place where Ena is to all of you.
Thank you very much.
So, we have a few dozen seconds left.
By now, some of you might have already seen the AfterLive.
Since it takes place after the story,
you can see Ena's refreshed face. Things will still be hard from here on out,
but you can see in her expression that she's truly made her decision.
I'd be happy if my voice and the song are reaching you all right now.
Truly.
Yes.
It's such a good story. Ena...
...is truly loved.
I'm so grateful for such a wonderful story.
With that said, let's talk about the song after we watch the 3DMV created for this event.
Here it is.
Breathing within a borrowed life and a body that can't become anyone.
If I dive deep inside, the me from that day I started drawing...
...is still smiling.
Looking back, it's certainly there,
the dream that had sprouted in my heart.
Crushed by the shadow of ideals,
it's no use stroking a past that eventually turned into hatred.
This small, gentle,
belief hasn't reached yet.
Even so, parched,
the pure white scenery before my eyes,
I'll try to paint more of the future with these hands.
Even if it's not beautiful,
in my own way,
just what I see,
I will keep painting this world.
And there we go... sorry, my screen just cut out.
The title of the song written for this event is being revealed for the first time.
The title is 'The Name of That Painting'.
That was the 3DMV.
Oh.
Wait, I have it here.
For a second, I thought my own notes were Chouchou-P's comments.
My mistake.
These are the notes I sent to the staff beforehand.
I'll read them.
Just listening to it makes me feel Ena's journey, and it brings me to tears.
The title contains the characters for 'painting' and 'Na' from her name,
so it really feels like a song written specifically for Ena.
Rather than just being pessimistic about regrets, frustration, and pain,
I sang this with her resolve to turn those feelings into strength and the positive outlook she gained from that resolve.
That's what the past me emailed to the staff.
As for Chouchou-P's comments, they've been introduced on the ProSeka Station and such,
and I think they're on Twitter—or X—so please check them out there.
Yes, those were the feelings I put into the song.
There are lyrics that feel like she's looking back at the past,
but it feels like the current Ena is the one doing the reflecting.
Ena definitely has regrets,
but she's a girl who understands that those regrets made her who she is today. So even for the phrases looking back,
I didn't want to sing them with total agonizing pain. I kept that in mind while recording.
Like I said earlier, she's found her resolve.
I sang with that sense of relief and the bright feeling of finally understanding, while keeping the story in mind.
But this isn't the goal; it's a new start.
I tried to capture that middle-ground feeling while singing.
So, rather than a huge explosion of emotion, it's more like quietly reciting the words within myself to spur me on.
Like I'm patting my own chest and telling myself to do my best.
I sang it with that kind of self-encouragement in mind.
I guess I really am going to cry.
I can hear the full version...
I'm the one who sang it, though.
I'm sorry.
I'm tearing up.
I just can't help it.
Both this story and the song just make me cry.
What should I do?
I really thought I wouldn't cry this time,
but here I am.
Yeah.
To those of you who were a bit jealous that I get to hear the full version...
Don't worry.
The 2DMV for this new song, 'The Name of That Painting', will be uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel at 22:15.
Please check that out along with the 3DMV.
So that means you'll be able to hear the full version too.
I hope the 2D MV is as great as always.
I haven't seen the 2DMV myself yet.
It's a bit late, but regarding my thoughts on the 3DMV...
We recorded the full version originally,
and the lines are distributed, so I wondered which parts would be Ena's.
The song starts with the other three members of Niigo in order.
In the 3DMV in my head, I thought, 'Oh, it's not Ena?'
I was wondering how it would start.
I wondered if all four or five of them would just pop onto the screen.
I thought it would start with Mizuki since they sing the first line, but...
Ena was on screen the whole time. Of course, because of that...
I'm sure fans of other characters are happy when their favorites get more screen time too.
But this MV really put the spotlight on Ena.
It matches the story so well, and I felt like the MV really captured Ena's way of life.
As Ena's voice actress, that made me really happy.
Her art is always featured, but the songs for Ena's stories...
The setting feels like it's gradually moving closer to the surface, and I like that.
Well, that's just my own geeky theory, but it makes me happy.
I've only seen it a few times myself, so I want to take a closer look later.
I'm so excited for the 2D MV.
Yeah.
I think that's it.
I don't think I have anything left to say.
Not really, but I've put everything into Ena's voice.
I've entrusted it all to her, so more than anything, I hope you can feel Ena's way of life through the song and story.
Everyone, please keep supporting Ena.
To everyone who supports her, thank you so much.
I'm not Ena myself, but...
As her voice actress, I like to think I'm close to her. She's made a new resolution, and I'll do my best to express her growth as an actress, so please keep an eye on her.
Thank you.
It's been a short time, but that's all for ProSeka AfterTalk.
You can read the whole event story in the game,
so please check it out.
We're always looking for messages for AfterTalk.
You can send them via the AfterTalk channel on the official ProSeka Discord or by email.
Please send one in when the next AfterTalk event is held.
Please make sure your messages are related to the event.
It'd be a waste if they didn't get read because they were off-topic.
Right.
So, it's almost time. In just a few dozen seconds...
The 2D MV will be out, so let's watch it together.
I'll watch it as soon as I close this stream, so you all should watch it too.
With that, I'll see you all again.
Goodbye!
Oh, I still have time?
Um...