Welcome to Project Sekai Aftertalk "Find the dream view" Edition!
Good evening everyone, this is Yuki Nakashima, voice of Shiho Hinomori.
In this Aftertalk, we'll recap the event while reading letters that you, the fans, have sent in.
So, how did you like the "Find the dream view" event story, everyone?
"Good 'need'-vening!*" Good 'need'-vening hahaha.
You know, I think you guys are the only ones who say that back to me.
Thank you for that.
"Good 'need'-vening" hasn't really caught on among us yet.
Do you think it'd be alright if we turned this into our official greeting? Hahaha
Leoni doesn't have a greeting yet like "wonderhoi",
I just said it on a radio episode once and it seems to have stuck with you guys, so thank you.
Is it okay to make it official? Not sure haha
Guess I just have to keep pushing it.
We've actually been using 'Kon-niido' for a pretty long time now, haven't we? www
Alright, with that— is it okay to start?
Let's talk about the "Find the dream view" event story.
I see in the chat you've all already been saying "the story was awesome", but what did you think?
Let's look back through the story while reading some of your letters.
First up, a letter from "Mist-san", thank you for the message.
"That live performance at the end of the story was peak excitement."
"I was blown away by the new special features added thanks to the 4th Anniversary update."
"Even through the screen, I was just as moved as the live audience."
"I thought, 'Leo/need is so awesome!'"
Yay~! Thank you.
I mean, that performance...
That performance really hit me as well.
It was way too good.
Later, I have some stuff I want to talk about for that part of the story,
but let's save that for later.
Moving onto the next letter.
From Pusesuki(?)-san, thanks for the message.
"This story was super exciting!"
"Especially in Chapter 7, seeing Leoni surrounded by an audience that isn't too familiar with them,"
"I got so fired up that I wanted to reach through the screen and shout 'do your best, Leoni!'"
"So when I heard 'star trail' playing, together with the cut-ins, I just ascended."
"I'm interested if you have any stories to share about recording for the event story or song."
Thank you so much.
I'm so glad to hear so many of your thoughts about Chapter 7 and questions about recording for the event story and song.
So let's start by watching the much-discussed Chapter 7.
I'm gonna cut out the chapter viewing because tbh Yuki doesn't say too much.
Also I don't wanna figure out how to add in the story subs lmao
Here we go!
Chapter 7 is soooo gooooood.
The story before it, too.
I mean, it's a 15,000-person venue, right?
Maybe Tokyo? Wonder where exactly it is.
Where would there be space for a 15,000-person venue?
I think Ariake Arena is around that size.
K-Arena is a little bigger.
But they're at a venue that big already...
But this venue...
It's Ariake Arena? Ehhhhh?!
I'm kind of glad.
Isn't that crazy?
Ahhhhhh.... Chapter 7... so peak...
I didn't really talk much, did I. Was too busy just watching.
Chapter 7 was seriously way too good.
So with that, we have a comment about this scene from the story production director.
Wait, that's awesome. We're gonna start having these staff commentaries with this mini-renewal.
Let's read it.
"In this event, we wanted to create a special animation showing that fleeting moment where the Leo/need members all meet eyes."
"Chapter 7 continues with depictions of each member's emotional state, so we wanted to not only capture the excitement of the performance,
"but also focus on the shift in those emotions."
"Through this animation, we wanted to convey the four’s shared desire,"
"to reach others with Leo/need’s music;
not just to their audience, but to our players as well."
"Also, as a slight change from previous events, we used BGM with vocals this time."
"We wanted to show the girls' music in the most impactful way possible through our visuals,"
"so we created this sequence where the four all meet eyes, the BGM chorus kicks in, the card stills appear, and each character speaks."
"It all comes together for a top notch scene."
"We went through a lot of trial and error on the technical side to deliver the best version of this scene possible, so we hope you enjoy it."
Incredible. Wasn’t that such a great scene, everyone?
So for the first BGM with vocals for Leoni, we recorded "star trail".
This time, we recorded with— we usually record with the same team,
but this time, we recorded with a different team than usual.
It felt— how should I put this,
recording for this song was more focused on calls from the background.
I think if you listen closely, Shiho is cheering everyone on in her own way.
She's going like "hai hai".
Lots of parts worth taking an extra listen for.
This is, how to say, through and through, a Leo/need song.
Maaaaan, I'm so glad at how well that scene turned out.
I mean, using that BGM there though is a bit unfair, isn't it? www
Like, you can't really help but cry there.
I was really just moved by the whole thing.
Yeah— "Full version when???" Right?
Not sure if we'll get the chance to do a full version...
Maybe if enough people ask for it.
Please ask for it. Please and thank you.
Ah—
Ehhhh!!??
Of course I get nervous.
"I know you have experience, but do you still get nervous on big stages?"
"How is it?*"
*The commenter used "donai" which is a
very Kansai dialect way of asking "how is it (for you)"
Hahahaha thank you for the question.
I get super nervous. Generally I'm the type to get really nervous.
But actually, for the first time performing on a stage this big,
I definitely think Shiho was a bit nervous, going up on a stage like that not knowing what it would feel like.
But for my first time, instead of feeling nerves, I was like:
"I have no idea what's gonna happen, so I'm not nervous!"
Haha something like that.
Then I actually stepped on stage and was like,
"oh crap we're actually gonna perform here?"
Then I started feeling nervous.
Yeah, it was something like that.
Now that I think about it, I don't think I've ever gone out on stage not feeling a bit nervous.
For one reason or another, I always end up nervous.
And in this story,
Leo/need was the opening act for an audience
that wasn't really familiar with them.
I've also had that experience before where you can kind of feel that lots of the audience isn't really as familiar with your music.
Somehow you can tell they're going like
"hmm, I'm not really sure how to vibe to this."
When that happens, sometimes you kind of just want to say "just follow along with us". Myself included.
But, I know exactly what it feels like to have that disconnect with the audience,
which is why the emotions in Chapter 7 were just so incredibly real.
When I first read the script for this story, seeing the slightly critical comments after the band was announced,
or the characters feeling like "maybe we should have practiced even more",
it felt so relatable.
I've felt the same thing so many times.
I feel the exact same way so often, that I actually started crying just reading the script.
It really moved me.
So when it came to recording this chapter—
for the event stories, we usually individually record one chapter at a time.
Usually we kind of just breeze through each one.
But for Chapter 7, there was so much coming from the heart, so many emotions coming out.
There were so many monologues.
I was directed to "just lay everything out bare."
I said "I got this. Let's do it!" Then recorded Chapter 7 all in one take.
Then they were just like "Ah, okay we got it," and we were done in one go.
Yeah, I think that just shows how naturally I was able to empathize with the script.
I think the story did an amazing job capturing this reality of performing.
And I really hope that really came through.
Yeah, I was really surprised we did Chapter 7 all in one take like that too.
So, I’d love for you to go back and watch not just that scene, but the whole story from Chapter 1 to 8.
And please check out the side stories for each card, too.
"Such a real story". Definitely.
Such a good story, and such a good production too.
Actually, did you see the card art move a bit?
That really made that scene hit harder, didn't it.
This is just a bit of wishful thinking, but wouldn't it be great if all cards could have something like that?
Like maybe just a cool little animation when
you pull them, even if it's just for 4 stars.
I’m putting that out into the universe right now www
Alright then, that's all we have for our story discussion.
So in a previous letter, we had a question about any stories from recording the event song.
Also gonna cut this, don't wanna deal with copyright.
Just go watch it on official YouTube haha
So first we’ll watch the 2DMV for the event song "Sympathy" together, written for us by Eve-san.
Then we’ll talk about some of the stories from the recording.
So let’s start by watching the MV. Enjoy!
You just listened to "Sympathy" by Eve-san.
Ahh, such a good song, isn't it?
So actually, this was the first song I ever had to do a "key check" for.
So I think you can tell if you've heard some of Eve-san's other songs,
but their songs have both super low- and high-pitched parts.
They're able to create songs that bring together so many different registers.
They told me "this song will be just like that,"
so they asked me to do a key check.
So I said "oh, okay, got it."
But when I asked why we're going to do one,
Shiho usually sings with a pretty low voice in a lot of the songs.
It does also fit her image well.
We were worried that if I were to sing too high, it might drift away from that image somewhat.
So in the chorus,
the part that goes "kodamashite~",
"let it ring out"
they wanted me to really belt it out in my chest voice.
We were like, "Is there a key that would let you hit those belt notes while also bringing out those low-pitched sounds?"
In the end, they let me decide.
I told them the original key seemed fine, so we stuck with the original key.
If we lowered it, the pre-chorus would’ve been too low.
If it was just me, I might have been able to hit it, but the other members might have struggled.
But I figured with the original key, I could really belt out the chorus,
and even though the high notes in the second half are pretty up there,
I told them "I can make it work," and we went with it.
You can hear this in other songs too, like "Peaky Peaky",
if you listen again, you'll see what I mean.
In the Another Vocal version, I think, for KAITO's parts,
we ended up using just the original range, without going an octave down.
But for this session, we actually recorded versions both an octave down and in the same key as KAITO.
Then usually, the staff decides which version to use in the final mix.
We always record extra takes like that just in case.
But then in that April Fools' cover we did for "Envy Baby,"
they actually ended up using both versions.
In the "haifai koiseyo raiaia" part,
"fall in a high-fi love lie-ai-a"
at first, they wanted me to record that in the original key,
but I was like "can I really sing this as Shiho?"
I was like "could we record an octave down just in case?"
And it turns out they used both!
That can happen sometimes.
Shiho, sometimes- yeah yeah yeah.
There are cases where both can be used.
So for me,
how to put it,
I'm always really excited to see how the final mix turns out.
Now, Eve-san wasn't actually present during the recording session this time,
but after I’d finished recording all the parts for "Sympathy,"
there was this one part....
I think it was a part where I’d recorded an octave-down track...
a harmony, if I remember correctly.
Well, Eve-san requested that I also record a high-octave harmony for that same section.
So I went back in for some extra takes.
Yeah, we recorded a lot of extra takes for this one.
So try listening to it really closely next time.
"Yeah, the harmonies are so good". Thank you.
Yeah, we did a lot of extra takes.
Right? I'm really glad we did.
Man, talking about it like this really makes it sink in for me how well "Sympathy" actually came together.
I'm really glad for the chance to share all these behind-the-scenes stories with you guys too. Thank you.
The MV is on the official YouTube channel, so please listen to it again if you have the chance.
Please also try out the song in game as well.
Yep. Please listen to it a lot~
I'm sure the other VAs have had similar experiences,
but having to do a key check for the first time for Shiho's event song was a real surprise.
Yeah, "Aoiro Enogu" is super high-pitched!
I just saw a comment about that and had to mention it.
Yeah, that song is super high.
I'll keep working to show many different sides of Shiho-chan, so please look forward to what's coming up!
So with that, I felt like this really flew by www
but that's all for this Aftertalk "Find the dream view" Edition!
How was it, everyone?
Time really flew by!
We did a bit of a mini-renewal today. From reading some of your fan letters,
hearing some commentary from the staff,
and talking about some behind-the-scenes, we covered a lot of ground.
It went by so quick.
We'll be sticking with the format from here on,
so please check out the submissions channel Discord,
and feel free to send your questions— not questions, your suggestions and such.
That really did go by so quick, didn't it?
Man, I'm so curious about how Leo/need is going to move forward from here.
This event really reaffirmed, or actually, helped me rediscover, exactly what Shiho wants to do.
But somehow, Saki-chan looked just a little "unsettled" at the end of the story, didn't she?
Well, "unsettled" is a bit of a strong word, more like she looked like something was still on her mind.
I'm very curious as to what's in store next, so please keep watching over them, everyone.
So with that, for everyone not finished with this event's story,
you'll be able to watch all chapters in the archive once the next event starts, so please do read it!
As we mentioned earlier, we're always looking for letters for the Aftertalks.
You can submit them in the submissions channel on the official Project Sekai Discord.
If you have any thoughts for the next Aftertalk, we'd love to hear them!
Please keep your messages related to the events.
Well, that's all for today! See you again next time!
Bye bye!