Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk: Grow Glorious Grow edition!
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Rina Honnizumi, the voice of Momojan's Shizuku Hinomori.
Yes.
This ProSeka AfterTalk is a place where we look back on the event story and enjoy the AfterLive together with everyone watching the stream.
This time, we're covering the Grow Glorious Grow event.
The event just ended a moment ago, but did you all check it out?
How was it?
I'll be keeping an eye on the comments, so please send them in.
Actually, I jotted down some notes earlier about things I wanted to talk about,
so I'm looking forward to discussing those with all of you.
That's the plan, anyway.
I was just so surprised.
Both as Momojan and as Shizuku, she's overcome so many walls, and she'd already grown wings and taken flight, but...
She's still surpassing herself.
Her growth just doesn't stop.
She's truly cool.
So, please post your thoughts on the event and this broadcast using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
I have the YouTube chat right here in front of me,
so I'll be picking up any comments that catch my eye.
Oh, Kon-more!
Thank you.
The staff has provided me with a device again this time,
so I'd like to use it to look at the story and the illustrations of the members appearing in this event.
Also, I'll be creating a private room for the AfterLive so we can watch it together.
I'll share the Room ID around 21:55, and I'll let you know again when the time comes.
Get your devices ready, let's watch it together.
Please join in.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now then, let's dive right into the story for this event, Grow Glorious Grow.
I want to look back on it, but first,
I'd like to watch a bit with everyone.
Just one episode.
And,
well, opinions might be split.
I have a feeling.
But I'm personally thinking I'd like to see Episode 7. What do you think?
How about you all?
Please let me know in the comments.
Ah, look, people are already saying 7.
You're all so kind.
Thank you.
Oh, 7 would be good? 7 it is then. Since you're all suggesting it,
thank you very much.
Then let's watch Episode 7 together.
Here you go.
Oh, I'm the one who has to start it.
I'm sorry.
It's not "here you go."
My bad, I'll start it now.
Yeah.
I won't lose!
Hagiyama-chan is such a good girl, seriously.
.
And... that's as far as we go.
That was the moment they truly recognized each other as rivals.
With that said, let's watch Episode 7 together.
That went by so fast!
And that's it for the clip.
Actually, I really love the part after this, where everyone...
When they're all at More More House watching the commercial that actually aired, and we see Saito-san...
I love that part, and I also love seeing Minori-chan getting all pure and excited, screaming with joy.
That's all for now.
.
Anyway, thank you so much.
Um, I have so much I want to say, but we need to start the live show together at 10:55.
I really want to see the live show, so everyone, please keep an eye on the clock too.
.
I might just keep talking without noticing the time... but I really want to chat.
I think I'll talk for as long as time allows.
Where should I start?
Right.
There are a few scenes I like... Let's review some parts that weren't in the episodes we just watched.
Hagiyama-san from Rewrite, who was there, previously performed with them at the Idol Lover festival in a past event.
She's a member of a wonderful unit that met Momojan there, and it feels like they'll develop a nice rivalry going forward.
And here she is again,
appearing as Shizuku's rival while they co-star as models.
They're both stepping up their game, and I'm really looking forward to seeing what's next for those two.
Also, regarding Shizuku's past,
there were several flashback scenes. I've forgotten exactly which episodes they were in, so...
I'd love for everyone to go back and watch them, but a junior member who greeted Shizuku during her Cheerful＊Days era makes an appearance.
Back then, Shizuku was overwhelmed with work and was being produced as a "mysterious" idol.
It was a really painful time when she was pushing herself so hard. And in the middle of that,
a new junior member joined... She had worked so hard to get in because she admired her seniors.
There's a scene where she tells Shizuku directly, "That's why I'm going to do my best too."
At that moment, Shizuku... for me, I...
It was a time when Shizuku felt she wasn't suited to be the center of Cheerful Days and was feeling really down,
but by meeting those juniors, she realized she was carrying their futures on her shoulders too.
She felt that if she lacked confidence, she had to polish herself until she found it.
This...
this was another important encounter for her, meeting those juniors.
That was a scene that really moved me and that I personally loved.
Also, the Momojan members... After Shizuku passed the audition this time,
while she was practicing silently by herself,
they brought her some snacks and things. In the card stories,
that sense of distance they have at that moment
is depicted really well.
Airi-chan especially knows Shizuku from her Cheerful Days era so well,
so she can feel Shizuku's level of commitment without needing any words. That's why Airi-chan intentionally didn't say anything,
and just watched over her. That dynamic within Momojan...
it really makes me feel all over again what wonderful girls they are.
Shizuku was like a string pulled taut the whole time,
with this intense tension and a sense of fragility, but Airi-chan was happy to see Shizuku looking like she did back when she was the center of Cheerful Days.
It's just so emotional, really.
But Airi-chan also knows how much Shizuku suffered back then.
Of course, she doesn't say that to Shizuku directly,
but she takes all of that into account while watching her grow. That's their relationship.
I really felt like saying "Thank you for writing this"
during the recording session.
Looking at the comments... Yes, everyone, it's all about trust.
Exactly.
Now, about Shizuku's side story, part two.
It's a nice way of giving back.
Everyone was thinking about what they could do for Shizuku and taking action.
Since she was being stoic and restricting her diet, they brought her snacks
that were high in nutrition and low in fat. That's just pure love, honestly.
It's all about supporting each other.
Exactly... Come on, talk a bit more.
Right.
Should we go with the drama?
So, about that Grand Fleur commercial...
What did you all think of the footage
that actually aired in the story?
When I record for the game, I usually record my lines alone.
It seems Hagiyama-san had already finished her voice recording, and we had some lines to say in unison.
There was a line where Hagiyama-san and Shizuku, along with the others, had to say "Grand Fleur" together.
Normally, for lines in unison, they play the previously recorded voice into my headphones,
and I listen to that while recording my part to match the timing.
That's the usual pattern for delivering perfectly synchronized voices to everyone, but get this...
We recorded that without matching it to anything.
And yet, it was so perfectly in sync!
I was so surprised. I saw the finished version at the same time as all of you, and it was amazing.
I got an "OK" right away. I thought I might have to redo it, but I guess
Hagiyama-chan and Shizuku were just naturally on the same wavelength.
I can't believe that actually happened!
The lines were actually quite long, too, like "The new Floraison Éclat..."
I even looked up what kind of color "Floraison Éclat" was.
It seemed like a really beautiful floral color.
I was just so shocked.
I'm glad everyone is saying it's amazing, too.
I thought that was a pretty rare occurrence.
It makes me happy that these two, who met as good rivals, could be so in sync.
I hope they continue to push each other to new heights alongside the other girls from RE:LITE.
I really do.
Let's talk a bit more.
Right.
Going back to the flashback scenes for a moment... when Shizuku was searching for what she was lacking,
MIKU-chan was in Shizuku's room, and Shizuku decided to watch some old footage...
It was around the scene where MIKU-chan asks Shizuku-chan how she's doing.
In the scene where they watch footage of Shizuku from her Cheerful Days era, there are lines from the past Shizuku.
"I need to do it more like this..."
We actually recorded several different patterns of her muttering to herself like that.
Really.
We delivered one of those versions to all of you, but...
For the patterns, there was a version of Shizuku that felt more precarious, like you'd be worried just watching her.
She was really pushing herself to the limit, thinking she had to master the dance to carry the weight of being the center of Cheerful Days.
I recorded several takes of that desperate Shizuku. I felt like...
We've seen Shizuku backed into a corner like this a few times before,
but it's been a while since she went that far. It was actually quite tough,
and there were several scenes that were pretty painful to perform.
Flashbacks to the Cheerful Days era always involve lines where she's pushing herself, which can be hard for me too.
But that Shizuku is what leads to the Shizuku we have now.
I thought having that contrast would create more of a story.
That's what I felt.
...
And yet, a cornered Shizuku has a certain charm of her own,
in a way.
Especially since she was being promoted as the "mysterious Shizuku" back then,
she never showed that side of her hard work.
That's why seeing her silently working so hard by herself behind the scenes feels so lonely.
Like she was doing her absolute best all on her own.
That's why it connects to the episode with her juniors I mentioned earlier,
where Shizuku feels like she has to work hard
for their sake as well.
...
Thinking about it that way, I'm so glad she met Momojan.
Seriously, Minori...
Haruka...
That's Airi for you.
That's how it feels.
...
Anyway, it's about time for me to start getting ready for the AfterLive.
I'll reveal the Room ID around 10:55, so everyone, please get your devices ready.
We'll do a "ready, set, go" so take your time.
I'll try my best not to make any mistakes while setting this up.
Okay, creating the room...
...
Writing down the numbers now.
I'm not showing it yet, everyone!
I'll show it on the count of three.
Please have your devices ready.
It'll be around 10:55.
Wait, it won't fit on this, sorry.
My bad.
This ID has six digits.
...
I managed to write it down correctly.
Is everyone ready?
Ready?
Type it in and enter on my signal.
Space is limited, so it's first-come, first-served.
Good luck!
Let's all get hyped together.
It's the first time everyone's hearing the song, after all.
I'm so excited.
It's my first time seeing it too, wow.
The AfterLive starts at 22:00.
I'm planning to introduce the cards and everything today, but...
Just a moment ago,
I was so surprised.
The illustration used for Shizuku's banner this time... I was like, "Is this really the untrained version?"
The quality is high enough to be a trained version.
It really shocked me.
I actually got a sneak peek during the voice recording session,
of how Shizuku would look this time.
And man,
it was just incredible.
I couldn't help but applaud.
Seriously.
I really wish they would sell this actual makeup line.
This is just amazing.
Truly.
We've seen Shizuku looking cool in a few events before, but...
the sparkle in her eyes is different here. Her strength and all her hard work really show in her expression.
She looks so cool.
The trained illustration is also amazing. It's like she's under a blue sky,
and you can see her looking like she's about to take flight. Let's all look at the cards together later.
They're wonderful.
The outfits are cute too.
It's like a hotel...
A hotel?
The script says it's a studio.
It's such a...
I thought the set really fit the concept this time. It feels very mature.
But since the goal was to attract a younger audience than Grand Fleur's usual target demographic,
Hagiyama-chan and Shizuku were selected for the job.
They fit the concept so perfectly that it just made me happy.
ProSeka really does a great job showing so many different sides of the characters.
They really do.
Speaking as a fan myself,
seeing such a wide range for the characters...
I bet there were people who literally fell out of their chairs because it was so beautiful.
Right?
...
I mean, you would fall over seeing this.
It's seriously mind-blowing.
I was surprised too.
I saw it trending on X earlier.
I figured it had to be something about ProSeka.
The banner had just been revealed, and I happened to see it right then.
When the official account posted the image for Shizuku's event banner on X,
everyone's reactions were just incredible.
It made me so happy.
Okay everyone, it's almost time to start.
About ten seconds left.
...
I'm so nervous!
I'm glad I get to enjoy this with all of you.
...
So, what did you all think?
Thank you, r-906, for writing "Hashiru" for Momojan.
It's such a great song.
Shizuku says,
"Look at me."
I've never seen her be this strong before.
It really makes me feel so emotional, seriously.
In the chorus lyrics,
it says, "Can you tell who the lead is?"
And then, "Look at me."
I feel like this really shows... earlier, Shizuku said she'd started leaning on everyone since joining Momojan.
That's how she described it, but...
well, that's definitely not a bad thing.
It was progress in its own way, but she called it "leaning on them."
And now, she's climbing
to even greater
heights.
Thank you so much for writing a song and lyrics that perfectly symbolize that growth.
Seriously, thank you, r-906.
So...
it's been added to the game now, and I really want you all to pay attention to the lyrics.
How should I put it... wait?
After the first chorus, there's a solo part where,
one by one, everyone comes to the center and...
well...
wasn't that just incredible?
The part where Shizuku comes to the center and turns around...
and...
I really felt like the formation and the choreography were just god-tier.
The lighting, the stage, and the outfits too.
The outfits were insane.
Seriously.
I touched on it a bit with the cards, but you can see a glimpse of it there too.
Let's all pour our love into it together later, seriously.
Seriously, thank you so much for all the comments.
Everyone's crying a little.
I totally get that feeling.
...
The outfits were so cute too.
They really grab your attention, seriously.
I'm so excited to see what's next
for Momojan, honestly.
Thank you so much.
By the way, the 3DMV was uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel
at 10:10 PM.
It's up now.
It's already live.
Please go check it out.
Since we're here, I'd love for you to watch this broadcast with me,
and then...
Please watch it a bunch of times later. But if you want to see it right now,
go ahead and watch it now.
Seriously, I'm so excited for the 3DMV.
...
Please look forward to it.
Thank you so much for the talk.
...
Being able to
deliver a new song to everyone like this...
Anyway,
there are five members in total who were newly added this time.
Everyone, did you check out the side stories?
Wait, just a second...
Let's take a look at the members.
...
Here we go...
Shizuku.
The trained version...
Trained.
Isn't the outfit from earlier just incredible?
Seriously, she's truly taking flight.
I really love the expression on Shizuku's face as she looks back.
I think you guys might relate to this...
It shows such strength.
It really does.
And this... should I call it a flag?
It's like a flag... do you see how it's shaped like a wing?
On the left side...
In the story, there was a metaphor about Shizuku being like a swan...
...
How they look elegant above the water...
...that's how they appear,
but beneath the surface, they're paddling their feet like crazy.
I really love that comparison, saying that's exactly what Shizuku is like.
This illustration really captures that feeling perfectly.
It's a beautiful illustration.
So gorgeous.
Next, here is the untrained version.
The banner art.
Oh my gosh.
This appeared in the story earlier too... it really surprised me.
Look at Shizuku here...
Isn't she sparkling?
The level of expression just keeps getting better and better.
Look at the way Shizuku is holding that poster in her right hand...
...
Seriously, I want this for myself.
It is just too beautiful.
I could stare at it forever.
Seriously.
Maybe I should use this as a reference.
...
It is seriously good.
When it is zoomed in like this... by the way...
Since she looks so mature, I tried to act a bit more mature myself
while performing her voice.
I can't help but be conscious of it when the art is this wonderful.
Thank you so much.
That was Shizuku.
Next up is...
Minori-chan!
...
She is bursting with energy!
I love Minori-chan's jumps. You know,
she is always the one jumping the highest during our lives.
She is seriously the personification of Momojan.
That leap...
Minori-chan's full effort really reaches you.
It really does.
...
This angle is also just irresistible.
You can even see her shoes...
There are wings on the heels of the shoes.
Isn't that amazing?
The attention to detail is just...
I can really feel the dedication.
...
The designs are slightly different for each member,
so I can't help but stare at them.
...
Wait, seriously...
That was Episode 7 just now. Look at what happens after.
...
This is when everyone watched the Grand Fleur commercial together,
and then this expression.
Airi's look here is just... I love this vibe.
Isn't she cute?
Minori, seriously, thank you.
...
And then, there's that.
It's Momo House.
This is the first time I've seen Momo House from this angle.
This illustration...
So that's what it looked like!
It's so heartwarming. It's Momo House.
Moving on... MIKU.
You can feel such a strong sense of will
from this MIKU.
It's so good.
MIKU...
She shows so many different expressions depending on her resolve,
and it's like she's carrying Shizuku's determination right along with her.
MIKU also, well, she stayed close to Shizuku in her own way,
and treated her with such a wonderful sense of distance. MIKU supported her,
and she was able to overcome it. Truly.
She's a goddess, seriously.
For real.
MIKU is so cool too.
She looks so strong.
.
Seriously, cool MIKU is just... I...
Thank you for the comments.
Miyashitsu.
The untrained art...
This is...
It's that one. Not from just now.
This is it.
It's from when I was talking about the Shizuku of the past,
the two of them are watching Shizuku practicing her dancing.
It's MIKU staying close to her while they check the screen together.
Thank you.
Man, this distance between them is so good.
Watching over her from so close by.
This scene is exactly that one.
From the past...
.
Well,
about the Shizuku of the past,
it's the part where she tells her that she's the Shizuku of today.
That's the spot.
So, Shizuku watches footage of her past self and says it doesn't even feel like her.
And this is the scene where MIKU tells her,
"This is you too, Shizuku-chan."
Wow.
It's so heartwarming.
You can really feel that she's not alone.
MIKU is always there to support us, truly.
Seriously.
It makes me so happy.
Moving on...
Here's Haruka-chan's trained art.
She's sitting down... this is nice.
That look of her watching over Shizuku.
...
Everyone understands Shizuku so well.
Well, they all understand each other, but...
Units are just so great.
Everyone is there for her,
and because Shizuku is there, everyone else is there too.
Seriously, I just...
...
Really, always...
I can't stop saying thank you.
This white clover is nice too, the three-leaf one.
Momojan.
The coloring is slightly different for each of them.
This time, it's all unified with a blue sky, as if to cheer on Shizuku as she takes flight.
It really suits Haruka.
It's lovely.
Personally, I like that Shizuku is wearing short pants... the shorts and...
The legs are asymmetrical too...
And this is what you'd call the "absolute territory."
Thank you so much.
It's lovely.
Shorts really suit Haruka-chan.
She looks as brilliant as ever.
Now, for this illustration...
This is the untrained version.
Haruka is...
She's making a high-nutrition, low-calorie meal
specifically for Shizuku.
Seriously, she's amazing.
Haruka-chan is so stoic and works so hard on her own diet,
so of course she's very knowledgeable,
she knows so much about nutritional value.
Even I learn things just by looking at the script.
Like, "This is a bit high in fat," or,
"This is a sweet you can eat even on a low-carb diet."
I'm like, "Oh, I see!" and use it as a reference myself sometimes.
Physical health... food is the foundation of your physical health.
It starts with the body.
Building the body.
And that's how Haruka-chan
is supporting Shizuku.
Thank you so much.
It's so colorful,
it looks great.
Delicious.
...Airi.
For Airi-chan, we only have the untrained version.
Isn't she cute?
She's showing her midriff, which is so typical of Airi-chan.
.
Airi-chan is just so cute.
That wink...
She's just bursting with energy,
it really shows.
.
When you think of Airi-chan,
you can't go wrong with this.
Seriously.
Honestly...
...this.
I was really happy we could look at these together just now.
.
And with that,
we've managed to see all of them for this time.
Thank you so much.
Some of you mentioned it in the comments too, but for this event...
...?
The team name.
I made it "Fabulous."
Yes, Fabulous. Honestly, that one word says it all.
.
Thank you.
So,
let me talk a little bit more.
And...
I touched on that, but wait, how far did I get?
Right, I talked about my favorite scenes.
And I mentioned the achievement of their voices syncing up for the Grand Fleur commercial.
Yeah, that's right.
So...
In this story, when Shizuku was working on Grand Fleur,
and she wanted to improve...
She saw Hagiyama-chan's performance,
and seeing her strength made her realize, "This is what I'm missing!"
There was that scene where she finally found it.
I actually really empathized with Shizuku in that moment.
When I'm doing my own work and activities,
there are so many times when I'm faced with what I'm lacking.
I'm aware that I'm missing something, and I run right into that wall,
but as for what specifically I should do to grasp that missing piece,
I just don't know.
I seriously have no idea.
Honestly, I could probably call this the main challenge of my life.
I'm very blessed with my environment, and the people around me
are all such charming, cool, and wonderful people.
Because of that, I see them having things that I don't have.
That's how it is.
In other words...
They look so radiant, and they possess things I lack.
When I'm struggling in those moments,
I get this image of myself struggling in the deep sea where I can't see any light or the path ahead.
It's really painful.
It's like no matter what I do, it backfires,
or I just can't get any results.
Maybe some of you...
I think there might be some people who feel this way.
.
There are times when things are just incredibly painful.
But,
when you finally realize it,
you realize, "This... this is what I was looking for."
There's a moment where it all clicks.
It's strange,
but you can only understand it the moment you find it.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure if I'm explaining this well.
I'm sorry for not having the right words, but in my experience,
it's something you only understand once you find that light,
and you realize, "This was it."
You can never see it while you're still struggling,
only the version of you that found it can understand.
So, if right now...
...
if there's anyone out there who is struggling right now,
it might be painful at this moment,
but there will be a moment when that light is in your hands.
I know it.
Truly.
This is just my take.
I hope for a world where that light is within your reach someday.
.
That's what I wanted to convey through this story and through Shizuku.
That was the personal theme I took away from it.
So, let's both keep doing our best.
Through everything.
Whether it is club activities, work, or job hunting,
...
I know things can be tough. In times like those, I hope you can use ProSeka's stories
to take a little breather, or listen to lots of our songs.
It would make me so happy if they could become a source of strength or healing for everyone.
That is...
what I was thinking.
When you lack confidence... well, it was the same for Shizuku. Shizuku,
right?
She was happy to pass the Grand Fleur audition, but she did not know
what she needed to do to have the strength to be worthy of co-starring with Hagiyama.
Being in that state of not knowing,
and then having the actual performance approach... that is terrifying, right?
Knowing that you are lacking something,
and having to smash through the wall right in front of you...
it is just so scary.
That lack of confidence,
and that fear... it was one of the scenes I really empathized with.
It really was.
And then, this part.
Um,
after seeing Hagiyama-chan's performance,
...
not wanting to lose to anyone, or give in...
Shizuku,
she felt that.
When Hagiyama-chan asked Shizuku what she was thinking during the audition,
I think it was during the fitting... she said she was thinking about giving a performance that would surpass her opponent. That really struck a chord with me. I'm lucky enough to get to take many auditions myself, but I get so nervous that I end up putting a lot of pressure on myself.
And of course, because they are such wonderful works, I start worrying if I'll be the one to...
drag the project down, or if I can do it well, or if I'll be a burden to my co-stars.
There are so many different feelings involved.
Sometimes you feel like you're going to be crushed by your own thoughts, but in those moments,
if you have that feeling of not wanting to lose or back down, you can hold onto yourself more strongly.
Hagiyama-chan is seriously so strong.
Really.
I ended up learning a lot from her too.
Just like Shizuku did.
Truly.
When someone has a heart that strong, I feel like I'm about to grow wings myself.
Like I'm ready to take flight.
I'll do my best right alongside Shizuku.
I look forward to working with you all.
That's what I wanted to say.
I learn so much from this.
The stories in ProSeka are just, seriously...
They're so educational for me.
They've become a source of emotional support.
I'd be so happy if they resonate with all of you in the same way.
.
Everyone is telling me "Let's do our best!"
Let's do it together, everyone.
Supporting each other.
.
Thank you for the support.
I'll work hard.
My heart is right there with Shizuku.
.
With that, I have no regrets.
I made sure to memo everything I wanted to talk about, and I've said it all.
.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for staying with me for so long.
The 3DMV for "Hashiru, Todoku" that we just watched together has been released, so...
Please check it out.
Oh, sorry, I made a mistake.
Was it 2D?
The 2DMV was just uploaded to the official YouTube channel, so please watch it.
It was the 2DMV.
Sorry about that.
I appreciate your understanding.
Both the 2DMV and the 3DMV... let me summarize.
Both the 3DMV and 2DMV for "Hashiru, Todoku" have just been released on the official YouTube channel.
Sorry, I always get a bit flustered, I apologize.
I'm a little bit...
Once this is over, please go and watch them a lot, everyone.
Thank you very much.
.
Everyone is saying they'll watch it.
Thank you so much.
And with that, this short ProSeka AfterTalk for the "Glow Glorious Glow" event has come to an end.
To everyone watching the stream, how did you like it?
I'm so happy because everyone's comments were so supportive.
Momojan is truly the best.
They just keep on growing and growing.
Growth with no ceiling is truly dazzling, isn't it?
Thank you so much, everyone, really.
I had a lot of fun.
I really did.
And that's it for today's look at Grow Glorious Grow... that's a mouthful.
If you haven't finished reading Grow Glorious Grow yet, you'll be able to read the full event story from the archives once the next event starts.
So please, read it as many times as you like.
The scenes I mentioned earlier that we didn't get to watch together today are all in there too,
so definitely check them out.
I'd be so happy if you're reading and think, "Oh, Hon-chan mentioned this part!"
Thank you so much.
And with that, thank you all for sticking with me for so long today.
I'll see you again soon.
Bye-bye!