Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk: "Grow Glorious Grow" edition!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Rina Honnizumi, the voice of Momojan's Shizuku Hinomori.
This ProSeka AfterTalk is a program where we look back on the event story and enjoy the AfterLive together!
This time, we're covering the "grow glorious grow" event.
The event just ended a moment ago, but did you all check it out?
What did you think?
I'll be keeping an eye on the comments, so please join in!
I actually jotted down some notes earlier
about things I really wanted to talk about,
so I'm hoping to go over those with you all.
I was just so surprised.
Both for MMJ and for Shizuku, they've overcome so many hurdles,
and even though she'd already grown wings and taken flight,
she's still surpassing herself!
Her growth just never stops.
It's honestly so cool.
Please post your thoughts on the event or the stream using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
The staff have set up the YouTube chat so I can see it right here,
so I'll be picking out comments that catch my eye.
Let's see...
Thank you so much!
The staff have provided me with a device again today,
so I'd like to look back at the story and the member illustrations with you.
Also, I'll be creating a private room to watch the AfterLive together.
I'll share the Room ID at 21:55, so I'll let you know then.
Please get your devices ready so we can watch it together.
I hope you'll all join in!
Let's get started!
Now then, I'd like to look back on the story of
"Grow Glorious Grow," but first, I want to watch
one episode together with everyone.
Just one episode.
I think
opinions might be split,
just a hunch.
Actually, I was thinking I'd like to see Episode 7.
What do you all think?
Please let me know in the comments.
Oh, you're already saying "7"! Everyone is so kind.
Thank you.
So Episode 7 is good? 7 it is. I'll go with your choice.
Thank you very much.
Alright, let's watch Episode 7 together.
Wait, I'm the one who has to play it!
Sorry.
I shouldn't have said "here you go."
My apologies.
I'll start it now.
"I won't lose!"
Hagiyama-chan is seriously such a good girl.
And there we go.
That's as far as we go.
That was the moment they recognized each other as rivals.
And that was Episode 7. We watched it together.
It went by so fast!
And that's as far as we'll watch.
Actually, I really love the part that comes after this,
where everyone is at Momo House watching the commercial that finally aired,
and we see Saito-san's reaction.
I also love seeing Minori-chan getting all pure and excited, squealing over it.
But that's all for the clips.
Thank you very much for watching with me.
I have so much I want to say, but we need to watch the live show at 10:55 PM,
so everyone, please keep an eye on the clock.
I might just keep talking without noticing the time, but I really want to chat,
so I'll talk as much as time allows.
Where should I start?
Right.
I have a few favorite scenes that weren't in the episodes we just watched, so let's review.
Hagiyama-san from Rewrite, who was in the commercial, previously appeared in the Idol Lovers festival.
She's a member of a wonderful unit that seems like they'll have a good rivalry with Momojan,
and it was great to see them meet like that. But here,
she appears again as Shizuku's rival while they're co-starring as models.
They're both stepping up their game, and I'm really looking forward to seeing them both in the future.
Also, regarding Shizuku's past...
There were several flashback scenes. I can't remember exactly which episode numbers they were,
but I'd love for everyone to go back and watch them. A junior member from her Cheerful＊Days era appears to greet her.
Back then, Shizuku was being produced as a mysterious idol and was completely overwhelmed with work.
It was a really painful time for her, but she was trying her absolute best. And then,
this new junior member joined. She had worked so hard to join because she looked up to her seniors.
There's a scene where she tells Shizuku directly that she's going to do her best too.
At that time, Shizuku was already...
She was feeling really down, thinking she wasn't suited to be the center of Cheerful＊Days.
But by meeting that junior, she realized she was carrying the future of those girls on her shoulders too.
She decided that if she lacked confidence, she had to polish herself until she finally found it.
This...
this was also a fated encounter, with her junior.
It's a scene that really moved me,
and one of my favorites.
Also, the Momojan members... after Shizuku
passed the audition,
she was practicing all by herself,
and they brought her some refreshments.
That's also depicted in the card stories,
that specific
sense of distance between them.
Airi especially knows Shizuku well from her Cheerful Days era,
so she can tell how serious Shizuku is without a single word. Airi doesn't even say anything,
she just watches over her. It really makes me realize
what wonderful girls the Momojan members are.
Shizuku was like a tightly wound string,
there was so much tension.
It felt a bit precarious, but Airi was happy to see the Shizuku who was the center of Cheerful Days again.
It's so emotional, really.
But Airi also knows that Shizuku suffered back then.
She doesn't say it to her face, of course,
but she's watching over her growth, including all of that. That's their relationship.
I was honestly thinking, "Thank you so much for writing this,"
while we were recording.
Looking at the comments... everyone's saying "trust."
That's it exactly.
In the second part of Shizuku's side story...
everyone is thinking about what they can do for Shizuku and taking action.
Since she was being so stoic with her diet, they brought her high-nutrition, low-fat
meals as refreshments. That's true love, honestly.
It's all about supporting each other.
I mean... I should probably talk about it a bit more.
Right.
What should I talk about...
So, that Grand Fleur commercial...
That live shot of Shizuku doing the recording...
What did you think of it, everyone?
When I record for the game, I usually record my lines alone.
It seems Hagiyama-san had already finished her voice recording, but we had some lines to say in unison.
There was a line where Hagiyama-san and Shizuku say "Grand Fleur" together.
Normally, for lines in unison, they play the previously recorded voice into my headphones,
and I listen to that while recording my part to match the timing.
That's the usual way we get those nice synchronized lines,
But get this!
I recorded that without listening at all!
And yet, it was so perfectly in sync!
I was so surprised. I only saw the finished version at the same time as all of you, so I was amazed.
I got an "OK" right away. I thought I might have to redo it,
but I guess Hagiyama-chan and Shizuku were just naturally on the same wavelength.
I can't believe that actually happened!
The lines were actually quite long, too, like "The new Floraison Éclat..."
I actually looked up what kind of color "Floraison Éclat" was.
It seemed like a really beautiful floral color.
I was so surprised.
I'm glad everyone is saying they were wowed, too.
I feel like that's really rare.
It makes me happy that these two, who met as good rivals, could be so in sync.
I hope they continue to push each other to new heights with the girls from ReLight.
Let's keep talking a bit more.
I'm going back to talking about the flashback scenes again,
but it was when Shizuku was searching for what it was she was lacking.
It was around the scene where Miku-chan calls out to her when Shizuku decides to watch some old footage in her room.
In that scene where she watches footage from her Cheerful Days era, there are lines from the past Shizuku.
She's was muttering to herself,
"I need to do it more like this..."
We actually recorded several different patterns for that part.
And we picked out the very best one for all of you.
As for the patterns... there was one where she sounded more precarious,
like a Shizuku who makes you worried just by looking at her.
She was really cornering herself, thinking she had to master the dance to carry the weight of being the center of Cheerful Days.
She felt like there was no turning back.
We recorded a few patterns of that desperate Shizuku, and I felt like...
Well, we've seen Shizuku cornered like this a few times before,
but it's been a while since she went that far. It was actually quite tough,
and there were several scenes that were pretty painful to record.
Flashbacks to her Cheerful Days era always involve lines where she's pushing herself too hard, which is painful for me too,
but that Shizuku is what leads to the Shizuku we have now.
I thought having that gap would create more of a sense of drama.
That's what I was thinking.
...
A cornered Shizuku has a certain charm to her,
in its own way.
Especially since she was being promoted as the "mysterious Shizuku" back then,
and she never showed that side of her effort to anyone.
Seeing how she kept working so hard in silence behind the scenes,
it really makes you feel how lonely she was, doing her absolute best all on her own.
And that connects back to the story about her juniors I mentioned earlier,
where Shizuku feels like she has to work hard
for their sake as well.
Thinking about it that way, I'm so glad she met Momojan.
Seriously, Minori,
Haruka,
and Airi...
That's really how it feels.
Anyway, it's about time for me to get ready for the AfterLive.
I'll reveal the room ID around 10:55, so everyone, please get your devices ready.
We'll all join at the same time.
I'll be careful not to make any mistakes with the controls here.
Creating the room...
Now I'll write down the numbers.
I'm not showing them yet, everyone.
I'll show them to you all at once.
Please have your devices ready.
It'll be around 10:55.
Oh, it won't fit here, sorry.
Sorry.
There are six digits in total.
I managed to write it down without any mistakes!
Is everyone...
ready?
Type it in and enter on the count of three!
Space is limited, so it'll be first-come, first-served.
I'm counting on you!
I really want us all to get hyped together!
It's the first time everyone's hearing this song, after all.
I'm so excited!
It's my first time seeing it too, how amazing!
The AfterLive starts at 10:00 PM!
I'm planning to introduce the cards today, but...
Just a moment ago,
I was so surprised.
I saw the illustration used for Shizuku's banner this time and thought, "Wait, is this really the untrained version?"
The quality is high enough to be a trained version.
It really shocked me.
Actually, I got a look at it during the voice recording session.
This is how Shizuku looks this time.
And man,
it was just incredible.
I even started clapping.
Seriously.
I really wish they'd actually sell these cosmetics.
This is just amazing.
Truly.
We've seen cool versions of Shizuku in a few events before, but...
there's a different sparkle in her eyes this time, a real sense of her strength.
You can really see all of Shizuku's hard work reflected in her expression.
She looked so cool.
And the trained illustration is amazing too.
You can see her looking like she's about to take flight into the blue sky.
Let's take a look at the cards together later.
They're incredible.
The outfits are cute too.
It's like a hotel...
A hotel?
The script says it's a studio.
It's such a...
I thought the set really fit the concept this time. It feels very mature.
But since they wanted to attract a younger audience than Grand Fleur's usual target demographic...
This time, Hagiyama-chan and Shizuku were featured,
and they fit the concept so perfectly that it just made me so happy.
ProSeka really shows us so many different sides of the characters,
they really do.
Seriously, speaking as a fan myself,
showing such a wide range for the characters...
I bet there were people who literally fell out of their chairs...
?
.
You'd definitely fall off. This one is just...
It's honestly mind-blowing.
I was surprised too.
It was even trending on X, too.
I thought, "This must be for ProSeka," when the banner was revealed.
I happened to be looking at X right at that moment,
and when the official account posted the image of Shizuku's banner for this event,
everyone reacted so strongly.
It made me happy too.
It's almost time to start, everyone.
About 10 seconds left.
...
I'm so excited.
I'm going to enjoy this with all of you.
...
.
So, what did everyone think?
Yuuyu-san wrote this new song for Momojan,
"Hashiru".
.
Shizuku says,
"Look at me."
She's never been this strong before.
It's so deeply moving.
I seriously started crying.
In the lyrics for the chorus,
it says, "Can you tell who the lead is?"
She's asking everyone to look at her.
I feel like... earlier, Shizuku mentioned that since joining MORE MORE JUMP!, she's been relying on everyone,
or rather, she described it as "spoiling herself."
But that's definitely not a bad thing; it's a form of progress for her.
However, she chose to call it "spoiling herself" and decided to aim for even greater heights.
.
Yuuyu-san wrote a song and lyrics that perfectly symbolize that growth.
Yuuyu-san, thank you so much, seriously.
Once it's added to the game, I really want you to pay attention to the lyrics. How should I put it...
Oh?
After the first chorus, there's a solo section where everyone comes to the center one by one, and...
Wasn't that just incredible?
The part where Shizuku comes to the center and turns around...
I really felt like the choreography and formations were just god-tier.
The lighting, the stage... and the outfits too.
The outfits were amazing.
Seriously.
I mentioned the cards briefly, but you can see it in the cards too, so later, let's all...
show them some love, seriously.
Seriously, thank you for all the comments.
Everyone's crying a little bit.
I totally get it...
...
The outfits were so cute too.
They really catch your eye, seriously.
It's a song that really makes me excited for Momojan's future,
it really is.
Thank you so much.
And with that, the 3DMV was just uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel at 10:10 PM.
It's already live!
Please go check it out.
Well, since you're here, I'd love for you to stay and watch the rest of this stream with me,
and then you can go watch the MV as many times as you want afterward.
But if you really want to see it right now, go ahead and watch it,
seriously. I'm so excited for the 3DMV!
...
Please check it out.
Haruka, thank you so much.
...
I'm so glad we can deliver another new song to everyone like this.
So, there are five members in total who were newly added this time.
Did everyone check out the illustrations and side stories?
Let's take a look at the members right now.
Alright.
Let's go.
First up is Shizuku.
This is the trained art...
Here is the trained version.
Isn't the vibe of this outfit just incredible?
She's really taking flight, for real.
I love the expression Shizuku has as she looks back.
I think everyone can relate to this feeling.
You can really feel her strength.
And these... should I call them banners? These flags...
Can you tell they're shaped like wings?
On the left side... in the story, there was that swan metaphor,
about how they look elegant above the water but are paddling like crazy underneath.
That's exactly like Shizuku. I really love that metaphor,
and this illustration really makes me think of that. It's so beautiful.
Next, here is the untrained version.
This is the banner card.
This is insane. It appeared in the story earlier, and I was so shocked.
Look at Shizuku here.
She's sparkling, right?
The level of expression just keeps going up and up.
And the cosmetics Shizuku is holding in her right hand...
I seriously want this new product for myself.
She's just too beautiful.
I could look at this forever.
Seriously.
Maybe I should use this makeup as a reference.
Seriously this time.
Okay, just like this.
Zoom in a bit... By the way, Shizuku looks a bit more mature today,
so I actually had my own look done a bit more maturely too.
I can't help but be conscious of it when Shizuku is drawn so beautifully.
Thank you so much.
It's Shizuku!
Next is Minori-chan.
The trained art...
She's bursting with energy!
I love Minori-chan's jumps. She's always the one bouncing around the most during lives,
that girl. She really is Momojan.
Minori-chan's jumping power and her full effort really reach you.
They really do.
...
This angle is just irresistible.
It is. Everyone, look at the shoes.
There are wings on the heels of the shoes!
Isn't that amazing?
I can really feel the incredible attention to detail in the small things.
...
The designs are slightly different for each member, so I can't help but look closely.
Wait, seriously, we just saw Episode 7, but looking at the story after that,
this... this is that expression she makes when they all watch the aired Grand Fleur commercial together.
And this sort of... look on Airi-chan's face...
Isn't it cute?
Minori-chan, thank you so much, seriously.
...
Also, this background... it's the Momo House.
I've never seen the Momo House from this angle before.
This illustration...
Seeing it like this makes the Momo House feel so cozy.
Next up is... MIKU.
You can really feel a strong sense of determination from this MIKU.
It's so good.
MIKU really shows so many different expressions depending on how strong her will is.
This time, it's almost like she's carrying Shizuku's resolve right along with her.
MIKU stayed close to Shizuku this time, supporting her with such a wonderful sense of distance.
Shizuku was able to overcome it because MIKU supported her. She's truly a goddess.
Seriously.
She really is.
MIKU looks so cool too.
She looks so strong.
?
I really love this cool MIKU too.
.
Thank you for all the comments, everyone.
And here is the untrained art of MIKU and Shizuku.
This is from that scene... wait, not that one.
This is the one.
It's the two of them watching the old footage of Shizuku practicing her dancing, like Shizuku mentioned earlier.
It's MIKU staying close to her while they check the screen together.
I love the distance between them here.
She's watching over her from so close by.
This scene is exactly that... where she tells her that the old Shizuku
is also the same Shizuku she is today.
Shizuku watches her old self and says, "It doesn't feel like me," but MIKU tells her, "This is you too, Shizuku."
It's such a heartwarming scene.
It really shows that she's not alone.
MIKU, thank you for always supporting her, really.
Seriously.
It makes me so happy.
Moving on...
Here is Haruka-chan's trained art.
She's sitting down in this one.
It's so nice.
This one also shows her watching over Shizuku.
...
Everyone understands Shizuku so well.
Well, they all understand each other.
Units are just so great.
Shizuku is here because of everyone, and everyone is here because of Shizuku.
Seriously, it's like...
Really... always.
I can't stop saying thank you.
This white clover is nice too, and the three-leaf motif.
The coloring is a bit different every time, and this time it's all unified with a blue sky, as if to cheer on Shizuku as she takes flight. This blue really suits her.
It's like Haruka's color.
It's lovely.
Personally, I like the shorts. Shizuku has different lengths on her left and right legs.
This... what you'd call the "absolute territory," this part right here.
Thank you so much.
...
Seriously.
Haruka-chan looks great in shorts too.
She's truly amazing.
This illustration is just...
This is... this one is the untrained art.
Haruka is...
making this highly nutritious, low, low-calorie meal for Shizuku.
Seriously, for real.
Haruka-chan is such a stoic girl who works so hard on her diet,
so she's naturally very knowledgeable about food and nutrition.
I actually learn a lot myself
just by reading the script.
Like, 'this is a bit high in fat,' or 'this is a sweet
you can eat even on a low-carb diet.'
I'm like, 'Oh, I see,' and I even use it as a reference sometimes.
Physical health... food is the foundation of your physique,
it starts with the body.
Building your body.
Haruka-chan supports Shizuku in ways like this.
Thank you so much.
These colorful vegetables look great, they look delicious.
And then, Airi.
For Airi-chan, we only have the untrained art.
Isn't she cute?
When you think of Airi-chan, you think of the midriff look.
It's a classic.
Airi-chan is so cute.
That wink!
It really gives you a burst of energy,
it really does.
When it comes to Airi-chan, you can't go wrong.
Truly.
Everyone, really...
I'm so glad we could look at these together just now.
.
And with that, we've seen all the cards for this event.
Thank you very much.
Someone mentioned this in the comments earlier, but for this time...
What was it?
The team name.
I made it "Fabulous."
It really is fabulous. That's the only word for it, seriously.
.
Thank you.
Anyway, let me talk a bit more.
I touched on this earlier, but how far did I get?
Right, I talked about my favorite scenes.
And about the achievement of our voices syncing up in the "Grand Fleur" commercial.
Yes, that's right.
Well...
In this story, when Shizuku was facing the "Grand Fleur" audition, she saw Hagiyama-chan's performance.
She saw that powerful light of hers and realized, "This is what I'm lacking." There was a scene like that, right?
I really empathized with Shizuku on that point.
In my own daily activities,
there are so many times when I'm faced with my own shortcomings.
I'm aware that I'm lacking things and I run into those walls,
but I don't know specifically what I should do to grasp what's missing.
This...
I really don't know.
Honestly, I could even call this one of my life's biggest challenges.
I'm very blessed with my environment, and the people around me are all so charming and...
just wonderful people.
Because of that, they have things that I don't.
In other words...
They shine so brightly and have charms that I don't have.
And when I'm struggling like that, I imagine being in the deep sea,
struggling in the dark where I can't see what's ahead. It's just so painful.
It's like everything you do backfires, or you just don't see any results.
Maybe some of you feel the same way too.
.
There are times when it's just so painful.
But you know,
there's a moment when you suddenly realize, "This is it..."
Like, "This is what I was looking for all along."
It's strange, but you only understand it once you've actually found it.
I'm sorry if I'm not explaining this well, I'm struggling to find the right words,
but in my experience...
there's something you only realize once you find that light, like "Oh, this was it."
You can't see it while you're struggling; only the "you" who found it can know.
So for those of you
who might be struggling right now, it might be hard, but one day that light will be in your hands.
That moment
will definitely come. Truly.
That's just how I feel.
I want this to be a world where that light is already within reach.
.
That's a theme I personally wanted to convey through this story,
and through Shizuku as well.
So let's both keep doing our best.
Whether it's club activities, work, or job hunting,
I know things can be tough. In those times, I hope you'll look at ProSeka stories,
take a little break, and listen to lots of the songs.
I'd be so happy if they could be a source of strength or healing for you.
When you lack confidence... Shizuku was like that too, wasn't she?
Shizuku was happy to pass the "Grand Fleur" audition, but she didn't know what she needed to do to reach a level worthy of performing alongside Hagiyama-san,
so facing the actual performance like that is so scary.
It's terrifying to have to face the wall in front of you when you know you're still lacking something.
That fear from a lack of confidence was a scene I really empathized with.
Also, also, there's this.
You see...
Shizuku felt Hagiyama-chan's unyielding will to never lose or back down during her performance,
and during the costume fitting, Hagiyama-chan asked Shizuku what she was thinking about during the audition.
She said she wanted to give a performance that would surpass her opponent, which really struck a chord. I'm lucky to go to many auditions, but I get so nervous that I put a lot of pressure on myself.
And since it's such a wonderful project, I worry about whether I...
...might hold the production back, if I can do it well, or if I'll be a burden to my co-stars.
All these different thoughts go through your head.
There are times when I feel like I'm going to be crushed by those feelings, but in those moments, if I had that will to never lose
or back down, I felt like I could stand much firmer as myself.
Hagiyama-chan is seriously so strong.
Really.
I ended up learning a lot too, just like Shizuku.
Truly.
I felt like if I had a heart that strong, I might even grow wings myself.
I'd take flight, just like Shizuku.
I'll do my best too.
I'm counting on your support!
That's what I wanted to share.
I learn so much.
Seriously, the ProSeka stories...
...really teach me a lot.
They've become a source of emotional support for me.
I feel the same way.
I'd be so happy if it resonated with all of you as well.
.
Everyone's telling me, "Let's do our best!"
Everyone, together.
Supporting each other.
Thank you for all your support.
I'll do my best too.
In my heart, I'm always right there with Shizuku.
So, I don't have any regrets left.
I had notes on everything I wanted to talk about, and I've managed to say it all.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for sticking with me for so long. The "Run, Deliver" 3DMV
is also out, so please check it out.
Oh, wait, sorry, I got that wrong.
2D?
The 2DMV was just uploaded to the official YouTube channel, so please go watch it.
It was the 2DMV.
Sorry about that.
Please check it out!
Both the 2DMV and the 3DMV... let me rephrase.
Both the 3DMV and the 2DMV for "Run, Deliver" were just released on the official YouTube channel.
Sorry, I'm always getting so flustered. My apologies.
I'm going to...
Once this stream is over, please watch them as much as you can.
Thank you!
Everyone...
Everyone's saying they're going to watch it.
Thank you so much.
And with that, it's time to wrap up this edition of ProSeka AfterTalk: "Glow Glorious Glow" edition!
To everyone watching the stream, how did you like it?
Wow, seeing all your supportive comments has made me so happy.
Momojan is just the best, seriously.
They just keep on growing more and more.
Growth without a ceiling is truly dazzling to witness.
Thank you all so much, really.
I had so much fun.
I really did.
Anyway, about "Glow Glorious Glow"... that's a bit of a tongue twister!
If you haven't finished reading "Glow Glorious Glow" yet, you can read it all in the Event Stories menu once the next event starts.
So please, read it over and over again.
The scenes I mentioned earlier that we didn't get to watch together today are all in there,
so I'd be happy if you think, "Oh, Hon-chan mentioned this part!" while you're reading.
Please check it out!
Well then, thank you all so much for sticking with me today.
See you again next time!
Bye bye!