Welcome to ProSeka Aftertalk "This story continues with hope" Edition!
This is Yuki Nakashima, voice of Shiho Hinomori from Leo/need!
In this edition of ProSeka Aftertalk, we'll look back at this event while covering messages you, the fans, have sent in.
This time, we'll be covering the "Unsteady, still steady step" event.
Ah, thank god I said it right.
When I first saw the script I was like,
"‘Unsteady, still steady step.’ There's way too many 'st's here."
"Is this supposed to be a tongue-twister?"
Right, so did you enjoy the this event's story, everyone?
Yep, I sure did read it right. Thank you.
"Kon-needo". Kon-needo.
It's like a st st party up in here.
Yeah but like,
talking about the story for real,
it's not like there were any earthshattering developments or decisions here,
Honami was just a little uncertain on this decision in front of her.
But,
"I liked the story!" Thank you.
Glad to hear.
We've a big of a mini-renewal for the Aftertalks since April
We've gathered your comments for this Aftertalk sent through email and the submissions channel on Discord.
Thanks for all the messages, everyone.
We'd like to go over some of them in our program today, so please look forward to that!
Also, if you have any thoughts on today's program,
please post them on X with #ProSekaAftertalk.
We'll also be watching the YouTube chat, so please keep all the messages coming.
Also, note that since the mini-renewal, we won't be watching the Afterlives. Thanks for your understanding.
Yeah, they're going to have to start choosing now that they're pros.
"Shindo-san helped out a ton." For sure.
I remember, that part where he's on the phone with her and— how to say—
the splitscreen part?
When it shows Honami and Shindo-san side by side,
it makes Shindo's frame look even bigger.
I saw it and was like,
"ah, that sure is a fully grown man."
"The Afterlive was really good!" Mmm!
Thank you!
Alright! Let's get right into the "Unsteady, still steady step" story—
there really are way too many "st st"s.
Let's get into the story.
Let's look back together while going over some of the messages you've sent in.
First up, a message from "King"-san. Thank you for the message.
"Kon-needo, Nakashima-san!" Kon-needo!
"I was really glad to see Leo/need growing more as pros in this story."
"Both the one-man live and the fan fes were big opportunities for Leo/need to move forward."
"There wasn't a clear right option so it was tough deciding which to write a new song for."
"I'm pretty indecisive myself and tend to freeze from over-analysis,"
so I was really able to sympathize with Honami."
"By the way Nakashima-san, when you're faced with important choices, how do you generally come to a decision?"
Thank you for the message?
Ehhhhhh?
I think usually,
I'm able to come up with a pretty clear option I'm favor more.
But if it were like the story, where I wanted to do both things...
I'd probably try to do both.
But if it were a real scheduling conflict, like on the exact same day,
like I had other work scheduled on the same day,
I'd just have to choose one.
but if it were like the story,
like if I ended up getting double booked and had to choose one,
I think I'd try to do both.
I'd probably try something like that.
I feel like I make decisions impulsively like that.
Oh yeah and of course,
I usually just go by vibes.
So sorry I can't really be of much help.
Actually, what would you all do?
Yeah. "If I could swing both, I'd definitely do it."
As uh... selfish as that would be www
Yeah...
Would probably try something like that.
Leave it up to vibes. Yeah.
"Flip a coin." Haha maybe.
Maybe if you're really don't want to regret your decision,
and you really can't decide on a clear favorite, maybe leaving it up to fate makes sense.
Play "eenie, meenie, miney, moe" or something.
That sure is one way to do it.
But I mean, like,
if it really were a "one or the other" situation,
I think I would just go with vibes...
Like just going with whatever my gut was telling me.
Even if I was just feeling it 1-2% more, I'd probably go with that one.
Right?
If I were in Leo/need's specific situation in the story,
and the request for the fan festa got withdrawn,
I'd actually be relieved.
I'd be like "Oh! We get to do both!"
Probably not good to think this way but I'd be like "we got lucky!"
Mmm. Something like that.
Okay. Let's move onto one more message.
Next up, from "Copy"-san. Thank you for the message.
"Yukki, kon-needo." Kon-needo.
"I was really excited to see Leo/need finally getting an opportunity to do their much-awaited one-man live."
"I was secretly hoping that they would do that instrument shuffle for the real thing."
Thank you for the message.
Oh yeah. Would definitely want to see that.
Ehhhh? Like,
I, uh, I don't really think I'd like that.
If I really had to do that, I'd be so nervous.
I wonder... Shiho switched from bass,
and had to play drums... or guitar or keyboard...
Would you even be able to get her to do it? That's what I'd be wondering.
I mean, if it were for rehearsal, I think she would be okay with it.
As someone so talented and self-confident in her music,
I think she'd have some pride on the line! Even if it were just for an MC, she'd be like "I'm not giving you my bass."
That being said...
I definitely would want to see that happen.
Seeing her get flustered like that... that'd be really fun to see.
But yeah, I kind of wanna see everyone go "how do you play this?"
I for sure could watch that forever.
w
But yeah, I'm interested in where the story will go from here.
"I can't really imagine Shiho-chan on the drums." Ahh, that's true.
Hmm, I don't know, she is good at keeping rhythm though,
so I feel like she might be able to keep up.
But your hands and feet are doing different things,
so she might end up a little flustered too. Very interested though.
"I'd wanna see her on guitar!"
Mmmmm.
That would be cool to see.
"Everyone going 'how do you play this?' would be so cute."  Oh yeah. 100%.
Ah, that would be so great to see.
So yeah, everyone, definitely look forward to the coming stories.
Thank you for the message.
Alright, I've picked a scene from the story I'd like to talk about, so let's watch it together.
This time, I chose Chapter 8.
Here we go!
Nakashima-san, could you play guitar when you started learning bass?
Nope.
I gave up on guitar pretty quick.
Speaking of Hona-chan as a leader,
her coming at it from the perspective of "which one will make our fans the happiest?"
and going out to  all that.
Actually going out of her way to really understand all the fans,
I think that's incredible. Shows her determination as a leader.
Waaah~
Great MV.
It has a feeling of, how to say, lightness and transparency,
while also keeping a pop vibe. Really nice.
I remember when I recorded for this song,
Even thought it's pretty upbeat,
I remember being asked to sing with a bit of hesitation and indecisiveness in the verse and prechorus.
Almost like I was a bit worn out.
And then in the chorus— how to say—
we were asked to sing with a much brighter and transparent feeling,
so that's how the song turned out.
Also, I love the part of the lyrics that says "and on days of celebration, we'll have apple pies" so much.
Actually, as far as commissioned song lyrics go,
I feel like this is the first time a character's favorite items have shown up.
I'm feel like that's the case.
Yeah. It's a pretty new feeling. And makes it easy to remember.
I remember that part being stuck in my head forever.
But a good kind of "stuck in my head". I really liked it.
Yeah
Actually, I saw that on the Master chart, there's an "apple pie" note
Somehow they made an "apple pie" note.
It's a super huge apple pie.
When I first played it, I was like "woah, it's an apple pie!"
If you're interested, definitely try out the Master chart.
Yo, will Shiho's ramen show up one day?
When would it show up?
Would Shiho get—
Would she get a pop song like this though?
I mean, I'd definitely be interested in seeing that.
Yeah, try the Master chart. It's uh...
You can, uh... they made it so you can play Master mode immediately now.
So do try it.
Would be cool if she got a metal song.
Kind of like "JYA JYA JYA",
or like "DA DO DO DAN DO" hahaha!
If ti really were like that...
I'd be a bit worried. If that really did happen.
just make it an April Fool's song if you're really gonna do it.
"Would have lots of slap bass." Yeah, I suppose it would.
"The steam from the ramen would zig zag everywhere."
Wow, everyone's already got so many creative ideas for this.
Really though, I'm excited for any potential favorite food inclusions in upcoming songs like this.
And getting to see Saki's outfit here in the MV was also really nice.
That heart mark here is actually different for everyone.
It's a super duper cute 2DMV.
Please check it out, everyone.
the 2DMV is already uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel, so be sure to watch it there.
Well then, it was just a short episode this time,
but that's all we have for the "Unsteady, still steady step" Aftertalk.
So quick!
That just flew by so quick.
It's already 9PM.
I saw the clock when I spun around, I was like "crap, it's already 9?"
I was like "I can't just be spinning here, we need to move on to watch the MV!"
That really did fly by.
"Let's do this again!" Yep.
"But I just got here!" Yeah!
So with that, if you haven't watched the "Unsteady, still steady step" event story yet,
after the next event starts, you can read it in-game in the "Event Story" section under the "Story" button, so please do so.
We'll be accepting submissions for future Aftertalks as usual.
You can submit your messages in the submissions channel on the official Project Sekai Discord, or through email.
Feel free to send them in after the next Aftertalk event starts.
Please keep your messages related to the events.
With that, thanks so much for a fun Aftertalk today!
See you again next time!
Bye bye!