Tomari-chan, we've really become a great duo, haven't we?
Now that you mention it, it's been quite a while since
I became a main personality alongside you, Kanon-senpai.
At first, I really worried about what we should talk about.
I remember you asking me if I was enjoying school.
I remember clearly how you told me
that you were having fun back then.
Of course, even now, I find school, school idols, and this radio show very enjoyable.
I can really tell how much you're enjoying this show, Tomari-chan.
After all, we're always facing each other like this during recordings.
Yes, I can see your expressions very clearly, Kanon-senpai.
Laughing, being troubled, being surprised...
You're so expressive that I never get tired of watching you.
Wait, really?
When you put it like that, it makes me feel like I don't have much of a "senpai" vibe.
Don't you have any thoughts like, "She's so reliable" or "She's so sharp"?
That's a difficult question.
It's that difficult?!
I'm just joking.
Of course I rely on you.
Oh, good.
I was getting a little worried.
Chi-chan once told me that I might act a bit childish on the radio.
I understand.
Since my way of talking is quite detached, you act that way on purpose to liven things up, right?
Huh?
Oh, well, I guess there's a bit of that...
Maybe.
But I think the main reason is that I really trust you, Tomari-chan.
Trust?
You're always so on top of things.
Your talk and timekeeping are perfect, so I think I've ended up depending on you.
It's not very good of me as your senior, is it?
No, it allows me to see a side of you that you don't show on stage,
and that honestly makes me happy.
Tomari-chan, you're such a good girl!
Let's keep delivering a fun radio show together from here on out.
Agreed.
Now, let's get today's recording started!
Yeah!
It's time for the Yuigaoka Girls' High School Suggestion Box, where we read your letters.
This is the Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Lunchtime Broadcasting Station, Lieraji!
Now, everyone say it with us! One, two... Suggestion Box!
Let's get right into the emails.
First, we have one from Liella name: Popcorn Who Wanted to Pop.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"I attended the 7th Live performance in Kanagawa."
"It was truly a blast."
"We got to see the solo songs for the first time, and Kanon-chan's 'Over Over' was especially hype!"
"Kanon-chan has always struggled with her feelings toward singing, so seeing her perform so happily..."
"It made me emotional realizing she reaffirmed her love for it through Season 3 of the anime."
"Her energy during the call-and-response really took my excitement to the max!"
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Next, we have one from Liella name: Mattsukutsui.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"Kanon-chan's 'Over Over' was so exciting!"
"I only realized this after seeing it live, but isn't that song incredibly difficult to sing?"
"Seeing Kanon-chan running around the stage with so much energy made me so happy,"
"but I also felt like she was singing at full power the entire time."
"I really felt like that song requires an immense amount of energy to pull off."
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
The solo songs...
Man, they were great.
Seriously.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
It's like...
I'm just so grateful.
Regarding 'Over Over'...
Kanon's past solo songs have had a lot of different vibes,
but I think this one was the most hype—or rather, it was like 150% pure positivity.
I was so happy to perform it.
It was amazing.
And you're right, it's actually a very difficult song to sing.
It's like being at full throttle the whole time. But since Kanon...
loves singing so much, she's always used a handheld mic,
and this time was no different. She gripped that mic tight,
feeling the blue sky pushing her forward as she sang.
So I, Sayuri, wanted to sing while feeling like I was that blue sky,
pushing Kanon forward from behind.
But to do that, I had to become the blue sky myself.
I felt like I had to go even beyond Kanon's level.
I don't know if "above" or "below" is the right way to put it,
but I felt like I needed to have more confidence than ever to support her.
That feeling made me so happy.
Also, I ran around the stage a lot to go see everyone in the audience.
Even though it's Kanon's song,
the lyrics use words like "we."
It's not just about her; it's about "how far can we go?"
It felt like she was singing to you, and with you.
So I made a conscious effort to look at the audience rather than the cameras.
I could tell.
That was so much fun, it just naturally made me smile.
I was genuinely enjoying myself.
That's lovely.
Like Sayuri said,
the feeling that it wasn't just about her really came across.
That's why everyone was cheering so loudly along with her.
Even though it's Kanon-chan's solo,
it felt like a song for everyone, created by everyone. That sense of unity was incredible.
I thought, "Wow, that looks like so much fun." It was beautiful.
It really was.
The lighting staff were so detailed too; they used marigold colors,
and they also used blue to represent the sky.
I was so happy they put so much thought into it.
Yeah.
I'm so grateful. It was a blast.
It was seriously so good.
I was actually really moved.
Like...
The tempo of the song is basically a full-on sprint the whole time.
It's not the kind of song that usually makes you feel quiet and emotional,
but even though it's so bright, it was somehow deeply moving.
Watching from backstage...
Even though my solo song is totally different from Kanon-chan's...
It was right after your solo performance, Sayurin, but...
seeing Kanon-chan's performance really gave us a push.
It made us feel like, "Alright, we're gonna do our best next!"
It was so great.
Actually, Saku came up to talk to me backstage.
I think it was during the rehearsal, but...
I was really nervous, wondering if I'd be okay.
But Saku came over and spoke to me, and it made me so happy.
She told me she was really moved by it.
I was moved every single time! It was amazing.
I was so happy. I thought, "Oh, it's Tomari-chan!"
It really made my day.
I got a lot of energy from you too.
Seeing Sayurin singing Kanon-chan's song...
I could really feel your soul in it.
My soul?
I'm honored.
Thank you.
Thanks for the soul.
I'm glad it reached you.
And the costume too, right?
Doesn't it fit perfectly?
That energetic vibe.
It really does.
Both options were good, and the other candidate was lovely too,
but once it was decided, I realized this one was the perfect fit.
I'm glad. The other one was like a long one-piece dress,
so if we'd gone with that, my movements probably would've been...
a bit more graceful, I think.
If you'd sprinted full speed in that, it would've looked a bit off.
Holding the hem of the dress like a princess going up the stairs.
I might have looked like I was just flailing around,
but it's all about the sneaker laces.
Just like Kanon.
Yeah.
It's in the lyrics of "Kokoro Kirarara" too.
And these colors, blue and orange, and on the back...
the "Superstar" embroidery.
It's so wonderful.
I love that it's on the back.
The fact that Kanon herself can't see it.
It feels like she's carrying it on her shoulders.
Exactly.
It brings a tear to my eye.
It really feels like everyone's attention to detail
came together to make it complete.
I was really happy about it.
Thanks for noticing all those details.
Thank you very much.
Shall we move on to the next one?
Sure.
Next, we have one from Radio name: Kabocha Samurai no Hasshin...
Wait, it's from Riya-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
"I attended Day 1 of the 7th Live in Kanagawa.
The visuals for 'Wild Card' on the screen matched the song perfectly,
and the costume had an Alice in Wonderland vibe.
I was completely drawn into that world.
The choreography also incorporated cards, and even though they weren't there,
it really looked like you were flipping and spreading them out."
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Next, we have one from Radio name: Yochi-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
"Great job on the two days of the 7th Live in Kanagawa.
I was there at the venue for both days.
Saku-chan, dressed in that cute white-based 'Wild Card' costume,
your singing and dancing with perfect facial expressions
was truly Tomari herself.
Since you mentioned the unique dance during the MC,
my friends and I had a great time mimicking it on our way home.
Thank you again for a wonderful live show."
That's the message.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
There it is.
There it is, 'Wild Card'!
Thank you so much.
How was it for you?
Well, since it was Tomari's first solo song,
I was really, really nervous.
Plus, it had been quite a while since I'd personally
performed at a Liella! live show.
So, I was actually pretty anxious about standing on stage alone to express Tomari's character.
But you know, from the very first day, during that initial 'clap-clap-clap' part,
even though I hadn't asked anyone to do it,
everyone joined in. I'd hoped they would, but
I didn't want to force it, so I didn't say anything.
In that moment, I felt this huge sense of relief.
I realized everyone was really watching and supporting me.
Even though I was standing on stage alone,
I felt like Tomari was with me and the audience was too. That feeling of not being alone
really gave me the courage to perform with confidence.
It's all thanks to everyone.
Thank you so much.
Man, it was just so good.
I absolutely loved it.
Yeah.
The way you did your expressions, and that sort of...
looking down from above, like a sidelong glance?
Saku,
as Tomari-chan,
was so good at that.
And that outfit suited you perfectly. It was so cute!
I have one favorite part—well, I love it all, but—
after the first chorus, when you sing 'Too Cute to Handle,'
on the... not the Oni... the big monitor?
You know that big monitor in the center?
Right after Saku says 'Too Cute to Handle' there,
she looks slightly to the side.
That face is seriously so cute. I mean, it's all cute,
every bit of it,
but while watching that, the cards... those cards,
they go 'whoosh' and
hide Tomari-chan behind them.
Up until then, we're all like, 'Ah, Tomari-chan!' but then
it's like she's gone,
like she's out of reach.
It just made my heart skip a beat.
I see. So you noticed that detail.
How should I put it... it's like,
there's a bit of mystery, but then there's that cute 'heart' feeling,
like the way you sang with hearts at the end of your lines.
And the dance used the stairs, right?
You had to move around, yet you kept your expressions and singing
perfectly in character as Tomari-chan the whole time.
It was truly amazing.
Aw, I'm so happy to hear that.
I definitely put a lot of thought into the expressions.
I knew I couldn't just be my usual self,
so I tried not to be too bubbly
and focused on keeping a cooler vibe.
Also, when we were learning the choreography,
they don't usually give specific instructions for your gaze.
Yeah, the dance teachers don't really tell you where to look.
So I thought about it myself, and
I felt like just staring straight ahead wouldn't be right.
I wanted to create moments where I'd look away, making people think, 'Wait, look at me!'
And then, 'Oh, she looked at me!'
I wanted to express that kind of back-and-forth teasing.
Whoa.
I thought it'd be good, so I intentionally added more moments
where I'd turn my face away. It was all calculated.
No way, that was calculated?!
Oh man, you've totally captured my heart. This is bad!
Also, for the choreography and expression changes,
I changed them slightly for each performance day. I hoped
that people who noticed would think, 'Oh, it's different today!'
I had that kind of thing going on too.
Actually, quite a lot of people noticed.
Oh?
They'd say things like, 'Wait, wasn't that different?'
when looking back at it,
or that the timing of the glances was different.
You really seemed so composed and effortless.
No, no, not at all.
But it was seriously so cute.
I was just acting calm, but my heart was pounding.
I really didn't know what to do.
You deserve a huge round of applause. It was amazing.
And before me... well, right before me was Pay-chan.
Sumire's song and her performance were just so overwhelming. Everyone was great, but...
Sumire had this incredible confidence,
and Pay-chan is so talented. So, following that...
there was a lot of pressure when I went out there.
But I felt like looking too desperate wouldn't be very Tomari-like.
I see, I see.
So I practiced as hard as I could,
and gave it my all.
But watching the stream back, there are so many things...
I wish I had done differently.
So if I ever get to do it again,
I want to raise the quality of my performance even more.
Right, right.
But it was a lot of fun.
And that costume really suited you, too.
What did you think of it, Saku?
I was so happy. You know, with "Wild Card"...
when I first heard it, it felt really dark and cool,
with a bit of an alluring vibe.
And...
when the "Behind the Spider" story came out,
I realized the song was about showing a side of Tomari that had never been seen before.
So I always felt like she wanted to show...
that she's more than just "cool."
That's why, while the other costume was also wonderful,
and I liked it too... how should I put it?
I thought if the costume had a completely different vibe from the song,
it would be easier to express Tomari's growth.
I felt this one created a better contrast with the lyrics, so when it was chosen...
Yeah.
I was really happy about it.
Ah, I see.
It really did look great on you.
But I want to see Toma wearing it.
Oh, that would be nice. Definitely.
I'm so happy that everyone's been drawing illustrations of it,
but I hope we can see her in it officially someday.
I didn't think Tomari would ever wear an outfit that went so all-in on being cute.
I thought that going forward,
it might not happen, so I feel like this is a new change for Tomari herself.
Yeah.
It's like, because she fell in love with school idols, she can now show a side of herself she never could before, and the outfit reflects that.
Right.
I'm so glad she got to wear something so cute.
It was super cute.
I want like, three of these for my house... this, this...
This thing.
Yeah.
Like a figure! But seriously, it's so cute.
Just like a little figure.
And it suits her perfectly.
It really does.
I'm so happy they even included that playing card cat embroidery.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
The visuals on the screen were amazing too.
The visuals?
It said "Sasaki" in the background.
It was truly beautiful.
They put so much detail into it. Thank you so much, really.
Thank you!
I want to watch just that part again.
Just that part?
Well, I was watching it.
Ah.
It was lovely.
I'm so happy to hear that.
And Tomari-chan... Sakun's expression was also very, very, very wonderful.
Truly.
I'm so happy. I can't thank you enough.
Oh?
We're running out of time.
We're out of time.
Time is just flying by.
We have to move on to the next one.
Let's go.
Next is from Liella name: K1.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Great job on the Love Live! Superstar!! Liella! 7th LoveLive! Fly and High!! Music World Kanagawa performance.
Thank you!
I was there to see it in person both days.
The song that personally left an impression on me was the second one, "UTOPIA MAGIC."
Mm-hmm.
I felt the lyrics in the chorus about "casting a spell on the usual scenery" fit the theme of this concert perfectly.
Yeah.
With the different hairstyles and the new performance structure, even small changes made it feel as fresh as if I were seeing it for the first time.
That's what they said.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Next, we have one from Liella name: Kubo-san.
Thank you very much.
I attended the Liella! 7th LoveLive! Fly and High!! Music World Kanagawa performance.
Thank you!
"UTOPIA MAGIC" was performed for the first time since the 3rd Live, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I wasn't able to attend the 3rd Live,
so I was so happy I accidentally let out a shout the moment the intro started playing.
Aww.
Since it was performed on stage this time,
the choreography for the chorus especially left a lasting impression.
I love the cute choreography, like making heart shapes with your hands and walking energetically.
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Yes.
"UTOPIA MAGIC."
We had both the low and high voices there.
But man, it was great having that as the second song.
In recent Liella! lives, the second song has usually been something like "Let's do this!"
Yeah.
Songs with a lot of grit and energy.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I totally get what you mean.
Um, what was it again?
Yeah, it was really intense.
I totally didn't expect 'UTOPIA MAGIC' to come up so early,
I know what you mean.
Yeah.
It feels more like a song you'd save for the encore, doesn't it?
Yeah, definitely.
Mhm.
But they performed it as the second song.
But it really fit the 'Music World' atmosphere perfectly.
Yeah.
That whole vibe.
Right?
It had such a theme park feel to it.
I totally get it.
We were even saying... what was it again?
Was it like a musical?
We talked about wanting to do it like that.
Yeah.
We did.
Like a parade.
That's it!
We were told to have the energy of parade performers, welcoming everyone,
Yeah.
and to use really big, wide movements.
We all talked about it together.
Right. And since it was the second song, after doing 'Open The Gate' on the second level,
Yeah.
we moved down for 'UTOPIA MAGIC'.
The choreography was designed to show a lot of movement.
Yeah.
Well, that's true for every song, but...
we discussed how we wanted the members' expressions
and movements to really come across in that second song.
I wanted people to think, 'Oh, Kanon is right there!' so I used the freestyle parts to wave.
Yeah, yeah.
Mhm.
Kanon waves her hands really wide, but...
Yeah.
I thought it might be hard for characters like Tomari or Shiki to wave like that.
It actually was pretty hard, yeah.
Those differences in expression...
varied by member, so it was something we really focused on.
Yeah, definitely.
That's true.
Exactly.
We really thought about how each individual member would dance or wave.
I feel like it was a song where we really connected with our characters.
Yeah.
Even the choreography was different for some members, right?
Like that part at the very end.
Oh, true.
Wait, what was Kanon doing there?
During the 'dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-durururu' part at the end?
Let's see... at that moment,
after saying 'Welcome,' it was like, 'Hyah!'
Was it something like that?
I was pointing up at the sky.
Yeah, while jumping.
That's nice!
Tomari is actually hilarious right there.
Wait, what? What?
What does Tomari do?
Right there, at that part.
Tomari is doing a jellyfish move.
Wait, hold on a second.
I don't think I knew that!
I talked with the dance teacher like, 'What should Tomari do here?'
Everyone else was doing movements that felt like their characters, but we wondered what Tomari's would be.
Right.
Yeah.
But since this song...
is so cute and catchy, we thought instead of her usual cool and sharp self,
Yeah.
maybe we should make her look a little cute.
I love that! Yeah.
So we decided on this... jellyfish move.
That's way more of a jellyfish than I expected, now that I've seen it.
Is it?
I don't think anyone has noticed it yet,
at least from what I've seen.
Yeah.
It was really funny, wasn't it?
But, you know, Tomari-chan... how should I put it?
She has these surprisingly humorous expressions.
Exactly, exactly.
She's probably being serious and doesn't mean to be funny, but from an outsider's perspective, it's hilarious.
Yeah.
It really makes me think she's her sister's sister.
Ah, right. They really are related.
Definitely.
The blood connection is there.
I see, I see.
She's a bit of a natural in what she does.
Watching her is so unpredictable, which makes it really interesting.
I totally get it.
Yeah,
it's funny.
So she was doing a jellyfish?
She was.
I see.
While doing that choreography, I wondered what kind of faces everyone had, so I looked at the people in the front, but no one looked confused.
They were all just smiling at us.
I see. Maybe they were under the spell of UTOPIA.
Maybe they were.
Maybe they didn't even realize it was a jellyfish.
Apparently, that part was a jellyfish, everyone.
Yeah.
It was a jellyfish.
It's such a fun song, I hope we can perform it again sometime.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do it.
Anyway, thank you everyone for all the mail.
Thank you so much.
Now, let's play a song.
We're going to play the song we just talked about, "UTOPIA MAGIC."
Here it comes!
It's here.
Here it is!
Everyone, please fall under the spell of "UTOPIA MAGIC" again.
Yes.
Now, please listen.
By Liella!,
"UTOPIA MAGIC."
There's no real meaning, but I'm having fun waving at the contrails.
After laying out a picnic sheet, the rooftop where I sing with you is UTOPIA.
Ah, the wind slipping through the base.
Catch it now, even that sky...
It feels like I could fly.
Casting a spell on the usual scenery.
Your smile gives me happiness,
too.
If I say "I love you" out loud, everywhere becomes the most wonderful place.
Please stay by my side forever from now on.
Finally,
I can touch it as many times as I want, so let's hold our breath.
It's okay,
on the count of three.
The scenery is looking all fluffy.
Basking in the sunlight with a dazed feeling,
my precious treasures
keep increasing.
If you're here, even the future will shine.
This is the most wonderful place, enough to make me forget time.
Let those fingers stay there forever.
Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Lunchtime Broadcast Station, Lieraji.
Announcements from Love Live! Superstar!!
First, regarding music information, we have some brand new news.
Yeah.
We will be releasing a new single on Wednesday, June 17th.
Yay!
Wait, what is it?
This is so sudden.
So sudden.
Yes, this single is scheduled to include one new song and its off-vocal version, for a total of two tracks.
Details will be announced at a later date, so please look forward to it.
Next, on Wednesday, July 8th, we will release the "Liella to Musubu Project" mini-album.
This will be released in five versions: Original, Photo, Team Kodomo, Team Sports, and Team Midori.
The Original, Team Kodomo, Team Sports, and Team Midori versions will feature new illustrations,
while the Photo version will feature new photos of the cast.
This mini-album is scheduled to include four songs, including one new group song, plus their off-vocal versions for a total of eight tracks.
Also, all versions will include an advance lottery application ticket for the Love Live! Series 15th Anniversary Love Live! Fes
and Love Live! Superstar!!.
Additionally, as a first-press bonus, the Original, Team Kodomo,
Team Sports, and Team Midori versions will include stickers.
The Photo version will include purikura-style stickers.
Furthermore, as a bundle purchase bonus, you'll receive a Liella! sticker book.
Don't forget to pre-order.
And to celebrate the release of the "Liella to Musubu Project" mini-album, we've decided to hold a handover event.
Nice.
The dates are Friday, October 2nd and Friday, October 9th.
Those who pre-order or purchase the mini-album at participating stores
will be invited to the handover event via a lottery.
The cast members will vary by date, so please check the application requirements
before applying.
Please check the Love Live! Superstar!! official website for details.
Next is an announcement from the Love Live! Series Official Card Game.
The Start Deck "Love Live! Superstar!!" featuring only Liella! members and songs is coming.
The latest information will be posted on the Loveca official website and official X account,
so please keep an eye out.
Now for appearance information.
Starting April 1st, Season 2 of "Liella no Tutorial" will begin on Nippon TV.
Time Machine 3-go will continue as the program MCs from Season 1.
Catch-up streaming will be available on TVer and Nittele TADA after the broadcast.
Don't forget to check it out.
Furthermore, a live event to commemorate the broadcast, "Love Live! Superstar!! Liella no Tutoria-Live 2026," will be held on August 1st
and 2nd at LaLa arena TOKYO-BAY.
Official advance lottery applications are currently open on Ticket Pia until 11:59 PM on Sunday, March 22nd.
Please check this out as well.
For details on all the information announced today, please check the official Liella! X account
or the Love Live! Superstar!! official website.
That's all for the announcements.
It's almost time to say goodbye to Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Lunchtime Broadcast Station, Lieraji.
We're always looking for your emails here at Lieraji.
We're currently accepting thoughts on our songs, the TV anime, and our live concerts,
as well as general mail like messages and questions for us.
We also have "Hamburg is Agree," where you share your little favorites,
and "Lunchtime Request," where you request Liella! songs to cheer you up.
Finally, there's "Open the Gate, Ouen the Yell,"
where we give you a push when you need some support.
We're waiting for lots of emails!
And now, here's the info for the next broadcast.
Episode 265, airing next Tuesday, March 24th, will feature Yabushima Akane, the voice of Mei Yoneme, as our guest.
Yep.
So, we talked a lot today, but...
how was it for you?
Man, it wasn't enough.
It really wasn't.
Still not enough.
Not enough at all!
Look, I still have so much left to say.
Yeah, yeah.
Because there's just so much to talk about.
Thank you, Mino-san.
Thank you so much.
Can we keep talking next week? I wonder if we can.
It looks like we'll be able to talk more next week too.
Then let's talk then!
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Otherwise, we'll just keep talking about our 7th Live impressions forever.
I honestly want to talk about it for the next three years.
Right?
The things we want to say about the live just keep piling up.
Everything ends up being about the 7th Live.
If we don't do Lieraji every single day, it might not be enough.
Let's do it every day then!
Shall we?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
We're doing it every day now!
Send us your mail!
Yep.
That's right.
Just kidding.
We're kidding.
Please tune in next week too!
We'll be waiting!
That's all for this episode of Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Lunchtime Broadcast Station: Lieraji.
Your hosts were Date Sayuri, the voice of Kanon Shibuya,
and Sakakura Sakura, the voice of Tomari Onitsuka.
See you!
I want to be with you.
Time and heartbeats
are creatures that know no hesitation.
In the twilight...
Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Lunchtime Broadcast Station: Lieraji.