Hello,
everyone.
I am Nakashima Yuki,
the voice of Hinomori Shiho from Leo/need.
Thank you so much
for this letter.
Hello, hello.
I am so excited that Leo/need's long-awaited first one-man live as pros is finally happening.
The letter says, "Personally, I would love to see an MC segment where everyone swaps instruments during the actual show."
Thank you very much.
I would definitely
like to see that.
But she might hate it.
If I were in her position, I would be incredibly nervous.
I wonder...
If Shiho had to play the drums or the keyboard instead of the bass,
I wonder if she would actually be willing to go along with it.
They did it because it was just a rehearsal, but when it comes to music,
she is so confident in her skills that her pride might make her refuse even for an MC segment, but I still want to see it.
I want to see her getting all flustered.
I really want to see everyone struggling and saying they can't do it.
I feel like I could listen to that and watch it forever.
Yes.
I want them to do it.
I wonder what would happen.
I am looking forward to seeing how the story develops.
I can't really imagine Shiho on the drums.
That is true.
She seems like she would be good at keeping rhythm, so she might handle it well, but
since your hands and feet have to move differently, she might end up fumbling after all.
I am curious.
I would like to see her on guitar too.
Yes.
I really want to see that.
She would definitely end up saying she can't do it.
True.
Exactly.
I definitely want to see that.
Everyone, please look forward to the future story.
Thank you for the letter.
I have picked out another scene that I personally want to talk about,
so let's take a look right away.
The one I chose is from Episode 8.
Here it is.
Can you play the guitar as well as the bass, Nakashima-san?
No, I can't.
She is giving up on both the one-man and the Fan Festa.
She said she looked into everything she possibly could on her own.
She understands how both sides of the audience feel now.
But what about Hona-chan's role as a leader?
She still hasn't found
the answer within herself as to which is better.
It is great that she researches every little detail.
She wants to show the way. Ichika-chan told her not to take it all on herself, and it is something for everyone to decide, but if she stays indecisive, it might just lead everyone astray.
That is why
she needs to make up her mind.
It is wonderful that she feels she has to decide on her own feelings here.
But I also hope it doesn't become too much of a burden for her.
Look.
The fans will definitely be happy with a new song for the one-man.
And she thinks Saki-chan and Shiho-chan would surely want to do that too.
However,
I really love this song.
Yes.
Episode 7 was great too.
It makes you feel like you aren't alone.
She wants people who love Virtual Singers to hear their music too.
Ichika-chan surely feels the same way.
If you think too much, you won't be able to choose.
If I have to choose one,
then I...
What I choose is...
Wait?
Shindo-san?
Good work today.
Good work.
I am sorry
for calling so late.
There is something I need to report urgently.
The timing was so perfect, it really surprised me.
.
Actually,
the request for the new song for the Fan Festa has been withdrawn.
?
Please, don't be alarmed.
It wasn't due to any fault on our part.
The representative just contacted me.
It seems they heard back from the creator who was ill.
...
So you mean the person who was originally in charge of the song?
Yes.
They said they'll be able to finish all three songs as planned, and they were very apologetic.
It sounded like they were ready to prostrate themselves over the phone.
...
I see.
But I'm glad they're feeling better.
It is a bit disappointing that the offer fell through, though.
True.
However, we actually received a new request.
A new one?
The rep said they'd love to have Leo/need perform in the 'Freshman Slot' at the next Fan Festa.
It's partly to make up for this time.
?
It's a bit further out, but I think we should consider it positively.
Since it's in the future, there shouldn't be any scheduling issues.
I understand.
I'll talk to the rest of the members about it.
Please do.
There's no rush, so feel free to take your time deciding.
I'm truly sorry for causing so much confusion in the end.
This is so realistic.
.
I think it couldn't be helped.
Besides, I'm glad we found out before we officially accepted.
I'm relieved to hear you say that.
I'll do my best to support you so you can focus on the one-man live and the new songs.
We're counting on you.
That's good.
Right now, I...
Well then, I'll leave contacting the other members to you.
I'll get in touch with the staff for the one-man live.
I want to proceed with the setlist that includes the new song.
...
.
I'll let them know.
Thank you very much.
I'll be going now.
I...
I feel so relieved right now.
.
Yeah.
I'm just so relieved.
I thought I had to make a choice, that I had to pick one over the other, but now that I don't have to...
I'm just glad.
I'm relieved.
She's so admirable.
Truly admirable.
But...
This isn't good.
This time I happened to avoid it, but there will surely be times in the future when I have to choose.
.
Times when I'll have to make a decision where there is no right answer.
That's why...
I need to become someone who can make those choices.
.
So that I can lead everyone.
She's leading herself.
As the leader of Leo/need.
.
And that was Episode 8.
Personally, the scene that caught my attention...
The part that left an impression was when Honami-chan said she would definitely choose...
She seemed a bit down, but...
The scene where she resolves to lead everyone as their leader was really moving.
If it were me, I'd probably be more optimistic, like 'Oh, wow!'
That's how I'd feel.
I've never had a job like being a leader before, so...
I wonder about that part.
How should I put it?
I find her strong sense of responsibility to be quite reliable,
but I also don't want her to take things too heavily. If she keeps going like that, she might break,
so it was a scene that made me worry about Honami-chan.
That's why I chose this scene for today.
This time, the offer was almost withdrawn, but then they were told they could have a slot...
You might feel lucky, but if it was withdrawn without a second chance, you'd definitely regret not speaking up sooner.
Decisions like that are really difficult.
But there are many times in life when you have to make those kinds of choices.
I'm not sure how Honami will make her choices from now on, or
what kind of path Leo/need will take, but
I want to keep watching over them. I hope they don't end up on bad terms or
have their mental health suffer.
I honestly don't know what kind of story is waiting for us either.
...
That's just how it is.
Project Sekai event stories always leave some kind of foreshadowing.
It's only natural, since the story continues.
It's natural, but still...
I wish she could share some of Yukki's lightheartedness.
Well, maybe it's still too early for that.
They're still high school students, after all.
I want them to worry a lot,
and learn from their failures.
It'll be okay.
.
That said, there was one more scene that caught my eye personally.
It was in Episode 7, and it also appeared in the middle of Episode 8.
I really liked the part in Episode 7 where Honami and Ichika go to see Miku's concert. Ichika was more excited than usual.
She was all giddy,
like, "It's Miku!"
I thought it was so cute.
I thought about featuring that part too, but
if I did, I'd just end up saying "how cute" the whole time, just like the audience.
So I decided to stick with Episode 8.
Episode 7 was really cute too.
It makes me want to watch it again.
...
You should go back and read it.
That part was truly adorable.
I want to go to a Miku concert too!
Actually...
.
Back when the title was still "MikuPa," I'm from Wakayama,
and there was a concert there. I was just as excited as Ichika.
I was like, "It's Miku!"
"It's Miku!"
I was getting all hyped up like that.
.
I want everyone to experience that feeling too.
Anyway, I got a bit sidetracked again. This time,
I'd like to take a look at the card illustrations.
First, I'll share some comments from the illustration team regarding the outfits.
This story was about Honami realizing the importance and weight of making decisions as a leader.
It's an episode about a leader's struggles, but the design reflects a positive outlook on the best choice for Leo/need.
Inspired by the rhythmic song, it captures a lightheartedness that keeps moving forward, with a sweet cuteness rare for the band.
The design features pop and cute star patterns along with casual sneakers.
To show them choosing their path, each of the three has a planisphere-like element in their outfit.
We also incorporated items where the color palette is meant to resemble a compass.
This palette represents the choice between Leo/need's new song and Miku's song,
symbolizing the many choices that will continue to appear in the future.
Let's take a look.
Now, where should we start?
From where?
Do we usually start with the 4-stars?
Let's start with the 4-stars then.
Here they are.
This is the card illustration for the scene that appeared in Episode 8.
This is the pre-training version.
Honami has a bit of a surprised look on her face, but that smartphone case is so soothing.
Is that a Shiba Inu on it?
It looks like one. It's very comforting.
And here is the post-training version.
Oh, this is nice.
This one is in portrait orientation. It looks even better when you view it that way.
Leo/need hasn't really had anything this pop and cute until now.
.
...
There's so much detail in it.
And look, there's a dog in the building in the background.
I love it. There's a compass on the bag too.
...
So, this is Honami's post-training art.
And the can is actually apple juice.
.
It's so good.
Moving on...
Ichika's training art.
This was in Episode 7.
Ichika was telling us not to worry too much about it.
.
And here is the post-training version.
I'm losing my vocabulary here.
It's just too good.
I can't say anything but 'it's good.' I love how the whole scene is visible in Ichika's art.
And the way she's sitting with her knees up with her guitar on her back is just wonderful.
I call it 'sankaku-zuwari' (triangle sit).
Is that what it's called?
.
Oh, my regional dialect is showing.
Is 'sankaku-zuwari' a Kansai thing?
People say it, right?
You've never heard it?
No?
Really?
You haven't?
.
Wait?
Sorry, I meant 'taiiku-zuwari' (gym sit).
.
Is it a dialect?
My apologies.
Doesn't sitting like that feel so 'student-like'?
You don't really sit like that once you're an adult.
Maybe only during a photoshoot.
If they tell you to sit there like a student, you might do it.
I'm being told 'taiiku-zuwari' is standard, but 'sankaku-zuwari' is Kansai-only.
I'm so sorry.
My mistake.
Anyway, I personally love it because it feels so much like a student.
Also, the background... there are so many instruments!
It's like...
there are so many, right?
There's a guitar, a bass, an acoustic guitar...
and you can even see some drums.
It's amazing.
.
That was Ichika.
Next is Rin.
Pre-training Rin.
She's all excited for a party.
That's our Rin.
Leo/need Rin is so good.
I really love how she's overflowing with that 'gyaru' vibe.
.
And that paper chain around her neck... she definitely made that herself.
Like a student would.
When you have a party, you always put those up on the walls.
.
And are those loose socks?
That's another great touch.
It really adds to the gyaru feel.
Wait, I mean...
the post-training art.
.
It's wonderful.
This really captures all of Rin's...
charm.
I love that she's wearing a sleeveless top underneath.
And what do you call this part...
of the road?
I love that she's walking along the curb.
It's so like Rin.
I want to tell her not to swing her instrument around.
I want to tell her not to get hurt.
Loose socks really are cute.
Trends always come back around eventually.
They really do.
And that ribbon is just adorable too.
It suits her so well.
.
That sigh... she's just too cute.
Now for Shiho...
Shiho's Training card.
Thank you so much for this, really.
Thank you for drawing such a lovely illustration.
It makes me so happy.
I could just spin around.
Really.
Wait a second.
Looking at the YouTube comments and seeing myself spin on the lag,
is so embarrassing.
.
Is she okay?
She looks drowsy. Maybe she slept too much the day before.
She looks so sleepy.
.
Very much so.
Plus, on the wall in the back, is that a photo
from the autumn shuffle event? Having that there is a nice touch.
I should look at this instead of that.
This is really great.
I'm happy I can see the details of Shiho's room like this,
and even the soles of her feet.
Usually, they're wearing shoes,
or you just can't see their feet at all.
Seeing the soles of a character's feet, especially a 2D one,
is actually kind of nice.
What am I even saying?
Am I a creep?
I'm going to get scolded,
by the devs.
"Please don't look at things like that!"
Then don't draw it in the first place, honestly!
They'll ask me what's wrong with me.
No, no, I'm just overflowing with love.
And that was only the Pre-Training version.
Let's look at the Post-Training one too.
Oh, it went back.
Post-Training.
This is nice.
So cute.
That varsity jacket...
And...
it's rare to see her with something like tea.
Maybe it's apple tea?
I have a feeling it is.
She's drinking that... I didn't know Shiho drank apple tea.
It really gives off that vibe.
It's lovely.
The location looks like it's in front of a music store, which really fits her.
Also, since Shiho's character color is light green,
using a green apple like this is a great touch.
It's so good.
.
I almost spun around again.
I was about to spin again.
My apologies.
And finally... Saki.
This is Saki's 2-star card.
When Saki wears it, the atmosphere changes,
and she looks so much more mature. It's amazing.
Really amazing.
The logo on the sleeve is great too. I want that logo.
Leo/need.
The Ln logo.
I want it so bad, I wish they'd make it into merch.
Someone said it's okay to spin as many times as I want.
But it's embarrassing, so I'll stop.
You usually do these After Talks alone, at your own pace,
so I end up acting like my usual self, which is embarrassing to watch later.
Even though it's an official stream, I'm just going at my own pace,
so I start to wonder if this is really okay.
.
I'm so sorry, really.
I really want that Leo/need logo.
I want them to release it as a patch or something.
Please make it happen someday, higher-ups.
Please enjoy.
So, let's take a look at the illustrations.
.
Next, I'd like to talk about the song and the MV while watching the 2D MV for 'Transparent Palette,' which Akuera-san drew specifically for this event.
So, let's watch the 2D MV that was released yesterday.
.
It's good.
This MV is really great, it has a sense of transparency but it's also poppy.
When we were recording this song... it's very refreshing, but
in the A and B sections, there's a lot of hesitation.
I was told to convey a sense of bewilderment and not to sing it too strongly.
And for the chorus... how should I put it...
I was told to sing with a sense of transparency, and we all sang it together.
Personally, I love the lyric about having apple pie on a day of celebration so much.
In the lyrics written for us...
there haven't been many times where a character's favorite thing is mentioned so directly.
.
Does it feel like her?
I had that image... I remember it feeling quite fresh.
That part just keeps playing in my head. I personally really like it.
And also, I think it was on the Master difficulty chart?
An apple pie appears in it.
They worked hard to make it look like an apple pie, a really big apple pie.
It was like, 'Oh, it's an apple pie!' and I played it a bit.
If you're curious, please try playing the Master difficulty.
I wonder if Shiho's ramen will show up eventually? Do you think so?
Would Shiho even get such a poppy song?
But I'd certainly like to see it.
Try playing the Master chart.
...
The Master chart should be available to play right away, so
please give it a try.
Shiho and ramen... I can't quite imagine it.
A little...
Do they want us to play it that much?
Or maybe they want it to be metal?
Like 'chugga-chugga-chugga-chugga.'
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d!
Slap bass is impossible... true.
The steam from the ramen would be all zigzaggy.
Wow, you have a great imagination.
In this way, characters' favorite things might be included in the future,
so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm also happy to see Saki-chan in her outfit here.
I also noticed that the heart marks and logos were different for each of them.
It's a very cute 2D MV, so please everyone, check it out.
It's been uploaded to the official Proseka YouTube channel,
so please take a look.
And with that, our short time is up. This concludes the Proseka After Talk: Unsteady Steady Step edition.
Oh.
It went by so fast, I just realized it's already past 9:00.
I thought about it when the time passed.
I realized quite a bit of time had passed while I was talking.
I thought, 'I shouldn't be doing this, I have to watch the MV too,'
or something like that.
.
It went by in a flash.
Let's do this again.
That's right.
I think I just got word...
I can talk more? Thank you!
So, for those who haven't finished the 'Unsteady Steady Step' event story yet,
even after the next event starts, you can read it all from the Event Story archives,
so please give it a read.
We are still looking for messages for After Talk.
We're accepting them via the After Talk message channel on the official Proseka Discord or via email.
When the next After Talk event is held, please send them in.
Please send in messages related to the event.
Anyway, I had a lot of fun.
I'll see you all again.
.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.