Right.
So today, rather than us just talking,
Yes.
we really wanted you to see that scene. Thank you so much for sharing all your impressions in the comments.
Thank you.
We really appreciate it.
With that story in mind, we'd like to talk a bit about how we approached our roles as actors.
These are just some things we kept in mind while performing, so please keep that in mind as you listen.
From Ena's perspective, regarding Episode 8...
Well, not just Episode 8, but looking back at the previous story too, I tried to put myself in Ena's shoes. I couldn't find a 'right' answer at all. I kept thinking about how she'd feel and act, staring at the script until we got to Episode 8. I found myself getting swept up in the emotional atmosphere of the event story and the direction.
I just couldn't help but feel tearful,
and the tears just kept welling up.
The script for Episode 8 always has notes on the nuances of how they want us to perform.
There were detailed instructions like 'cry here' or 'sniffle here.'
Based on that, I initially planned to play Ena as someone crying because she desperately wanted to tell Mizuki,
'You're fine just as you are' and 'You're important to me.'
I wanted to perform with that honest feeling. But when I got to the recording, the direction I received was that they wanted a 'catfight.'
When they said they wanted to see a catfight between Mizuki and Ena, I asked,
'So I don't have to cry? I can actually fight?'
When I thought about what kind of Ena that would be, it hit me. The script literally says Ena hasn't changed.
My initial plan and the notes in the script were lovely,
but being overly careful because she cares so much about Mizuki didn't feel quite like Ena.
Caring is important, but because she cares, it was more important for her to clash and have their usual arguments, like 'Why don't you get it?' Since I'm not actually Ena, looking at it from the outside made it feel like this grand, epic thing.
The problem itself is certainly something only Mizuki can truly understand.
But for the two of them, and for Ena, it was probably just a fight.
We might have made it seem like a huge deal from the outside, but I interpreted it as the first time these two truly clashed with someone they hadn't been able to be honest with before. That's how I approached the performance.
I was worried because the illustration of an angry Ena didn't match what I'd imagined, but it turned out so wonderful that I'm really relieved.
Yes.
So, that was Episode 8. Since we're here,
Mizuki had a lot going on in this Episode 8 and the previous one, and there was that back-and-forth with Ena. I'd love to hear about that if we have time.
Do we have time?
Right.
From Mizuki's perspective,
you can't miss either of those Episode 8s.
In the previous Episode 8, Ena was mostly at a loss for words,
so for me, that was all there was to it. How about you, Mizuki?
Mizuki-chan?
Well, let's see.
I don't think it's my place to say exactly what the character was thinking, so I'll talk about the technical side. For the previous event and this one, I debated until the very last minute whether to record standing up.
When it comes to voice acting, I'm the type who feels I need to perform with my whole body, so I thought standing would be better, like on stage.
But when you're crying, you lose strength in your legs. I decided it might be better to sit so I could focus entirely on the voice. For the previous Episode 8, my initial plan was to speak clearly even while crying, but the direction was to cry more. We did about three or four takes. I recorded without hearing Minori-chan's lines,
both last time and this time. So I heard our full interaction at the same time as everyone else.
Seeing how it all came together as a finished work,
I feel like I gave it my absolute all.
We see each other quite often, even if we don't record together.
We're always talking about things like, 'How did you record that?'
or 'What kind of direction did you get?'
This is a small request for the staff,
but we've said it would be wonderful if we could record together in the same studio someday.
The ProSeka staff really respect the actors' performances.
Mizuki and Ena have grown, and they might hit another big wall in the future,
or they might move to help someone else.
I hope we can record those kinds of wonderful scenes together next time.
It's amazing how well it fit together without us being in the same room. We're pretty good, aren't we?
Yeah! Anyway, that's what we wanted to share.
It's almost time, so let's all watch the AfterLive together.
Yes.
Private...