Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk for the event "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow."
Yay!
Good evening, everyone.
"I'm Hinata Sato, the voice of Mizuki Akiyama from Nightcord at 25:00."
"ProSeka AfterTalk is a stream where we look back on the event while reading letters from all of you."
"This time, we're focusing on "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow.""
"Did you all enjoy the story?"
"The event just ended yesterday. How was it for everyone?"
What did you think?
I hope you all enjoyed it.
It was a story where Mizuki really faced their future and thought about what they want to do.
I think it was a very meaningful chapter.
"For those of you at an age where you have to decide on your education or career path, parts of this story might have really hit home."
"Also, AfterTalk had a mini-renewal in April."
"We've been collecting your messages in advance via the official ProSeka Discord and email."
"Thank you so much to everyone who sent one in."
"I'll be reading some of your letters during the show,"
so please look forward to that.
If you want to post your impressions of the event or this stream,
please use the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
I'm keeping an eye on the YouTube chat and I'll check the hashtag later too,
"so I'll try to pick out some interesting comments."
"There are more international comments than I expected! I can't find many in Japanese. "Your ribbon is cute," "Your hair matches Mizuki's...""
"The stream is probably a bit delayed for you right now,"
"but I see people mentioning my hair and outfit."
"I tried to match the card illustration for today."
"Well, I always try to, but I was especially conscious of it this time."
Good evening! Hello everyone.
"Thank you all for being here."
"Oh, someone said, "The story and the new song were so good I sobbed.""
"I'll talk about the song later."
"When I saw it at home, I was like, "What is this?!""
In a good way! I was just stunned.
"I really felt the incredible effort the team put into it."
Yes, exactly.
"But we'll save that talk for later."
"So, let's dive right into the story of "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow.""
"Here we go."
"We received letters about this story as well,"
"so I'd like to look back on the events while reading them."
"First, we have a letter from Kotori no Mama."
"Hello, Hinata-san! Ko-Niigo!"
Ko-Niigo!
"My child and I enjoy playing ProSeka together."
"Mizuki-chan's banner was incredibly cute, interesting, and moving."
"Through their past experiences and interactions with those around them,"
"I'm glad we got to see so many of Mizuki-chan's different feelings."
"I think staying true to yourself and not giving up on what you love can be hard when you face obstacles."
"But I believe that if you hold onto those feelings, a time will come when they are rewarded."
"Just like the members of Niigo, there are definitely people out there"
"who will see and accept you for who you truly are."
"I really love the stories in ProSeka."
"Hinata-san, thank you so much for always voicing them."
"I'll continue to support both you and Mizuki-chan with all my heart."
"Thank you so much, Kotori no Mama."
"In this story, Mizuki's sister comes home from abroad."
"It starts with the pop-up shop, and I felt it was a huge step forward for Mizuki to want their sister to meet the rest of Niigo."
"Kanade and Mafuyu had met Yuuki-san before,"
"but Ena met her for the first time here. The story really progressed in many ways."
"There was a lot of development."
"Mizuki loves making videos, but they also love things like"
"remaking clothes, visiting boutiques, and looking at makeup. They have so many things they love."
"So, when it comes to what they want to do in the future, thinking about what they want to aim for..."
"I think it's amazing that they're already facing those questions at this stage."
"When I was going to college, I just thought that if I was paying for it,"
"I had to study something that would give me a practical skill. I spent all my time at open campuses thinking like that."
"So, my approach to finding what I liked was completely different from Mizuki's."
"Even so, I think this was a time for Mizuki to re-examine what they love,"
"at their own pace. That's such an important thing to do."
"It wasn't just about their sister's pop-up shop."
"Being around those clothes helped them realize that it's not just a hobby—they might want to make it their career."
"Realizing that is a huge deal, so I was just really happy to see them smiling."
"All right, I've picked out some scenes that I personally wanted to talk about,"
"so let's take a look at them together."
"Here they are."
Wonderful.
Such a good story.
It's a really good story.
"That's how I feel about it."
"Since I'm someone who has already chosen my own career path,"
"witnessing the moment someone else makes a choice—"
"even if it's just through an event story—really resonates with me."
"There are always moments where you wonder if you're making the right choice. But if 10 or 20 years from now,"
"you can look back and think, "I'm glad I made that choice back then," then it was definitely worth it."
"I think that feeling comes from the effort you put in. When it comes to things that require hard work,"
"I don't think there's really a "right" or "wrong" choice."
"With a choice that involves real effort, you might think a year or two later,"
"Oh, I shouldn't have done this."
"But looking at it over 10 or 20 years, I'm sure there are times"
"where it all connects in the end."
"You'll think, "If I hadn't done that then, I wouldn't be able to do this now.""
"Even if you're in a different profession, I think you'll feel that way."
"So for any kids out there who are working hard or have something they want to work toward, please keep at it."
"I hope this event story serves as a catalyst for you to make that decision for yourself."
"Now then, let's talk about the illustrations."
"First, let me read a letter."
"This one is from Meshi-san. Thanks for writing in."
"Thank you very much."
"Hello, Sato-san. Kon-Niigo!"
"I'm always having fun playing ProSeka."
"The 4-star illustrations this time, especially Mizuki's, were so good that I went all out on the gacha to get them."
"Just like the trained illustrations for 'Secret Distance' and 'Where Shall This Path Lead?',"
"Where?"
"Where Shall This Path Lead?"
"Mizuki was shown in a space filled with torsos."
Torsos appear quite often in Mizuki's illustrations.
They're like mannequins for displaying clothes.
Like the one right here... here... here... oh, here!
Right here.
"This is called a torso."
"It's the torso from "Reaching Out for an Unraveling Tomorrow.""
"It was an illustration of Mizuki in a space with torsos."
"Usually, the torso space represents Mizuki's dark feelings,"
"but this time, after feeling the warmth of family and friends, they're looking forward."
"The space now represents Mizuki's bright and cheerful feelings."
"I was so happy to see this change in Mizuki's state of mind."
"I can't thank the staff enough for creating such wonderful illustrations and scenarios,"
"and the voice actors for their amazing performances that bring such depth to the characters."
"Thank you for always creating such wonderful events."
"Please take care of yourselves and keep up the good work."
"I'll be rooting for you as a fellow Tofu."
That's what they wrote.
"Thank you, Meshi-san."
"Yeah, the colors in the illustrations are quite rare for Niigo, aren't they?"
"We've had pale colors before, but seeing Niigo bathed in sunlight..."
"I mean, they don't go outside much to begin with,"
"so seeing Niigo during the day felt very fresh to me."
"Usually, we don't see this kind of touch very often."
"But everyone's cards were great, not just Mizuki's—both before and after training."
"It made me realize what amazing artists we have."
"I'm truly grateful. And actually,"
"we've received comments from the illustration team regarding the outfits this time,"
"so I'd like to share those as well."
"Oh, there's a comment about it too."
"Someone said, "Pure cuteness is rare, isn't it?""
"Mizuki, having been accepted by Niigo, wants to create clothes that can help children who have similar worries,"
"or children who can't bring themselves to like who they are."
"Inspired by the story of Mizuki thinking about a future career in fashion,"
"we wanted to express the image of the future they're starting to envision—a future that's finally coming into view."
"So, we went with a simple and clean one-piece design with fewer gothic elements."
"As a special touch, we included the yellow daisy embroidery used in Mizuki's previous unit outfit."
"This carries the message of 'being true to yourself,'"
"resulting in a simple outfit design that is uniquely Mizuki."
"Also, to reflect the song's calm, warm impression and Mizuki's faint expectations for the future,"
"we used a palette of soft, gentle colors."
That's what they said.
I see.
It's true that the colors are soft for everyone across the board.
So that's why.
"Did everyone notice the daisies? They're in there!"
The daisies are there.
Oh, I see people commenting "Daisy, daisy" now.
Right.
Yeah.
The blue traffic light was really striking.
That's true.
And since Mizuki was born in summer, on August 27th... Happy Birthday!
I didn't mean to say it so casually, but Happy Birthday to them.
Even though they're a summer baby, I feel like they haven't had
"that many summer-themed illustrations until now."
"I always felt like they usually wore long sleeves or clothes that covered their skin,"
"though they've had things like T-shirts before."
"So I was really happy to see an illustration that feels so refreshing and screams "summer" the moment you look at it."
"All right, then, let's talk about the event while looking at the card illustrations."
"I'm appearing on the monitor right now, right? On everyone's screens?"
"Yes, I'll believe that I am."
"First, let's look at Mizuki's pre-training card."
Here it is.
I absolutely love this illustration.
First of all, seeing Ena looking at Mizuki with such a happy smile reminds me of the New Year's event,
where Yuuki-san gave a ribbon to a young Mizuki. It really overlaps with that scene.
And Mizuki's expression here, showing it off and asking "How is it?", is just incredible.
I can't believe this is just the pre-training art.
Seriously.
"I love the atmosphere of this space."
"Apparently, that's a torii gate in the background."
All right, let's take a look at the post-training version too.
Here it is.
So good.
Butterflies and ribbons have always felt very symbolic for Mizuki,
but in my mind, when those motifs appear in illustrations,
I usually have a strong image of Mizuki holding scissors.
But this time, there are no scissors. It's such a bright space, and even though their mouth is covered, you just know they're smiling. It's so precious.
Really.
My kid is such a good kid, honestly.
Next up is Ena-chan.
I'm so happy Yuuki-san is here too.
Meeting the older sister for the first time and being overwhelmed by how pushy she is...
That "Whoa!" reaction from Ena is just great.
Ena is just so good here.
Isn't she?
If you haven't read the event story yet, please check it out in-game.
Seeing the sister interact with all the siblings is definitely a must-see.
Next... isn't this Ena amazing?
"I've always thought girls with flowers in their hair look great,"
"so this illustration is incredibly good."
"I almost thought she was a florist."
Wonderful.
Ena-chan.
So cute.
The way she's looking down slightly is also very nice.
Ena is just so cute.
Next is Len-kun.
How cute! Seeing him eating the souvenirs from his sister is just adorable.
Really cute.
What is this level of cuteness?
Even if that were a protein bar, he'd still be cute.
I just want him to be eating something forever.
Thank you.
"Next is the post-training version."
Isn't this insane?
"I thought it was insane."
Only you could pull this off.
"I thought, "Wow, he really suits short pants.""
Truly beautiful.
Thank you.
"I just felt so thankful."
"The overall taste is quite rare for Niigo, which is nice."
Is he holding a book about daisies?
Probably.
"My knowledge of daisies is a bit shallow, but I'm pretty sure that's what it is."
Yeah, it's great.
The idea of "sharing delicious things" is so lovely.
Everything tastes better when you share it.
And then, there's this.
Kanade-chan.
Way too cute.
These clothes look exactly like something Mizuki or Yuuki-san would pick out.
Especially around here.
She looks a little troubled too.
Of course it suits her!
Setting aside where she'd actually wear this...
I mean, it's Kanade.
I'm not sure if she'd actually wear that headpiece when she occasionally goes out.
But it suits her.
"If it looks good, I think she should wear it."
"Wow, she's really cute."
"Thanks for always being so cute, everyone."
"And here's the post-training version."
"She looks like a proper young lady from a good family."
"Are these daisies too?"
"The ones on her chest and head probably are."
"In the side story, Kanade-chan is so cute being made to try on all these different clothes, so please check that out too."
"Everyone's saying how cute they are."
They really are adorable.
Aren't they great?
It really hits home how rare it is to see Niigo wearing white.
Having done so many of these AfterTalks now...
Mafuyu-san...
Man, I have to say,
it might not be a full-on smile,
but seeing a version of Mafuyu with so much warmth makes me so happy.
Because the event story itself was so heartwarming,
"I think it's wonderful how all the illustrations have this gentle warmth to them."
Just wonderful.
"Thank you so much."
"And that wraps up our card illustration segment."
"Next, we're going to talk about the new song written for this event by Onuma Parsley,"
""Envy Baby," while we watch the 3DMV together."
"But before we watch the 3DMV, I actually have a comment"
"from the Sega 3DMV production team to share with you all."
"In the 3DMV for 'Envy Baby,' we used the visual of falling underwater to represent Mizuki's wavering emotions and the feelings they can't quite express to the other members."
""We utilized the insert feature and dedicated a lot of time to the underwater falling sequence,"
"going through a lot of trial and error to get the expression just right.""
""While we still face challenges in fully depicting a character's inner psyche,"
"we hope you enjoy this new style of expression through Mizuki.""
"That's what they had to say."
"Now then, let's take a look at the 3DMV right away."
Here it is.
Did you see that expression just now?
They were smiling.
"It's so good."
Wow, that was wonderful.
Honestly, I was blown away when I first saw the MV for "Consilium."
I was like, "I can't believe the scenery changes this much!"
Like, it goes from a school-like setting to an after-school vibe, with shots through windows showing leaves...
And when they're walking down the hallway, you see those little things floating in the light.
No, it's not Wi-Fi signals.
What would you call it?
Like, not exactly dust, but you can see little particles in the air.
The direction is so detailed, I kept wondering how they even did that.
It was really, really amazing.
"And the way everyone spins around and the characters swap out... the direction was just incredible."
"I loved it."
"It's great that we can look back at it like this."
"It's so good, and the 2DMV is also fantastic, so I want you all to see that too."
Regarding the 2DMV...
Well, this is just my personal take,
and since it hasn't been officially stated, I'm not entirely sure, but...
In the 2DMV, Mizuki is sitting at a table with a cake, like a birthday seat,
and the camera pans across things that symbolize Mizuki.
You see things like the letter from their sister, clothes,
ribbons, and stuff like that appearing.
The 2D version was really lovely too.
Both were amazing.
I was surprised by how much information was packed in there.
"Also, about the song... I feel like Mizuki's songs usually have a lot of painful lyrics."
"I'm not trying to compare it to past songs, but I felt this one had a lot of very positive lyrics."
"Even so, I still feel like Mizuki hasn't fully opened up yet, and there are still swirling emotions inside."
"So, I consulted with the director about the nuances, like how much weakness"
"or strength we should add or subtract. We talked a lot while creating this song."
"For the parts that sound like a radio broadcast,"
"we discussed whether to put a lot of emotion into it or try making the voice a bit raspy."
"We consulted on many of those subtle nuances for this track."
"I hope you enjoy both the full 2DMV and the 3DMV where Mizuki smiles at you."
"Both are already uploaded to the official ProSeka YouTube channel,"
"so please go check them out."
"Well then, although it was a short time,"
"this concludes the ProSeka AfterTalk for the "Reaching Out to an Unending Tomorrow" edition."
"To everyone watching the stream, how did you like it?"
"Let me take a look at the comments for a bit."
Hmm.
"The atmosphere of Oonuma Parsley-san's MV and Niigo's 2D version were different, but both were great."
That's so true.
For Mizuki, how should I put it?
Well, students have their career paths, and ProSeka is about to reach its 5th anniversary.
Mizuki has been through a lot leading up to the 5th anniversary, but they're looking forward now.
It shows that this happened, which allowed them to look forward,
"and that feeling of "I'm going to do my best" is summarized there."
"I think the Niigo version feels like it's decorated with those feelings."
"As for Oonuma-san's version, how should I describe it?"
"It's like an MV where a tired working adult is encouraging themselves to keep going and look ahead."
"I felt that "Consilium" is a song with a very wide range depending on the singer and how it's expressed."
"So please, check out Oonuma-san's... would you call it a 2D version?"
"What would you call that?"
The music video?
"I hope you enjoy that MV as well."
"Looking back at the event story, Niigo stories have often been heavy or focused on suffocating situations."
"But I think this story is one that high schoolers—from first to third years—"
"can really relate to on a personal level."
"It's an event story that feels very true to life."
"Whether it's deciding on a career path, or lacking confidence in your own interests... if there's anyone who feels they can't love what they like right now,"
"and that goes for working adults too, not just students... if you haven't seen the story or heard the song yet,"
"I think you'll find words that resonate with you exactly because of who you are right now."
"So, I hope everyone, both adults and students, enjoys it to the very end."
"If you haven't finished the story for "Reaching Out to an Unending Tomorrow," you can read it all from the event story archive once the next event starts."
"It will probably be uploaded to YouTube at a later date as well,"
"so it's perfectly fine to wait for that."
"AfterTalk is always looking for your messages."
"You can submit them through the AfterTalk submission channel on the official ProSeka Discord,"
"or via email."
"Please send them in once the next AfterTalk event begins."
"We look forward to your messages regarding the event."
"Well, August is almost over, and once September passes, the Thanksgiving festival awaits."
"We've been busy making preparations here and there,"
"so I'd be happy if you look forward to that too."
"August is ending, but..."
"The heat isn't letting up yet, so please be careful not to get heatstroke."
"If you feel like it's too much, please don't hesitate to get away from it."
Let's all escape the heat.
"Moving forward is what matters most."
"I hope to see you all at the Thanksgiving festival."
"We'll be waiting for you, whether you're watching the stream or at the venue."
"Thank you so much for watching until the very end."
"Let's survive this summer together, and I'll see you all again soon."
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Mafuyu Asahina.
12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031323334353637383940414243444546474849505152535455565758596061626364656667686970717273747576778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899.
123456789101112131415161718192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404142434445464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899.