プロセカアフタートーク、ほどけぬ明日に手を伸ばしてひとイエWelcome to ProSeka AfterTalk for the event "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow."
皆さんこんばんは。Good evening, everyone.
"25時ナイトコードで暁山瑞希役の佐藤日向です。I'm Hinata Sato, the voice of Mizuki Akiyama from Nightcord at 25:00."
"このプロセカアフタートークは皆さんから頂いたおたよりを紹介しながらイベントを振り返る配信となっております。ProSeka AfterTalk is a stream where we look back on the event while reading the fan letters you've sent in."
"え、今回はほどけぬ明日に手を伸ばしてひととなっています。This time, we're focusing on "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow.""
"皆様ストーリーはお楽しみいただけましたでしょうか。I hope you all enjoyed the story."
"ちょうどね、昨日までやっていたイベントなんですけれどもどうでしたかね、The event actually just ended yesterday. How was it for all of you?"
みんな。I'd love to hear your thoughts.
楽しんでくれてたらいいなと思うですけれども、I really hope you all had a good time with it.
結構ね、あの25瑞希自身が将来何をしたいかっていう未来に向けてこう向き合う、It was a story where Mizuki really had to face the future and think about what they want to do,
あの、お話になっていたんじゃないかなと思うので、so I think it was quite a significant chapter.
"もしかしたらね、あの進学とか進路とか決めなきゃいけない時のことかはなんかちょっと刺さる部分があるストーリーになっていたんじゃないかななんていう風に思います。For those of you who have to decide on your education or career path, there might have been parts that really hit home."
"はい、え、4月からアフタートークがプチリニューアルしまして、Also, AfterTalk got a bit of a renewal starting in April,"
"事前にプロプロセカ公式Discordとメールにてアフタートークのおたよりを募集させていただきました。and we've been collecting messages in advance via the official ProSeka Discord and email."
"皆さんおたより送っていただいてありがとうございます。Thank you so much to everyone who sent one in."
"え、皆さんから頂いたおたよりを番組内で紹介させていただきますのでお楽しみに。I'll be sharing some of those messages during the show, so please look forward to that."
"またイベントやこの配信放送をね、え、感想していただく感傷感想つぶやいていただく場合はハッシュタグプロセカアフタートークでポストしてください。If you want to share your impressions of the event or this stream, please post using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk."
"え、YouTubeのチャットも見ていますし、え、ハッシュタグも後ほどさせていただきますので、I'm keeping an eye on the YouTube chat and I'll check the hashtag later too,"
"え、気になるコメントどんどん拾っていこうかなと思います。so I'll try to pick up any comments that catch my eye."
"思ったよりね、海外のコメントばっかりでね、あの、日本語のコメントが全然見当たらないんですけれどもリボン可愛いとか瑞希とお揃いの髪形で可愛いとかあ、Wow, there are so many international comments! I can barely find the Japanese ones. People are saying "The ribbon is cute" or "Your hair matches Mizuki's, so cute.""
"今のターンちょっとまだ配信がね、多分遅れてるから、Since the stream is probably on a bit of a delay,"
"あの、髪形と服のことに触れてくれてますね。everyone is just now noticing my hair and outfit."
"今日、今回はね、あの、ちゃんと、あのイラスト意識して今回はてかいつもですけど。I tried to match the card illustration for today's look—well, I always do, actually."
"イラスト意識してきました。I definitely had the illustration in mind."
"こんばんは、こんばんは皆ありがとうございます。Good evening! Thank you all for joining."
"あ、ストーリーも描き下ろし楽曲も良くて号泣しました。Oh, someone said, "The story and the new song were so good I bawled my eyes out.""
"曲のこと後ほど触れます。I'll talk more about the song later."
"私ももうね何ですかあれはって家で言いましたよ。When I heard it at home, I was like, "What is this?!""
何ですかこれはって。I was just stunned.
"なんかすごい、あの、企業努力を感じました。I really felt the incredible effort the team put into it."
"はい、はい、はい、そんな話は後でさせていただこうかなと思います。Anyway, I'll save that talk for later."
"え、それではね、早速今回のほどけぬ明日に手を伸ばしてのストーリーについてお話ししていこうと思います。So, let's dive right into the story for "Reaching Out to an Unraveling Tomorrow.""
"え、皆さん今回のストーリーについてもね、おたよりいただいてますので、We've received letters about this story as well,"
"え、紹介しながら一緒にストーリーを振り返っていけたらなと思います。so I'd like to look back on the events while reading them."
"まずね、え、小鳥のママさんから頂いたおたよりです。First, we have a letter from Kotori no Mama-san."
"え、ひなつさんこんにごです。"Hinatsu-san, Kon-Niigo!""
こんにご。Kon-Niigo!
"え、親子でプロセカ楽しませてもらっています。"My child and I both enjoy playing ProSeka together.""
"さよしの瑞希ちゃんバナー最高に可愛くて面白くて感動しました。"Mizuki-chan's banner event was incredibly cute, funny, and moving.""
"今までの体験や周りの人達との関わりで、"Through her past experiences and her interactions with those around her,""
"え、瑞希ちゃんの様々な思いに触れられることができて良かったと思っています。"I'm glad we got to see so many of Mizuki-chan's different feelings.""
"自分らしく自分の好きなものを諦めないで続けていくことって迷ったり壁に当たったり大変なことだと思います。"I think staying true to yourself and not giving up on what you love can be hard when you face doubts or walls.""
"それでもその思いを持ち続けていればいつか報われる時が来ると思っています。"But I believe that if you hold onto those feelings, a time will come when they are rewarded.""
"25のみんなのようにありのままの自分を見てくれている人、"Just like the members of Niigo, I believe there are always people out there""
"認めてくれる人ってのは、絶対いると思っています。"who will see and accept you for who you truly are.""
"プロセカのストーリー本当に大好きです。"I really love the stories in ProSeka.""
"ひなつさんいつも声をあげてくださり本当にありがとうございます。"Hinatsu-san, thank you so much for always providing her voice.""
"これからも瑞希ちゃんとひなつさんを全力で押させていただきます。"I'll continue to support both Mizuki-chan and Hinatsu-san with all I've got!""
"ということで小鳥のママさんありがとうございます。Thank you so much, Kotori no Mama-san."
"いや、今回はまずお姉ちゃんが海外からお家に帰ってきてくれるっていうのは、In this story, it starts with Mizuki's sister coming home from abroad to open a pop-up shop."
"そのポップアップショップをやるっていうのところから始まって、その25のみんなとお姉ちゃんをに会ってもらいたいって瑞希が思ってることがすごく瑞希にとってはまず前進だなと私はすごく思いましたし、Mizuki wanting her sister to meet the rest of Niigo felt like a huge step forward to me."
"あの、これまでね、あの、奏とまふゆは奏さんに会ったことあったけど、Kanade and Mafuyu had met her before,"
"絵名がね、今回初めて会えたりとか、いろいろね、but Ena finally got to meet her this time, so the relationships are really progressing."
"あのお話も進んでいたりはするんですけど、The story moved forward in a lot of ways,"
"やっぱ中でもま、なんか瑞希が今好きでやってることって動画を作ることもそうだけど、but above all, Mizuki has so many things they love doing right now, like making videos,"
"そのお洋服をリメイクしたりとか、お洋服屋さん見に行ったりとか、remaking clothes, visiting boutiques, and looking at makeup."
"コスメ見たりとかそういう好きなことがいっぱいある子だからこそ、Because they have so many passions,"
"じゃ、それを自分が将来何かをするってなった時に自分が目指したいものって何だろうってこの時点で向き合えてるのってすごいなと私は思っていてもうね、I think it's amazing that they're already facing the question of what they want to aim for in the future."
"私なんて大学行く時なんてお金払うんだったらちゃんと手に職がつけられる手元に残るものを勉強しなければ意味がないと思いながらオープンキャンパスをひたすら回ってたもんだから、When I was looking at colleges, I just thought, "If I'm paying for this, I need to study something that gives me a practical skill," and I just went to tons of open houses."
"なんか結構瑞希とは入り方、好きなものの探し方の入り方が全然違うななんていう風にね、My approach to finding what I liked was completely different from Mizuki's."
"思ってたんですけど、そんな中でなんかこうゆっくりではありつつ瑞希のスピードではありつつ自分の好きを見つめ直すことができる時間だったと思いますし、But I think this was a vital time for Mizuki to re-examine what they love at their own pace."
"それってすごく大切なことだなと私は思ったのでなんかこう瑞希にとってお姉ちゃんが出したポップアップショップだけじゃなくて、It wasn't just about the sister's pop-up shop; it was about realizing that fashion isn't just a hobby,"
"そのお洋服に触れることが自分の中でそれがただの好きじゃなくて好きを職にしたいかもしれないって思えることって結構大きいことだなと思うのでなんか笑ってくれて良かったなと私は思いました。but something they might want to turn into a career. That's a huge realization, and I'm just so glad Mizuki could end it with a smile."
"はい、ということでね、え、今回も私が個人的に語りたいシーンをピックアップさせていただきましたので一緒に見ていけたらと思います。All right, I've picked out some scenes I personally wanted to talk about, so let's watch them together."
"こちらです。Here they are."
はい。Okay.
7話ですね。This is from Episode 7.
ま、正確に言うと6話と7話に登場するお話なんですけどやっぱ6話に登場したこの洋服着たいけど似合わないしなって悩んでる女性がどこかこう引っかかる瑞希がいての7話だ。Well, technically it spans Episodes 6 and 7. In Episode 6, there's a woman who wants to wear these clothes but worries they don't suit her. Mizuki can't stop thinking about her, which leads into Episode 7.
私がこんなの着てもな。"Even if I wore something like this..."
もしかしたらそれだけじゃないのかも。"Maybe it's not just that."
え?"Huh?"
一緒に行こうショップ回れてないですよね、ミク達と。They're going around the shops together, right? Mizuki and Miku and the others.
あのすみません。"Um, excuse me."
え?"Yes?"
"もしかしてあっちのワンピース気になってました?"Were you interested in that dress over there?""
すみません。"Oh, sorry."
これが言えるのって結構深いだと思いますよ、Being able to say that is actually quite profound,
"私は。I think."
深いよ、天才ですよ。It's deep. They're a genius.
うちの子僕達はもう見終わったので、"We're already done looking, so..."
どうぞ。"Please, go ahead."
うちの子とか言うとお前の子じゃないとか言われそうだからあれですけど、If I call them "my kid," people might say "they're not your kid," so I should be careful,
"うちの子と私は認識しております。but in my mind, they're my kid."
"私はここで見てるだけで十分なので。"I'm perfectly happy just watching from here.""
ねえそうなんですよ。Right, exactly.
このストーリーも良かったよね。This story was so good too.
正月でしたっけ?Was this during New Year's?
気がする。I think so.
昔の僕にIt reminds me of my past self.
よければこちらご試着だけでもしてみませんか?"If you'd like, would you care to just try this on?"
お姉ちゃんBig sister!
お姉ちゃんなんすよ、やっぱり。She really is the best big sister.
お姉ちゃんBig sister...
試着ですか?"Try it on?"
突然すみません。"Sorry to bother you so suddenly."
もしこのワンピースに興味を持っていただけたのならこういう話しかけ方ならいいのにって思っちゃうもんね。If you're interested in the dress, you'd wish someone would approach you like this, wouldn't you?
あ、いや。"Oh, no..."
って言われると思うな。I feel like that's what they'd say.
"かけられて嫌だなって思っちゃうタイプ私は。I'm the type who gets a bit uncomfortable when approached."
"すみませんって言うじゃないすか。You end up just saying "Sorry," right?"
アウトレットLike at an outlet mall.
30%オフって言ってると時々して、あ、これ話しかけられたらどうしよってなる。When they're shouting "30% off!" I sometimes worry, "Oh no, what if they talk to me?"
"これはすごく個人的な話なんですけど実はこのワンピース私がデザインしたものなんです。"This is a very personal story, but I actually designed this dress myself.""
"可愛いものが好きな人に届いたらいいなって思って。"I made it hoping it would reach someone who loves cute things.""
"なのでもし可愛いって思ってもらえたのなら試着していただくだけでもとても嬉しいなと。"So if you think it's cute, I'd be so happy if you'd just try it on.""
"私がめちゃくちゃ佑希さん素敵だなって思うのがちょっと自分の似てるとこに近い部分を持ってくださったりとか、What I find so wonderful about Yuki-san is how she brings parts of herself that are similar to the character,"
"私が可愛いっての時に開ける隙間とかもしかしたら意識してくださってるのかもって芝居の随所に感じられるのでなんかいつかお姉ちゃんともアフタートーク出たいですね。and I can feel through her acting that she's conscious of the space I leave when I say something is "cute." I'd love to do an AfterTalk with "Big Sister" someday."
あ、素敵。Oh, that's lovely.
お姉ちゃんからの言葉で励まされてる人間近で見るの2人目ですからね、That's the second person I've seen up close being encouraged by her words,
自分も含めたら。including myself.
では試着室にご案内しますね。"Then, let me show you to the fitting room."
あの、お客さん試着してくれることになって良かったね。"I'm glad that customer decided to try it on."
そうだね。"Yeah."
瑞希さっきはありがとう。"Mizuki, thanks for earlier."
え?"Huh?"
あの、お客さん前もお店に来てくれたことあるんだ。"That customer has actually been to the shop before."
でもずっと試着をためらってたみたいだったからいいよ、"But she always seemed to hesitate about trying things on."
お姉ちゃんよ。She's such a good sister.
声をかけたりすると逆にプレッシャーになっちゃいそうな感じもあってこういうきっかけでもないと話しかけられなかったと思う。"I felt like calling out to her might put too much pressure on her, so I don't think I could've talked to her without a chance like this."
なるほどね。I see.
そうだったんだ。So that's how it was.
ね。Yeah.
きっといろんな事情があるんだろうけど"I'm sure she has her reasons,"
気に入ってくれたらいいな。"but I hope she likes it."
あなんかめっちゃあ兄弟なんだなって感じられていいですよね。It's nice how you can really feel their sibling bond here.
7話めっちゃ好きなんですよ。I really love Episode 7.
"どうされました?"Is something wrong?""
"えっと、そのとても可愛いし特に問題はなかったんですけど"Um, well, it's very cute and there's no problem, but...""
"もしよければ外の鏡で見てみませんか?"If you'd like, why don't you take a look in the mirror outside?""
靴もご用意してるので。"I've prepared some shoes as well."
"ああ、わかりました。"Oh, okay.""
ああ、Ah...
可愛い。So cute.
大きな鏡の方にご案内しますね。"I'll lead you to the large mirror."
"こちらです。"Right this way.""
"お姉ちゃんのこの服好きなんですよね、私服衣装。I really like Big Sister's outfit here, her casual clothes."
私服衣装。Her casual outfit.
私服?Casual?
とてもお似合いですよ。"It suits you very well."
そうですかね?"You think so?"
ええ。"Yes."
"デザインした身としてもとても嬉しいです。"As the designer, it makes me very happy.""
"なんだか不思議な気持ちです。"It's a bit of a strange feeling.""
不思議?"Does it feel strange?"
はい。"Yes."
見慣れないなさすぎて似合ってるかどうかはよくわからないんですけど。"I'm so unused to seeing myself like this, I can't tell if it actually suits me."
うん。Yeah.
でもずっとこういうのが着たかったんだなあって。"But... I've always wanted to wear something like this."
こう言ってもらえる服作れるっていいよな。It must be so nice to make clothes that make people feel that way.
可愛い服がお好きなんですか?"Do you like cute clothes?"
そうですね。"I do."
"ずっと憧れはありました。"I've always admired them.""
"でも小さい頃からずっと可愛い系のものって全然持ってなかったです。"But ever since I was little, I never owned anything cute.""
"そういうのが似合うとも思えなかったし自分に対して偏見持っちゃうとどっちかと言うとかっこ子って感じでそれで可愛いものが好きってなかなか言い出せなくて。"I didn't think they'd suit me, and I had this bias that I was more of a 'cool' type, so I could never bring myself to say I liked cute things.""
"1度だけ勇気を出して着てみた時があるんです。"There was one time I worked up the courage to wear one.""
"こういう可愛いワンピース。"A cute dress just like this.""
"そしたら友達にらしくないねどうしちゃったのって言われちゃって。"But my friend said, 'That's not like you at all. What's wrong?'""
じゃないんだよ。No, that's not it!
え、珍しい、それも似合うじゃん、だよ。The right answer is, "Oh, that's rare! It looks great on you too!"
正解はね。That's the correct response.
それはみんな気をつけてね。Everyone, please be careful about that.
こういうの。Saying things like...
らしくないねって。"That's not like you."
遠回しに似合わないねみたいに捉えちゃうから、人って。People take that as a roundabout way of saying it doesn't suit them.
でもなんかそれで心が折れちゃったっていうかめっちゃいいじゃん、It's like their heart just breaks. Even if you follow up with "It's actually cool,"
でも似合わないねとかそういう頭に褒めたらいいとかも違いますからね。praising them after saying it doesn't suit them doesn't fix it.
そういうことじゃないから。That's not how it works.
褒めたら貶してきてとかじゃないですからね。You can't just insult them and then try to compliment them.
そっか。"I see."
あの目はそういうことだったんだ。"So that's what that look in her eyes meant."
好きな服を着るのを否定されてらしいってはらしいっていうのこっちが勝手に思ってるの。Being told you shouldn't wear what you like because it's "not like you" is just someone else's opinion.
ステレオタイプを押し付けてるみたいなもんですから。It's like they're forcing a stereotype on you.
それでも"Even so..."
"だけどこのワンピースはすごく可愛くて着てみたらどんな感じなだろうってずっと頭から離れませんでした。"This dress was so cute, I couldn't stop thinking about what it would be like to wear it.""
なるほど。I see.
それで何回もお店に来てしまって。"That's why I kept coming back to the shop over and over."
そう思える服って素敵だよな。It's wonderful to find clothes that make you feel that way.
今日もお店に来てくださって。"Thank you for coming back today."
ん?"Huh?"
"お客様がそのワンピースを着たところを見られて私もすごく嬉しいです。"Seeing you in that dress makes me so happy too.""
"とても素敵な笑顔が見られたので。"Because I got to see such a wonderful smile.""
おお。Oh!
"もしお客様が可愛い服を着たいと思うのであればその思いを大事にしてほしいなって私は思います。"If you want to wear cute clothes, I think you should cherish that feeling.""
いい言葉。What beautiful words.
プロセカが掲げ掲げてるメインテーマみたいなもんですよね、That's basically the main theme of ProSeka, isn't it?
思いていうのは。The power of your "feelings."
"やっぱり私は可愛いものが好きで年齢は関係ないですから、"I really do love cute things. Age doesn't matter...""
思いには。"...when it comes to how you feel."
嘘はつきたくないな。"I don't want to lie to myself anymore."
うん。Yeah.
"あのありがとうございます。"Um... thank you.""
"おかげで大事にしたい気持ちに気づけました。"Thanks to you, I realized what I want to cherish.""
"私は可愛いものがこの服がすごく好きなんだってこんなの作り手に言われたらもう嬉しいよ。Hearing someone say they love the clothes you made... as a creator, that's the best feeling."
作り手側に対してね。For the person who made it, I mean.
よくお似合いですよ。"It looks very good on you."
ああAh...
そっか。I see.
自分の作った服が誰かの背中を押したって感じた時たまらない気持ちになったんだ。When you feel like the clothes you made gave someone a little push, it's an overwhelming feeling.
ああ、Ah...
これはThis is...
すごく幸せなことだなって。This is such a happy thing.
きっとこの瞬間のことなんだ。It must be this exact moment.
お姉さんThat lady...
すごいね。She's amazing.
うん。Yeah.
本当に眩しいな。She's truly radiant.
僕もI want to...
僕もいつかこんな風にできたらうん。I want to be able to do something like this someday too.
素晴らしい。Wonderful.
いい話。What a great story.
本当にいい話。It's a really good story.
"って思います、私は。That's how I feel."
"自分がね、もう進路を選択した身ではあるからこそ、Since I've already chosen my own career path,"
"こう誰かが選択する瞬間みたいなのに、ま、witnessing the moment someone else makes a choice—even if it's through an event story—"
"立ち会うというか、ま、イベントストーリーという形でですけどっていう時にやっぱりなんかこうここで自分の選択合ってるのかなって思う瞬間って絶対あるからでもなんかそれが10年後20年後の自分にとってあの時この選択取って良かったなって思えてたらそれはきっとあれ、it reminds me that there are always moments where you wonder if you're making the right choice. But if you can look back in 10 or 20 years and think, "I'm glad I chose that,""
"いいことだと思うんですけど、そこに伴ってくるのってやっぱり努力だと思うので努力が必要なことに関しては選択に合ってる間違ってるも私はないなと思うので努力が伴った選択っていうのはきっと1年とか2年とかではね、then that's a good thing. I think effort is what makes it work. When it comes to things that require effort, I don't think there's a right or wrong choice. Even if after a year or two,"
"ああ、これやんなきゃよかったなってもしかしたら思う時が来るのかもしれないけど、you might think, "Maybe I shouldn't have done this,""
"10年20年って見た時にはそれがね、when you look at it over 10 or 20 years,"
"結果的にね繋がってる時も絶対あると思うし、I'm sure there are times where it all connects in the end."
"この時これやってなかったら今これできてないもんなとか、You'll think, "If I hadn't done that then, I wouldn't be able to do this now.""
"同じ職業じゃなくてもきっと思う事ってあると思うので、Even if you're not in the same profession, I'm sure you'll feel that way."
"今努力してるもの、努力したいものがある力は是非続けてもらったり、So if you have something you're working hard at or want to try, please keep going."
"あの、やるっていう決意をしてもらえるっていうきっかけになるイベントストーリーになっていたらいいなと私は思うイベントストーリーでございました。I hope this event story serves as a catalyst for people to make those decisions. It was a truly wonderful story."
"ということでね、え、ここからはイラストについてお話ししていこうと思います。All right, from here on, I'd like to talk about the card illustrations."
"ではおたより紹介させてください。First, let me read a fan letter."
"めしさん、めしさんからいただきましたおたよりです。This one is from Meshi-san."
"ありがとうございます。Thank you so much."
え、佐藤さんこんにご。"Hello, Sato-san! Kon-Niigo!"
"え、いつも楽しくプロセカをプレイさせてもらっています。"I'm always having a great time playing ProSeka.""
"え、今回の星4イラスト、特に瑞希イラストがとても良くて必死でガチャを回し手に入れました。"The 4-star illustrations this time, especially Mizuki's, were so good that I went all out on the gacha to get them.""
"今回のイラストもシークレットディスタンスや畦道の道はいずこへ、"Like the trained illustrations for 'Secret Distance' and 'Where Shall This Path Lead?',""
どこへ、いずこへ。"Wait, 'Where Shall This Path Lead?'..."
の、え、瑞希の特訓後イラストのようにトルソーの空間に、"Mizuki is shown in a space filled with torsos."
え、トルソーっていうのは結構瑞希のイラストでよく出てくるま、Torsos appear quite often in Mizuki's illustrations.
マネキンじゃないけど、お洋服着せるこういうやつ。They're not exactly mannequins, but those things you put clothes on.
あのここにある、ここにある、ここ。Like the one right here, right here...
ここ、ここ、あ、ここ、ここ。Here, here... oh, here!
"ここにある、これトルソーって言います。This thing right here is called a torso."
"ほどけぬ明日に手を伸ばしてトルソーです。It's the torso from 'Reaching Out for an Unbreakable Tomorrow'."
"え、トルソーの空間に瑞希がいるイラストでした。"Anyway, Mizuki was in a space with torsos again.""
"いつもは瑞希の暗い気持ちを表すものとなっていたトルソーの空間ですが、"Usually, the torso space represents Mizuki's dark feelings,""
"今回は家族や25、友達の温かさに触れて前を向いている、"but this time, it felt like a space representing Mizuki's bright, cheerful heart,""
"え、瑞希の晴れやかで明るい気持ちを表す空間になっていて、"looking forward after feeling the warmth of family, Niigo, and friends.""
"瑞希の心境の変化を感じとても嬉しく思いました。"I was so happy to see this change in Mizuki's state of mind.""
"こんなに素晴らしいイラスト、シナリオを作るスタッフさん、またこれらに深みを持たせるためキャラに寄り添い素晴らしい表現をする声優さん達には頭が上がりません。"I can't thank the staff enough for creating such wonderful illustrations and scenarios, nor the voice actors for their deep, empathetic performances.""
"いつも素敵なイベントを作4てくださりありがとうございます"Thank you for always creating such wonderful events.""
といただきましたThat's what the team said.
といただきましたThat's what they had to say.
。
え 、これからもお体に気をつけ頑張ってください"Please take care of yourselves and keep up the good work."
"25として応援しています。 といただきました"I'll keep supporting Niigo!" That's what they wrote."
。
"メシさんありがとうございますThank you, Meshi-san!"
、淡い色味は今までありましたけどWe've had pale colors before, but...
。
、なんか太陽光を浴びてる25を見れることSeeing Niigo bathed in sunlight is special.
いや 、イラストもね結構25だと珍しい色味というかなんかなんて言うんだろうThe colors in these illustrations are quite rare for Niigo, aren't they?
、ま 、あんま外に出ない子達だからっていうのもありますけどI mean, they don't really go outside much to begin with,
"、日中の25って珍しいなって私は思ってso seeing Niigo during the day felt very fresh to me."
、結構大体ねUsually, you don't see them like this.
、あの 、こういう達あんまりないなと思ったんですけどI thought it was a really nice touch.
、瑞希に限らず全員分良かったですからねAnd it wasn't just Mizuki; everyone looked great.
"、特訓前も特訓後も素晴らしい絵師がいるんだなと思いましたBoth the pre-trained and trained versions made me realize what amazing artists we have."
、え 、今回もねAnd this time,
、え 、イラスト制作チームから今回の衣装についてのコメントいただいておりますのでwe've received comments from the illustration team regarding the outfits,
、え 、そちらも紹介させてもらえたらなと思いますso I'd like to share those with you as well.
"、純粋な明るさって珍しいですよねと言います"Pure brightness is rare for them," it says."
、自分を好きになれない子の力になれるような服を作りたい"or children who can't bring themselves to like who they are."
、これから思い描いていく未来 、やっと少しずつ見えてきた自分の未来というイメージを表現したく"To show a future that's finally coming into view, we intentionally kept the elements minimal."
、え 、あえて要素が少ないシンプルかつ清楚なワンピースデザインにしています"We chose a simple yet elegant one-piece dress design."
。
いや 、本当ありがたいなと思ったんですけれどもI'm truly grateful for them.
、黄色いデイジーの刺繍を入れ
、え 、ありのまま"By including this, we wanted to convey a message of being true to oneself."
、自分らしさというメッセージ
、メッセージ性も乗せて
"、今回の瑞希ならではのシンプルな衣装デザインとしています"This resulted in a simple design that is uniquely Mizuki's.""
、え 、抱き
、抱き始めた瑞希の心情表現を表すように
、淡く 、優しい色合いでまとめました。"we used a palette of pale, gentle colors."
。
あ 、コメントでもありますねOh, I see a comment in the chat too.
え 、25に受け入れてもらえた瑞希が自分と同じように悩んでいる子やえ"Mizuki, having been accepted by Niigo, wants to create clothes that can help children who have similar worries,"
、そうなんだI see!
、デイジーもね 、入ってるんだって皆さん気づいDid you all notice that the daisy was included?
"、気づきましたDid you catch that?"
、デイジーってコメントがありますけどI see people commenting "Daisy" now.
。
、8月20on August 27th...
服飾系の仕事に就きたいという自分の将来を考えるストーリーから着想を得て 、え"Inspired by the story of Mizuki thinking about a future career in fashion, we wanted to express the image of a future they've started to envision."
、あ 、瑞希Oh, Mizuki,
、お誕生日おめでとうhappy birthday!
、誕生日おめでとうなんですけどbut happy birthday anyway.
、夏だけどEven though it's summer,
"、夏っぽいイラストって今まで結構そこまで多い方ではない子だなと私は思っていてだからこそI've always felt that Mizuki hasn't had many summer-themed illustrations until now."
、なんか長袖だったりとかThey usually wear long sleeves
、こうor clothes
"、肌を覆ってる服が多かったりとかするなあと私は思ってたんですけどthat cover up a lot of skin."
、ま 、TシャツとかありましたけどWell, there have been T-shirts and things like that,
、そういうのはof course.
"、一瞬見ただけで夏だなって感じられるイラストを見れるのは嬉しいなって私は思いましたねwhere you can instantly feel the summer vibe. It makes me really happy."
。
、それではねmoving on.
ワンポイントとして瑞希の新旧後のユニット衣装に用いていた 、え"As a special touch, we added the yellow daisy embroidery used in Mizuki's initial unit outfit."
、え 、カードイラストを実際に見ながらお話ししていけたらと思いますI'd like to talk about the card illustrations while we actually look at them.
、特訓前こちらHere is the pre-training version.
。
、幼い頃の瑞希にリボンを贈った佑希さんとすごく重なるなあと思っていてwho gave a ribbon to Mizuki when they were little during that New Year's event.
また 、楽曲のゆったりと落ち着いた温かな印象や未来への淡い期待を"Furthermore, to reflect the song's calm, warm impression and Mizuki's budding hope for the future,"
、でどうかなって見せてるこの瑞希の表情がめちゃくちゃいいんですよAnd Mizuki's expression here, showing her how it looks, is just incredible.
、映ってるの 、後ろに映ってるのが燈そうですけれどもAkito in the background there, right?
、はいYeah.
。
確かにね 、全体的にも全員通して淡い色合いにはなっているなと思うんですがIt's true, the overall color scheme for everyone is quite pale this time.
、ハサミをねusually involve them holding scissors.
、持ってるイメージが多かったんですけど 、今回ハサミを持たずすごく明るい空間でBut this time, there are no scissors, and they're in such a bright space.
?
デイジー入ってるってThe part about the daisy.
、こう口元隠してるけどこの笑ってるに決まってるじゃんっていう表情してくれてるのが愛おしいですねEven though their mouth is covered, you can just tell they're smiling. It's so precious.
。
あ 、デイジーAh, "Daisy!"
はい 。Right.
はいYeah.
、とってもReally.
。.
青い信号が印象的だったThe blue traffic light was really striking.
。 確かにねI agree.
。 なんか瑞希って夏生まれでMizuki was born in the summer,
、お姉ちゃんとね 、初めて会ってねthey're meeting the older sister for the first time,
、お姉ちゃんのグイグイにね 、ちょっとねand Ena is getting a bit overwhelmed by how pushy she is.
、ああ 、ってなってる絵名がいいんですよThat reaction is just great.
。 こんな雑談で言うつもりはなかったけどI didn't mean to just say it casually like this,
、またAgain.
、イベントストーリー内でもチェックしてほしいんですけどplease go check it out in the game.
、やっぱお姉ちゃんとねSeeing the sister
"、25全員が会話してるんでそこはね必見ですtalking with all of Niigo is a must-see."
、とんでもなくいいんですよis insanely good.
。 その中で結構爽やかでこうBut it's so refreshing to see an illustration
、お土産をねthe souvenirs from the sister
、食べてるともかわいいですよis just so cute.
。.
はい 、ということでAll right then,
。
これ今モニターに私映ってるよね 、みんなのモニターにはI'm appearing on the monitor right now, right? On everyone's screen?
そう 、信じていますYeah, I'll believe that's the case.
。
では 、まず瑞希からえFirst, let's start with Mizuki.
このねイラスト大好きI absolutely love this illustration.
。
、この辺は
まずお姉ちゃんがすごい嬉しそうににこにこ瑞希を見てるっていうのがお正月のイベントでね 、あのFirst of all, seeing the older sister smiling so happily at Mizuki reminds me so much of Yuki-san,
、奏がねI'm not sure if Kanade would really wear that headpiece
、たまに出かける時に本当にこの頭のやつつけるのかって言うとちょっとわかんないですけどwhen she occasionally goes out.
、これはもう
、きっとright?
、着て 、着てってさせられてる奏ちゃんもめっちゃかわいいのでgetting forced to try on all these different clothes.
。
特訓前とは思えないよねIt's hard to believe this is just the pre-training art.
"、サイドストーリーもぜひ見ていただけたらなと思いますI definitely recommend checking out the Side Story as well."
。
本当にSeriously.
"この空間が私は大好きですI love the atmosphere of this space."
。 これねAnd you can see
。
ということで 、特訓後も見ていきましょうAnyway, let's take a look at the post-training version too.
こちら 。Here it is.
いい 。So good.
非常に結構瑞希にとって蝶々だったりリボンだったりっていうのはすごく象徴的になってるなあと思ってたんですけど 、そういう時大体瑞希って私の中でイラストのイメージButterflies and ribbons have become very symbolic for Mizuki, but in my mind, those illustrations
"、こう全員に温かみがあるイラストが続いていて私はすごく素敵だなあと思いましたand I think it's wonderful how that warmth carries through into all of these illustrations."
、え 、続いてMoving on,
、え 、今回のイベントのためにwe'll be talking about the new song
、え 、大沼パセリさんに描き下ろししていただきましたwritten specifically for this event by Onuma Parsley.
、飾っての3MVを見てLet's watch the 3DMV for "Kazaratte"
"、楽曲についてのお話をしていこうと思いますand discuss the track."
、え 、3MV制作チームからコメントいただきましたので紹介させてくださいfrom the Sega 3DMV production team, so let me share that with you.
"、瑞希が他のメンバーに素直に言い出せない感情をテーマに揺れ動く気持ちを水中落下という演出で表現しています"we used a falling-into-water sequence to represent Mizuki's wavering emotions and the feelings they can't honestly share with the other members.""
、えon
。
、試行錯誤を重ね 、表現してきました"trial and error to bring this underwater scene to life."
うちの子いい子なんですよ 、本当My kid is such a good person, honestly.
。
続きまして 、絵名ちゃんNext up is Ena-chan.
また佑希さんがいてくれるのが嬉しいI'm so happy Yuki-san is in this one too.
。 このねIn this scene,
うんYeah.
うん うんYeah, yeah.
うん うんI see.
うん うんRight, right.
うん うんYeah.
うん うんMhm.
うん うんRight, right.
うんYeah.
うんRight.
うん うんI see.
うん うんRight, right.
うんYeah.
。
いいよなあIt's so nice.
ぜひ 、あのイベントストーリーまだ見てない方はIf you haven't seen the event story yet,
。
続きましてこの絵名さ 、やばくないNext, isn't this Ena incredible?
?
"やっぱ耳掛けしてる女の子っていいなあと私は思うんで 、このイラストねI think girls with their hair tucked behind their ears are great, so this illustration"
。
お花屋さんかと思ったもんねI almost thought she was a florist.
素晴らしい 、絵名ちゃんWonderful, Ena-chan.
。
かわいい 。So cute.
こう 、ちょっと伏し目がちなところもいいですねThe way she's looking down slightly is also nice.
。
絵名かわいいんですよEna is just so cute.
続きまして奏君Next is Kanade-kun.
。
かわいい 、このお姉ちゃんのねAdorable. Seeing her eating
本当にかわいいReally, really cute.
。
何このかわいいさWhat is this level of cuteness?
これがプロテインバーだとしてもかわいいもんねEven if that were a protein bar, she'd still be cute.
。 うんYeah.
うんYeah.
。
もうずっとなんか食べててほしいI just want her to be eating something forever.
。 ありがとうThank you.
。
続きまして 、特訓後ですNext up is the trained version.
これやばくないIsn't this incredible?
?
"私はやばいと思ったよI think it's absolutely stunning."
。
あんただけや 、ショートパンツが似合うのはと思いましたI was thinking, "Only you could pull off short pants like that."
本当に美しいShe's truly beautiful.
。
ありがとうThank you.
"ありがとうと思いましたI just want to say thank you for this."
。
なんか全体的に珍しい25のテイストでいいですよね 、本当にIt's a rare aesthetic for Niigo overall, which is really nice.
これもデイジーのお花の本を持ってるのかな 、きっとShe's probably holding a book about daisies here, right?
。
ちょっとデイジーのお花への知識というか造詣が浅すぎてあれですけれどもMy knowledge of daisies is a bit too shallow to say for sure,
"きっとそうだと思いますbut I'm sure that's what it is."
。
いや 、いいですねMan, this is great.
。 おいしいを分け合ってっていうのがいいですよねThe idea of "sharing something delicious" is so lovely.
。
分け合ったら何でもおいしいからねEverything tastes better when you share it.
で 、これよAnd then, look at this!
。
奏ちゃんKanade-chan!
かわいすぎるShe's way too cute.
。
でめっちゃ瑞希が選んだっぽい 、佑希さんが選んだっぽい服ですからねThis outfit looks exactly like something Mizuki or Yuki-san would pick out.
ちょっと困ってるしShe looks a little troubled, too.
。 似合うに決まってるでしょBut of course it looks good on her!
。
ま 、どこにつけていくかは置いておいてSetting aside where she'd actually wear it,
でも似合う 。But it suits her.
似合うなら着た方がいいし 、つけた方がいいって私は思いますIf it looks good, I think she should wear it!
。
いや 、本当にかわいいですねSeriously, she's so adorable.
みんないつもありがとう 、かわいくてThank you all for always being so cute.
。
"特訓後ですAnd here's the trained version."
もう 、いいとこのお嬢さんだよShe looks like a proper young lady here.
。 これもデイジーのお花なのでしょうかねI assume these are daisies too,
。
胸元と頭についているのはきっとそうThe ones on her chest and head surely are.
サイドストーリーでね 、そのお洋服いろいろ着てIn the Side Story, Kanade-chan is so cute
。
みんなかわいって言ってるEveryone in the chat is saying how cute she is.
マジでかわいいShe really is.
。
いいですよねIt's so good.
なんか25が白着てんのってやっぱ珍しいんだなあと思いますね 、ここまでいろいろアフタートークとかやらせていただいてDoing these AfterTalks makes me realize how rare it is to see Niigo in white.
。
真冬さんAnd Mafuyu-san.
いや 、いいWow, this is great.
。
ちょっとさShe's almost smiling.
微笑んでるまでいくかもだけど笑み成分が多い真冬っていうのは私すごい嬉しくてこう 、朗らかな気持ちになれるイベントストーリーだったからこそなんかSeeing Mafuyu with even a hint of a smile makes me so happy. This event story was so heartwarming,
。
いや 、素晴らしいWow, that was wonderful.
"ありがとうございましたThank you so much."
。
ということでね 、イラストコーナーではございましたがAnd that wraps up our card illustrations segment.
え 、3MVを見る前に今回はセガのBut before we watch the 3DMV, we actually received a comment
。
え 、飾っての3MVでは"In the 3DMV for 'Kazaratte',"
今回はインサート機能を一過し 、水中落下の演出には時間さんを先"We utilized the insert function and spent a lot of time"
。
まだまだ心情を描くまでの表現にするには課題もありますが 、新しい表現を瑞希を通して見ていただければ幸いです。"While there are still challenges in fully depicting such deep emotions, we hope you enjoy this new form of expression through Mizuki."
それではね 、早速3MVを見てみましょうAll right, let's take a look at the 3DMV right away.
。
どうぞ 。Here it is.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うんYeah
。
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 。
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah, yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
。 うんRight.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんうんMm-hmm, yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんRight.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 。...
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah, yeah.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんRight.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんRight.
。 うんI see.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんMm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんMm-hmm.
。 うんYeah.
。 うんRight.
。 うんI see.
。 うんYeah.
。...
うん 。Yeah.
うん うんYeah, yeah.
。...
うん 。Yeah.
うん うんYeah, yeah.
。...
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。I see.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんYeah.
。 。...
うん 。Yeah.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah, yeah.
。 うんYeah.
うん 。Yeah.
うん うんRight, right.
。 うんYeah.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんうんYeah, yeah.
。 うんYeah.
。 。...
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
。 。Right.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
。 。Right.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mm-hmm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
。 。...
うん 。Right.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah, yeah.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
。 うんYeah.
。Yeah.
うん 。Yeah.
。 。Yeah.
うんうん うんYeah, yeah, yeah.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Yeah.
うんRight
。.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
うん 。Right.
うん 。Yeah.
うん 。Mhm.
Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh, oh.
Oh,oh,oh. Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh.
oh,oh. Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Oh,ohoh. Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Oh,oh,oh. Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh.
Oh,oh,oh.Oh, oh, oh.
うんYeah.
。.