Hello, everyone.
Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk: At The End of The Unraveled Thread edition!
I'm Honnizumi Rina, the voice of Hinomori Shizuku from MORE MORE JUMP!
It's a pleasure to be here.
This ProSeka AfterTalk is a program where we'll look back on the event and enjoy the AfterLive together with everyone watching!
We'll be covering the 'At The End of The Unraveled Thread' story this time.
The event just finished a moment ago. How did you all like the story?
I have so much I want to talk about!
Wasn't it amazing?
That definitely was an eventful story, and I want to talk about all of it today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Feel free to post your thoughts on the event using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
The staff have set up the YouTube chat so I can see it right here,
so I'll be reading your comments as we go.
Also, they've given me a phone I can use to watch the story and illustrations with you all.
I'll also be personally using the phone for today's AfterLive,
so we can all join the same room and watch the show together.
I'll create a room ID right before the AfterLive starts, so we can all join at the same time.
You might need to switch devices or apps, so I'd appreciate it if you could get everything ready now.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Now, let's get into our lookback of the event.
We'll start with reviewing the 'At The End of The Unraveled Thread' event story.
I see comments like, "The entertainment industry is so scary."
I really felt that the way Shizuku faced her past was so cool when I first read the script.
The story really depicts the realistic behind-the-scenes side of things.
There were some quite painful scenes,
but because Shizuku faced them head-on without running away,
she was able to make everything work out well in the end.
I really want to tell Shizuku she did a great job!
I want to thank the other MORE MORE JUMP members too!
I'll go more in-depth about it later.
Right, I'd also like to watch one of the story episodes with everyone today.
Which episode should we do?
I'd like to see the... the main event?
The iHaz filming scene where MMJ and Cheerful＊Days go at it.
What do you think?
Maybe Episode 7 or 8?
I think that'd be—
What do you all think?
Yeah, we got to see a little more of Shizuku's past this time.
We've seen bits of her time in Cheerful＊Days before,
but this time we got to see the nitty gritty of what actually happened.
It's hard to choose, but maybe 7 or 8?
It looks like there are a lot of votes for 7.
Should we go with 7?
Is 7 okay with everyone?
Alright everyone, let's watch Episode 7 together.
Watching it with all of you makes it so much fun.
Episode 7.
Thank you so much, everyone.
I see everyone in the YouTube chat saying how emotional that was and cheering for Shizuku.
Thank you so much!
So...
we have to move onto the next part soon,
so I'll keep my thoughts brief for now, but...
Seeing Shizuku's past like that...
Shizuku is such a kind person.
She has such a strong will.
This scene really highlighted her strength in being able to say "thank you" face-to-face with Arisa like that.
To put all her feelings into words, and to have the courage to do it right in the middle of filming,
and being able to clearly express everything she wanted to say,
isn't Shizuku is the coolest person in the world?
I really just want to give her a hug.
I'm already hugging her in my heart.
She's just the best.
And while herself Shizuku didn't get angry, but Airi-chan got all fiesty in her place, didn't she?
That dynamic is just so good.
We got to see more of the intense idol business,
And speaking of Airi-chan, I have some thoughts on her role in all this too.
We'll get more into that later.
But for now, are you ready with your phones, everyone?
We'll be watching the 10PM AfterLive together in a bit.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad we got to watch that all together.
Ah~
My heart is just racing.
What did you think?
That was the new song for this event.
I think they previewed it a little during the last WonderShow Channel stream.
But that was super cool, wasn't it?
We've seen lots of different kinds of songs from MMJ so far,
and I feel like we get to see different emotions or facets of the group come out each time.
And so this was yet another kind of "coolness" we got to see.
Since this was an AfterLive, seeing it as a live performance with the costumes...
Everything came together and looked so cool.
And the way it went dark for a moment before the pre-chorus,
and then Len-kun came to the center...
I really loved the lighting in that part.
That was awesome.
Ah yeah, and the high notes were cool too.
Recording those was a lot of fun.
So speaking of recording for this song,
It's not just the theme, but I think...
In this story, Shizuku took yet another step deeper into her facing her struggles.
And for me,
seeing Shizuku get her wings and awaken... I felt this song has that kind of power.
That's what I thought when I first read the lyrics.
The lyrics are filled with so many emotions,
so I really wanted to express them with everything I had.
What we just showed you was the game-size version.
I hope we'll have the chance to share the full version with you, someday.
When you do listen to it,
there's a part at the end second verse, going into the chorus, where I almost feel like she's taking off flying!
I'd love it if you listen to that part and experience it for yourself.
Everyone wants to hear the full version!
But even in the game size version,
at the end of the chorus,
I think the "I having nothing left to fear" lyrics really touched everyone.
That was so good!
And then everyone waves like this, and the stage suddenly brightens up.
I thought that part...
was really nice!
Alright, thank you all so much for having fun watching the AfterLive with us!
The 3DMV was posted on the official ProSeka YouTube channel today at 10:10 PM.
Ah, it's already premiering!
Looks like It's already up, so please check it out.
Please watch it a lot.
Thank you so much.
And now,
let's take a look at the newly added card illustrations.
There are five cards for us to look at,
and they're all so cute!
Let's start by looking at Shizuku's.
Isn't this amazing?
This is the trained art.
It's like...
The large flower Shizuku is sitting on...
it kind of feels like it's made of stained glass.
I think that smooth glass-like texture looks really good.
It has a certain fleeting, almost fragile beauty to it.
Love it.
And this is the untrained.
I think this was the art that was previewed a bit (in the event Twitter anouncement).
A bit of Arisa was visible in the corner
I saw people posting about that a lot Twitter.
Like—
doesn't it make you go "Just who does she think she is?"
It does, doesn't it?
This art is just...
Looking at this one alone, Shizuku has such a cheerful expression.
But then Airi is going ">:(" while Arisa is walking away like ":/".
This shot alone is really funny,
but if you read the story you can understand what's going on here.
This is a great shot though.
Arisa is great, and Airi's expression...
I really like it.
Next is Minori.
Isn't she adorable?
Here's the trained art.
Super cute.
It's a total change from Shizuku's outfit, black and white with red accents.
And the leaf!
The way she's wearing the leaf on her head...
...is just so cute, right?
I called her a Korpokkur earlier.
She has kind of feels like a fairy, super cute.
And this is the untrained.
Snacking time.
So actually,
ProSeka recordings are just like this too, but in the green rooms staff always provide us with delicious food.
We got bento today too.
But yeah, having snacks laid out like this vis actually quite realistic.
Normally you're nervous before a show, but the snacks are so good you just nom away at them.
Oh yeah, definitely check out the side story for this card too.
It's really cute.
And next is Airi.
This is her trained art.
Her outfit is pretty similar to Minori's,
but the skirt is slightly different.
Airi has flowers spread out like a pannier. It's so cute.
I can't stop looking at it.
The droplets scattered around her make it feel like the rain just stopped.
And that feeling really reminds me of the story.
Here's the untrained.
This is another still from the story.
Airi's always worrying about Shizuku, isn't she.
She'll was checking on her like "Are you really okay with this?"
Shizuku tends not to speak up about stuff like this,
so Airi is always looking out for her.
She really is.
And Airi...
Without Airi, the Shizuku we know today wouldn't exist.
Even back in her Cheerful Days days, Airi...
Airi encouraged her so much during back when she was on QT.
You can really see their bond.
And then there's Haruka.
Her trained art is amazing.
That...
the frog there looks so surprised.
Isn't her expression just so cute?
Landing on the lilypad like that.
It's so good.
Haruka's outfit isn't just red, it has some orange in it too.
Very cute.
There's lots of subtle differences in the outfits.
That's really cool.
The lotuses also look really pretty.
And here's the untrained.
Is this the actual filming studio for AiHaza?
The background, the camera crew, the emergency exit sign in the back...
and by the door in the back,
you can actually see the emergency exit sign lit up.
And then the monitor in the bottom right under the camera.
It all feels so real!
It really looks exactly like this.
The perspective you have when standing in a studio with cameras.
Haruka here...
...looks so nervous, like she's right about to go on for the real thing.
This expression is so good.
The camera?
But it really is like this.
They're constantly filming different expressions from various angles...
...switching between cameras to create the screen...
...that everyone usually sees. So this is what it's like.
It's so realistic.
And finally, Meiko.
Meiko, you look so elegant.
This white... this white outfit is just...
But it suits her so well.
That's our Meiko.
She looks so mature.
It's wonderful.
Holding the flowers...
...she's so cute.
The way the sleeves flare out a bit is great.
And so...
Looking at this, I wanted to write that the group name got smaller...
...but because of the character limit, it just says "got small."
That happens sometimes.
What do you mean?
"The outfits are really cute!"
Yeah they are pretty simple, but—
Oh yeah yeah, I actually saw this comment from earlier.
They were talking about something they realized about all the outfits.
So when I first saw the illustration, I just like "oh look, she's like a fairy! Fufufu that's so cute!"
But that commenter said that this might be based on Thumbelina. Now, for me,
I've definitely heard of a fairy tale called "Thumbelina" before,
but I'd never actually read it.
So when I looked up what kind of story it was,
it's about a tiny girl born from a flower who gets named Thumbelina.
She gets kidnapped and faces all sorts of dangers.
She really goes through a lot of difficult things.
But in the very end, a swa... swallow?
A swallow saves her,
and she finds freedom in a happy ending.
And looking here...
Aren't these costumes like swallows?
The black and white...
Minori-chan, Airi-chan, and Haruka-chan.
When they pointed it out, they do look a bit like swallows.
The yellow on their chests looks like a beak.
Whoever noticed that is amazing.
I'm so glad they told me about that.
It really makes so much sense now.
It changes how I see the set. There's even a frog here.
There's a frog in Thumbelina too.
So it all clicks for me now.
That's really cool.
And the story of Thumbelina is about how if you don't give up,
you can make your dreams come true and be free.
I was like, "That's fits this story so well!"
Shizuku getting saved by the swallows,
and now she can spread her wings.
Doesn't that just hit the feels?
That's what I wanted to share. Thanks so much for telling me about that!
So that was everything for the "At The End of The Unraveled Thread" event.
The story, the art, everything came together so beautifully.
Thank you so much.
So actually, I really want to talk a bit about Arisa-chan now.
So from the premise of the story,
Shizuku and the Cheerful＊Days members clash quite a bit.
So, looking at Arisa-chan and the rest of the Cheerful＊Days girls from a certain perspective,
maybe you wouldn't call them villains per se,
but there were moments where you might go "grr" or "just who do they think they are?"
But you know,
Mei-chan mentioned it too, but they're all serious about being idols.
They were all after that center position Shizuku had.
They all worked incredibly hard.
That's why they get so genuinely jealous of her, and why they're so motivated to continue working.
So their feelings were pretty intense.
I feel like Arisa is someone who's really straightforward,
and so, Shizuku...
Right when she met Arisa and the other Cheerful Days members,
Arisa immediately went, "I'm going all out, so you'd better do the same."
She really wasn't hiding anything with those words of hers.
I thought that straightforwardness, always giving it her all, was really cool.
That being said...
when we saw in the story—
what was it...
when the other members went and hid Shizuku's outfit like that...
The way they went about it... wasn't the best way to handle it.
I'm not saying it's a bad thing to really want to be the center like that.
I completely understand being so driven that you start feeling like "damn it" towards others.
I'm definitely not perfect either, I struggle with this too.
It's just if you fixate on those feelings of jealously and let it control how you treat others,
really bad things can happen.
It's a really difficult thing!
It's just something you need to take time with and confront within yourself.
That "I won't lose" feeling can actually help motivate you,
and push you to improve yourself.
I strive for that myself.
I definitely feel that jealousy all the time though,
Like "ah, she must have it nice," or "damn it, why her?"
I really do. I'm serious.
Every single day, actually.
I really do get those feelings.
But on the other hand, Shizuku...
because the other girls all really wanted to become the center,
what Shizuku said hurt them.
Of course, she didn't say it out of spite. I think we all know that Shizuku's not that kind of person.
It's not that she had bad intentions.
She was just so overwhelmed with all the expectations at the time,
that she could only see what was right in front of her.
And that anxiety made her say that someone else might be better for the center.
It was heat of the moment.
I definitely understand that.
The pressure of being the center is insane.
Between all the expectations and having to keep up that persona...
Shizuku could't be her true self.
Plus she had to maintain that character everyone was expecting, which made it even harder.
That was part of it too.
This story was just... just too real.
It really was.
Way too real.
At such a sensitive, young age,
and on top of that, having to be chosen by someone else to succeed...
It's just cruel.
Working hard alone won't make you the center.
You need someone to recognize you and say, "You're the center."
That's what makes it so tough.
But I suppose that's exactly why they're able to shine so brightly.
I really felt that.
Looking at this scenario, I thought to myself...
"I really need to be careful."
But because of her past, we have the Shizuku we have now.
Without this, we wouldn't have MORE MORE JUMP!, and I'm so grateful for that.
Shizuku said "Thank you" too. Truly, thank you.
Arisa-chan also stuck to her guns until the very end.
Nothing she said was wrong.
Her actions might have been wrong,
but her words weren't wrong at all.
Even during the iHaz recording scene we just watched,
you might wonder why she'd press Shizuku so hard on a TV show,
but she pressed so hard knowing full well that the viewers wanted to see those deep conversations from idols.
All of that was to liven up the program.
She worked with the other Cheerful Days members like Marina-chan and Hina-dan to make it exciting.
You can really feel her dedication through that.
She's a true professional.
That was really tense, though.
Even I was so anxious, wondering how it would turn out.
But Arisa's not a bad person at heart.
She's just very straightforward, serious, and strict with both herself and others.
That what I wanted to talk about.
I ended up rambling quite a bit.
I'm glad I got to talk about all that.
And so...
When you're working really hard, your own camera tends to tunnel vision on just yourself.
You start to only see what's right in front of you.
When that happens, you need to pull the camera higher, kind of like a drone,
and try to look at things from a broader, bird's-eye view.
If you do that, if you ever find yourself wondering "why was that person like that?"...
you might realize they had their own position or reasons for feeling the way they did.
If you can try to understand what's happening under the surface of what people show, work towards understanding each other better.
It'll help you communicate better too. This is a great lesson for daily life.
This was a turning point where Shizuku took a step forward.
We saw her purity, her strength,
and just how cool she can be.
Also, the title "At The End of The Unraveled Thread" has the word "thread" in it.
The lyrics of "Metamo Re:born" also mention "threads". It's kind of like a key word.
I think that's really nice.
I really like the little connections like that.
I'm sure everyone has lots of thoughts about the event and story, so please feel free to tweet using the hashtag.
It's a very raw story, so I feel like different people will empathize with different characters.
It's natural to have many different feelings, so I hope you all share those too.
That was a really good story!
YES!
And so with that...
I've been pretty put together today, haven't I?
I even surprised myself.
Since I'm alone today, and the story being what it was, I came prepared to say what I really wanted to say.
See, I can be put together!
I'm often MC the WonderShow Channel livestreams,
so maybe you'd think at first that I would be a bit nervous here,
but I do have times when I speak seriously like this!
I appreciate you all listening!
Thank you very much.
And so, even though it was just a short time,
that's all we have for our "ProSeka AfterTalk: At The End of The Unraveled Thread" edition.
Thanks everyone for watching along!
Thanks for so many comments! I was sure to keep up with all of them.
I'm sorry I couldn't get to all of them.
Being able to watch the AfterLivein the same room together,
and connecting with everyone watching the stream in real-time has a different kind of appeal compared to watching alone.
How was it for all of you?
Did you have fun?
I'm glad.
Thank you so much.
If you haven't finished the "At The End of The Unraveled Thread" story yet, you can read it all in the Event Stories menu once the next event starts.
So please, read it as many times as you like.
Thank you.
Well then, thank you very much, everyone.
Bye bye!