Hello, everyone.
Welcome to Project Sekai After Talk: Beyond the Untangled Threads Edition.
I'm Izumi Rina, the voice of Hinomori Shizuku
from MORE MORE JUMP! It's a pleasure to be here.
This After Talk is a broadcast where we look back at the event story
and enjoy the After Live together. This is the 'Beyond the Untangled Threads' edition.
The event just finished a moment ago. How did you all like the story?
I have so much I want to talk about!
Wasn't it amazing?
So many things happened, and I want to talk about them today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please post your thoughts on the event using the hashtag #ProsekaAfterTalk.
The staff has set up the YouTube chat so I can see it right here,
and I'll be reading your comments as we go.
The management provided a device again, so I'll use it
to look at the story and the illustrations of the members with you.
For today's After Live, I'll be operating the device myself
to join a room and watch the live show with you all.
I'll create a room ID right before the After Live starts
so we can all enter it at the same time.
You might need to switch devices or apps, so I'd appreciate it
if you could get everything ready now.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Now, let's look back at the event.
We're reviewing the story for 'Beyond the Untangled Threads'.
I see comments like, "The entertainment industry is so scary,"
and many other things.
I really felt that the way Shizuku faced her past
was so cool when I first read the script.
The story really depicts the realistic behind-the-scenes side of things.
There were some quite painful scenes, but because Shizuku
faced them head-on without running away, she was able
to reach that kind of conclusion to the story.
I really want to tell Shizuku she did a great job,
and say thank you to the members of MORE MORE JUMP!
I'll talk more in-depth about it later.
I'd like to watch one episode with everyone here today.
Which episode would you like to see?
Personally...
I want to see the intense battle during the filming of I-Hazard.
What about you?
Episode 7 or 8?
What do you all think?
Regarding the story of her past...
We've seen fragments of her time in Cheerful＊Days before,
but this time it really delved deep into what specifically happened.
It's hard to choose, but maybe 7 or 8?
It looks like there are a lot of votes for 7.
Should we go with 7?
Is 7 okay with everyone?
.
Alright everyone, let's watch Episode 7 together.
Watching it with all of you
makes it so much more fun.
...
Episode 7.
Thank you so much, everyone.
I see people in the YouTube chat saying it's emotional and sending applause.
Thank you truly.
.
Oh.
I have to head out soon to prepare for the next part.
So I'll keep my thoughts brief for now, but...
It was quite something.
Seeing Shizuku's past like that...
Shizuku is such a kind person.
She has such a strong will. This scene really highlighted her strength in being able to say "thank you" face-to-face.
To put it into words, and to have the courage to do it right in the middle of filming...
Shizuku is the coolest person in the world for being able to clearly express everything she wanted to say.
I really just want to give her a hug.
In my heart, I'm already hugging her.
She's truly the best.
And Shizuku doesn't get angry, but Airi-chan gets all fired up for her, right?
That dynamic is just so good.
It captures that intense idol atmosphere, and Airi-chan's part in it...
I have some thoughts on that too, so I'd like to talk about it
in the second half.
Thank you very much.
It's so nice being able to watch this with everyone.
...
My heart is just racing.
.
What did you think?
We have a new song this time.
It's the new song we briefly introduced during the last WonderShow Channel.
It was really cool.
Momo-chan has sung many different songs up until now,
and I felt like we were able to see different sides and expressions of her each time.
But this was a different kind of coolness
that we got to see.
Since this was an After Live, seeing it as a performance with the costumes...
Everything came together and looked so cool.
The way it went dark for a moment before the pre-chorus, and then Len-kun
came to the center...
I really loved the lighting in that part.
It was truly great.
The high notes were wonderful, and the recording session was so much fun.
When it came to the recording this time...
...
It's not just the theme,
but...
in this scenario, Shizuku took that first step and went even deeper.
For me,
seeing Shizuku get her wings and awaken... I felt this song has that kind of power.
When I received the materials,
the lyrics were filled with so many emotions, so
I really wanted to express them with everything I had.
What we just showed you was the game-size version.
I hope we'll have the chance to share the full version with you somewhere, someday.
When that time comes,
I'd love for you to feel Shizuku's sense of taking flight,
especially after the second chorus.
Everyone wants to hear the full version!
But even in this version,
at the end of the chorus,
I think the feeling of "having nothing left to fear" really reached everyone.
It was absolutely wonderful.
And then everyone waves their hands, and the stage suddenly brightens up.
I thought that part
was really nice.
.
Thank you all so much for getting excited with us!
This 3DMV was posted on the official Proseka YouTube channel today at 10:10 PM.
It's already started,
and it's already up, so please go check it out.
Please watch it a lot.
We'd appreciate your support.
And now,
I'd like for us to take a look at the newly added illustrations.
There are five of them,
and the cards are all so cute.
Let's start by looking at Shizuku's.
.
Isn't it amazing?
This is the "After Training" version.
It's like...
The large flower Shizuku is sitting on...
it has this stained glass feel,
a glass-like texture that I really love.
It has a certain fleeting,
fragile beauty to it.
I can really feel it.
And this is the "Before Training" version.
I think this illustration was shown first.
A bit of Arisa was visible in the corner
of the image posted on Twitter and such.
Honestly,
it makes you go,
"Who is this woman?"
This illustration too...
Looking at this one alone, Shizuku has such a cheerful expression.
But then Airi is going "shaa," and Arisa has this "huff" look.
It's really funny once you've seen the story.
It makes a lot of sense.
.
I really love this. Arisa is great, and Airi's expression is...
...just wonderful.
Next is Minori.
Isn't she adorable?
This is the Trained version.
It's amazing.
It's a total change from Shizuku's outfit, with black and white and red accents...
...and it's just so cute.
This leaf...
The way she's wearing a leaf on her head...
...is just so cute, right?
I called her a Korpokkur earlier,
because she has this really fairy-like vibe.
And this is the Pre-Trained version.
Snacking time.
Seriously...
It's just like the ProSeka recording sites. In the waiting room...
...they always provide us with delicious food. Everyone really...
We got bento today too. Having snacks laid out like this...
...is actually quite realistic.
You're nervous before the show, but the snacks are so good you eat them anyway...
...or something like that.
You should definitely check out the side story.
Really.
It's great.
It's so good.
And next is Airi.
This is her Trained version.
The outfit is similar to the one Minori was wearing...
...but the skirt is slightly different. Airi has flowers...
...spread out like a pannier. It's so cute.
I can't stop looking at it.
The droplets scattered around her make it feel like the rain just stopped...
...and that kind of feeling...
...really reminds me of the story.
And here is the Pre-Trained version.
This scene was in the story too.
Airi is always...
...worrying about Shizuku.
She'll say, "Hey, you!"
...to check on her.
Shizuku tends not to speak up about things,
so Airi is always looking out for her.
She really is.
Airi...
Without Airi, the Shizuku we know today wouldn't exist.
Even back in her Cheerful Days era, Airi...
...
...encouraged her so much during her Cutie Days. You can really see their bond.
And then there's Haruka.
Her Training art is amazing.
This...
...the frog looks so surprised.
Isn't this expression just so cute?
It's landing on a leaf.
It's so good.
Haruka's outfit isn't just red, it has some orange in it too, which is...
...so incredibly cute.
These subtle differences in the outfits are...
...just wonderful.
Even Hatsune Miku looks incredible.
...
This is the pre-Training version.
Is this the actual filming studio for AiHaza?
The background, the camera crew, the exit sign in the back...
...the way the emergency lights look...
...and the monitor in the bottom right under the camera.
It really looks exactly like this.
The perspective you have when standing in a studio with cameras.
Haruka here...
...looks so nervous, like she's right about to go on for the real thing.
This expression is so good.
The camera?
But it really is like this.
They're constantly filming different expressions from various angles...
...switching between cameras to create the screen...
...that everyone usually sees. So this is what it's like.
It's so realistic.
And finally, Meiko.
Meiko, you look so elegant.
This white... this white outfit is just...
But it suits her so well.
That's our Meiko.
She looks so mature.
It's wonderful.
Holding the flowers...
...she's so cute.
The way the sleeves flare out a bit is great.
And so...
Looking at this, I wanted to write that the group name got smaller...
...but because of the character limit, it just says "got small."
That happens sometimes.
What do you mean?
The outfit is so cute.
It's actually quite simple...
...
Someone pointed it out to me, but looking at Shizuku's outfit,
I realized something.
When I first saw the illustration, I just thought she looked like a fairy.
I was just giggling at how cute she was, but then someone told me...
that this might be based on Thumbelina. Now, for me,
I obviously knew the title "Thumbelina,"
but I'd never actually read the story properly.
So when I looked up what kind of story it was,
it's about a tiny girl born from a flower who gets named Thumbelina.
She gets kidnapped and faces all sorts of dangers.
She really goes through a lot of difficult things.
But in the very end, a swa... swallow?
A swallow saves her,
and she finds freedom in a happy ending.
...
Wait, are these swallows?
The black and white...
Minori-chan,
Airi-chan, and Haruka-chan. Now that you mention it, they do look like swallows.
The yellow on their chests looks like a beak. Whoever noticed that is amazing.
Thank you for telling me.
It really makes so much sense now.
It changes how I see it. There's even a frog here.
A frog appears in Thumbelina too.
It all clicks for me now.
It's so interesting.
The story of Thumbelina is about how if you don't give up,
your dreams come true and you can be free.
I thought, "That's exactly this story!" Shizuku is saved by the swallows,
and now she can spread her wings.
It's just so emotional, really.
That's how it feels. Thank you for the info.
.
So, at the end of "The Untied Thread,"
the story and everything come together, and the illustration is just wonderful.
Thank you so much.
.
Now, I really want to talk about Arisa-chan.
In this story,
the way it's structured, Shizuku and the Cheerful＊Days members clash quite a bit.
So, from a certain perspective, Arisa-chan and the other former Cheerful＊Days girls
might seem like the villains. There were many moments where you'd think, "Oh, these girls..."
But you know,
Mei-chan said it too. They're all serious about being idols, and they all seriously wanted
that center position Shizuku had. They're girls who have worked incredibly hard.
That's why they get so genuinely jealous and put in so much effort.
...
It was quite intense.
I thought Arisa was such a straightforward girl...
Right, Shizuku?
Yeah.
The moment Arisa and the others met
the members of Tiade...
Arisa was like, "I'm going all out,
so you'd better do the same."
She really puts those feelings into words for you.
...
I thought her straightforwardness, always giving it her all,
was...
really cool.
But...
Well...
hiding things like that...
The way she went about it
wasn't the best way to handle it.
...
So...
It's not a bad thing to have those feelings because you want to succeed.
I understand that those "damn it" feelings come from being serious about it.
I have to learn from that. I felt like it wasn't just someone else's problem.
If you direct those feelings of jealousy the wrong way,
really bad things can happen. It's difficult to handle those feelings.
You just have to find a way to deal with them inside yourself.
That "I won't lose" feeling can lead to growth
and become the energy to work hard. I want to be that kind of person too.
I have those feelings myself sometimes.
Like, "I'm so jealous of her," and things like that. Really.
Seriously.
Every single day, really.
I feel it.
But on the other hand, Shizuku...
This time, towards the girls who were seriously aiming for the center position...
She said some things she shouldn't have.
Of course, she didn't mean any harm.
I think everyone who knows Shizuku
understands that about her.
It's not that she had bad intentions.
Shizuku was just so overwhelmed at the time,
and she could only see what was right in front of her. That's why she blurted out that someone else might be better for the center.
It just came out.
I understand that feeling too.
The pressure of being the center is insane.
Between the expectations and her persona... Shizuku wasn't being her true self.
She had a character she maintained thanks to everyone, which made it even harder.
That was part of it too.
Truly.
It's so raw.
This...
It really is.
It's just so intense.
At such a sensitive, young age,
and on top of that, having to be chosen by someone else to succeed...
It's just cruel.
Working hard alone won't make you the center.
You need someone to recognize you and say, "You're the center."
That's what makes it so tough.
But I suppose that's exactly why they're able to shine so brightly.
I really felt that.
Looking at this scenario, I thought to myself...
"I really need to be careful."
But because of this past, we have the present.
Without this, MORE MORE JUMP! wouldn't have been born, and I'm so grateful for that.
...
Shizuku said "Thank you" too. Truly, thank you.
Arisa-chan also stuck to her guns until the very end.
Nothing she said was wrong. Her actions might have been a mistake,
but her words weren't wrong at all. Even during the AiHaza recording we just watched,
you might wonder why she'd say such things on a TV show, but she knew the viewers wanted to see idols have those deep conversations, so she did it to liven up the program.
She worked with Marina-chan and the Cheerful*Days members to make it exciting, and you can really feel her dedication.
She's a true professional.
Truly.
It was nerve-wracking, though.
I was so anxious, wondering how it would turn out.
But she's not a bad person at heart.
She's just very straightforward, serious, and strict with both herself and others.
That's what I really wanted to talk about.
I ended up rambling quite a bit.
...
I really felt that way.
That's why...
When you're working your hardest, your perspective becomes subjective.
You can only see what's right in front of you. In those moments, you need to pull the camera back like a drone...
and try to look at things from a broader, bird's-eye view.
If you do that, even in moments when you're wondering "Why?"...
you might realize the other person had their own position or feelings.
If you can understand what was happening where you couldn't see, I'm sure you'll be able to reach an understanding.
It'll help you communicate better too. This is a great lesson for daily life.
...
So, that was...
the story.
This was a turning point where Shizuku
took a step forward. We saw her purity, her strength,
and just how cool she can be.
...
Also, the title "Beyond the Untangled Threads" includes the word "thread"...
The lyrics of "Metamolibbon" also mention "thread," which is a key word. It's really nice.
I think these little connections are amazing.
.
I'm sure everyone has different thoughts, so please tweet them using the hashtag.
It's a very raw story, so the characters people empathize with will probably vary.
It's natural to have many different feelings, so I hope you all share those too.
.
It really was a fascinating scenario.
So...
I'm being quite serious, aren't I?
.
I even surprised myself.
Since I'm alone today and the story was so impactful, I came prepared to say what I really wanted to say.
I have moments like this too.
I often serve as the MC for things like the Wondershow Channel, so...
I think there was a moment when everyone saw me alone
and felt a bit uneasy.
But I have times when I speak seriously like this, too.
.
Thank you for your support.
Thank you very much.
And so, although it was only for a short while...
This concludes the "Proseka After Talk: Beyond the Untied Thread" edition.
Thank you to everyone who watched the stream.
I was watching all the comments you were sending.
I'm sorry I couldn't get to all of them.
.
Being able to join the same room for a Virtual Live like this,
and connecting with people watching the stream in real-time has a different kind of appeal
than watching alone, I think.
How was it for all of you?
Did you have fun?
I'm glad.
Thank you so much.
.
If you haven't finished the "Beyond the Untied Thread" story yet, you can read it all in the Event Stories menu once the next event starts.
So please, read it as many times as you like.
Thank you.
Well then, thank you very much, everyone.
Bye!