The songs you told me about, Mei-senpai, were all truly wonderful.
Right?
I knew you'd like them, Yuri.
Did you see the MVs too?
Yes.
Before, I would've felt that MV production should be left to the professionals,
but that handmade feel from the members is what makes them so good.
You can really feel the love for the music.
And the pride of being school idols really shines through.
You get it, Yuri!
Oh!
It's rare to see you two getting so excited together.
What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing.
Nothing at all.
Hey, Yuri...
Mei-senpai was telling me about some recommended school idols and their songs.
Kano-senpai, that's not it!
I just thought Yuri might like them.
To me, Runa is the absolute best school idol.
Please believe me!
Uh, well...
It's okay, Mei-chan.
I believe you.
That reaction was like someone caught in the middle of an affair.
But now I'm curious since you two were so into it.
Tell me about those school idols too.
Sure.
No way! I love the lyrics Kano-senpai writes straight from her heart. I love her voice. Her excitement, her worries, her dreams... everything about her is the absolute ultimate!
Wait, why?
Eh?
Thank you, Mei-chan.
But this person is actually quite easily influenced.
I just can't stand the thought...
of Kano-senpai's unique style changing because of other school idols.
Especially if it happened because of me.
Even if it's just a little bit, I'd hate it.
Is it okay for me to be influenced, then?
Yuri, you wouldn't be swayed by something like this.
Um, Mei-chan, do you trust Yuri-chan more than me?
I'm your senior, you know.
Well, Mei-senpai, let's save that talk for another time,
and get the radio show started.
Ding-dong-dang-dong!
Since it's almost April Fools' Day, we've hidden a few lies in our opening talk.
Everyone, please try to see through our lies!
Ding-dong-dang-dong!
Love Live! Superstar!! Musuba Musubi Broadcasting Station: Liella! Radio - Toma, Kano, and Mei!
Hello, everyone!
I'm Sakakura Sakura, aka Sakuchan, playing Onitsuka Yuri.
Playing Shibuya Kano...
I'm Tate Sayuri, aka Saerin.
Playing Yoneme... I'm Yabushima Kano, aka Yabuchan.
And we are...
Liella!
Nice to meet you!
We've just started, but we're passing through a tunnel right now, so our voices are echoing like crazy!
You're right.
The echo is incredible!
Whoa!
Nice one, Saku.
Nice.
What's wrong, Sakura?
Sakura?
Ah.
Sayuri, say something to her.
Yabuyabu, you're so cute.
I love Yabuyabu.
I love you, Yabu.
Thank you!
I love you too!
And with that...
we've finally cleared the tunnel.
Thank goodness.
What a relief. Truly, truly.
That's good.
I'm so relieved.
Now then, Yabuchan, thanks for being our guest today! Your hair looks lovely, what do you call that style?
Glad to be here!
Wait, my hairstyle?
Today, I'm wearing my hair down, just like my favorites Sayuri and Sakura often do.
It's a hairstyle that shows my love for them!
Aww, I love you guys!
Love you!
Oh my god, I love you.
I love you so much! Oh, by the way...
I love you too!
Sayuri, I heard you've been into something lately. What is it?
Me?
Listen to this!
Hmm, let's see...
Me?
Uh...
What was it again?
What was it...
Housework?
I've been really into housework lately.
I've actually been doing quite a bit of cooking,
lately.
Wait, isn't that amazing?
That's crazy! So cool!
Praise me!
Come on, praise me!
That's awesome.
It really is.
That's so cool of you, Sayuri!
That's our Sayuri!
Right?
Thank you!
Wait...
Speaking of which,
Saku-chan, don't you have something you need to tell us?
That's right!
I,
Sakakura Sakura,
will be celebrating my birthday in three days, on April 3rd!
Happy early birthday, Saku-chan!
Thank you!
Congrats!
Happy birthday, Sakura!
Congrats, Sakura!
Oh my god!
Happy birthday, Saku!
Congrats, Sakura!
Okay!
Wait, what? What's going on?
Wait, what's happening?
For now, let's just get into the spirit!
Alright, here we go!
Saku-chan, happy birthday!
Thank you!
Happy birthday to you~
Happy birthday, dear Saku-chan~
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
And with that,
some real treats have appeared from behind!
Yay!
You can actually eat these!
I'm so happy!
Aww, they're so cute!
Thank you so much!
So cute!
I love the sweets from this place!
I'm so glad. These sweets are perfect for you, Saku!
Thank you!
A Sakura kitty!
Since it's cherry blossom season right now.
Right?
So many kitties!
Kitties!
So cute!
I'm so happy!
Oh, thank you so much!
That surprised me!
So, Sakura, your birthday is coming up on April 3rd. I know it's sudden, but do you have any goals for this year?
Oh!
I hadn't thought about it at all.
It's a surprise, after all.
That's true.
Hmm, what should I say?
Anything come to mind?
Anything is fine.
I was actually trying to do an impression of Sayuri just now,
but it didn't sound like her at all.
But I kind of get it.
The things you were saying were actually pretty spot on.
Really?
What do you mean?
I'm happy to hear that.
Look, everyone is nodding.
Yeah, it was similar!
Really?
There was definitely a resemblance.
It felt like you were just rambling on about nothing,
which is kind of my vibe today.
Did the way I spoke sound like her?
You captured her traits well.
Well, that's good then.
I wasn't really satisfied with it myself, though,
so I want to get to know everyone better and,
make this a year where I communicate more and get to know everyone even better.
That's lovely.
Reflecting on things even in a moment like this...
That's wonderful.
It's great.
Last year, I didn't really get to hang out with the Liella! members much in my private time,
so I hope we can make lots of memories together this year.
Definitely.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Thank you.
You guys are the first ones to celebrate with me!
Oh wow!
We did it!
Is that okay?
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much.
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Well then, we'll be talking about the live concert today as well,
so let's have a fun show. Please stay with us until the end. Love Live! Superstar!! Musuba Musubi Broadcasting Station: Liellaji! Let's Super Start!
Yes!
Love Live! Superstar!! Musuba Musubi Broadcasting Station: Liellaji!
Once again, I'm Sakakura Sakura, aka Saku-chan, the voice of Onitsuka Tomari.
I'm Date Sayuri, aka Sayurin, the voice of Shibuya Kanon.
And I'm Yabushima Akane, aka Yabu-chan, the voice of Yoneme Mei.
We are...
Liella!
Now, it's time for the Yuigaoka Girls' High School Submission Box, where we read your letters!
Everyone, all together! One, two... Submission Box!
Let's introduce the first email.
Okay.
This one is from Liellaji Name: Rodem-sansei.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"Everything about the 7th Live was great,"
"but 'Pop Talking' performed by the 2nd-years was especially memorable."
"It's a bright song to begin with, but seeing the four 2nd-years just being their usual selves fit the song perfectly."
"It felt like you were all singing so freely and having a great time."
"Also, seeing Yabushima-san sobbing while talking about this song during the MC was so emotional."
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Next is from Liellaji Name: Masumasu OK-san.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"I attended every single performance of the 7th Live for the first time."
"Even with the same songs, every show had something different, and it was so exciting."
"Especially 'Pop Talking'—the four 2nd-years looked like they were having so much fun singing and dancing, like they were having a bright conversation."
"It was a song that really made me feel the bond between the 2nd-years."
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Pop Talking.
Man...
The four-person version of Pop Talking.
It was so cute. And fun! Yeah.
It really was fun.
With Pop Talk-
ing, the lyrics move so fast from one person to the next, so the hand-offs are really quick.
It's like, "Oh, she's singing now! Now it's her turn!"
You don't have enough eyes to keep up, even when we usually sing it at lives.
But seeing it performed by just four people felt so fresh.
Because of that, they could walk side-by-side
and really look at each other's faces. It felt like four friends walking home together after school,
just chatting while they sang.
I really felt that.
I thought so too.
It was singing, but it felt more like a conversation. They'd end up laughing because of how the person before them sang.
Seeing them turn their real-time feelings into words like that was so fun to watch.
It felt like we were right there participating with them.
It was great to watch.
The intro to Pop Talking started with all four of them doing Kinako-chan's "Tekuteku Biyori" first.
They were all in matching outfits too.
The whole thing felt so special.
True.
Since they were in matching outfits, it really felt like they were heading home after club activities
or some other plans they had together.
Like, "Let's all go home!" It felt so much like high school girls.
I totally agree.
That was fun.
It was adorable.
Man, it was so good.
They looked like they were having the time of their lives.
They said they had a blast, and they were having so much fun backstage too.
I kind of wanted to join in.
That's awesome.
I was so jealous.
I want to sing it with all 11 of us again.
It's a song that really transforms and shines on stage.
This was the first time the chorus actually had choreography.
That's true.
We never had that before.
And they each showed their personality by doing peace signs or blowing kisses.
For me, I did a bit of a "gyaru" style peace sign.
They did peace signs that matched their respective characters.
I don't know if anyone noticed,
but there was a lot of individuality in those moments.
Wow, that's nice.
Yeah, that was really great.
They looked so happy.
Everyone, please listen to Pop Talking a lot!
Please do.
Alright, let's keep moving.
Next is from Liellaji Name: Ka-chan.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"I attended Day 2 of the 7th Live in Aichi."
"The song that left the biggest impression on me was Sing! Shine! Smile!."
"Just like the lyrics 'Sing, let's sing together, Smile, connecting our hearts'..."
"Singing this song with everyone made the whole venue feel like one. It was so much fun."
"It reminded me once again that Liella!'s music has so much power."
"Just like the name Yuigaoka suggests, I felt that we are all tied together through song."
"Through the 7th Live, I've come to love Sing! Shine! Smile! even more."
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
We also have one from Liellaji Name: Nonokura Nonoka.
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
"Hearing that the 7th Live is recommended even for first-timers,"
"I attended my very first live on Day 2 of the Aichi performance."
Thank you!
Thanks for coming!
"I was completely captivated by everyone's charming performance,"
"and the three hours flew by in an instant."
"One thing that surprised me was during Sing! Shine! Smile!,"
"when the flow led to everyone singing together."
"At first, I was hesitant, wondering if it was okay to sing along instead of just doing calls."
"But the sense of unity from everyone singing the same song was so fresh and pleasant."
"I felt a connection with everyone in the venue, and it became my best memory."
"Great job on the 7th Live."
"I'll keep supporting you!"
That's the message.
Thank you so much.
It's true that having everyone sing along to this song like that...
We haven't really had many moments like that until now.
That's true.
We all put a lot of thought into how to make this happen.
Well...
Just like Nonokura Nonoka-san mentioned,
most of our songs usually have 'Hai! Hai!' calls.
So even with 'Sing Shine Smile,' where the lyrics say 'Let's sing together,'
many people were probably wondering, 'Is it okay for me to sing out loud?'
or 'How loud should I be singing?' I think there was a lot of hesitation.
I actually saw many people who looked that way. But since the 7th Live was 'Music World,'
we really wanted to showcase Liella! as a group that cherishes singing
and a school that truly values music.
That's why we wanted everyone to sing, and why we chose 'Sing Shine Smile' for the double encore on the final day.
Even though the lyrics say 'Let's sing together,'
and some people have been singing along for a while,
there were still many who weren't sure what to do.
We're grateful for them, but we really wanted to say, 'Please, sing with us!'
We thought so much about how to lead them to feel that singing is fun.
We wanted to encourage everyone to sing along
while still maintaining the immersive world of 'Music World.'
That's what we were aiming for.
But everyone sang so much,
and it made me incredibly happy.
Plus, with every performance,
more people realized, 'Oh, it's okay to sing!'
The voices kept getting louder with each show,
and I was so moved by how the sense of unity grew stronger.
When everyone is singing, we can see your sparkling smiles
so clearly from the stage.
Those smiles are truly wonderful.
Singing together makes us smile even more too.
It was just so wonderful.
For this live, we really wanted to connect our hearts through song more than ever.
We wanted to make it a concert where everyone could feel that.
Since we all felt that way, I'm so glad we could include songs for everyone to sing.
I definitely want to have more opportunities like that in the future.
I want to keep increasing the number of songs
where we can all sing together.
Lately, Liella! has had many songs that are more about 'showing' the performance,
like 'Aspiration' or 'Jump Into the New World.'
While we're performing those, it's more like 'Whoa!'
There wasn't really that kind of back-and-forth interaction
with the audience.
So, 'Sing Shine Smile' was a big challenge for us in a good way,
and I was so happy that everyone joined in with us.
Yeah.
I feel like...
I could really feel that connection.
We felt it too.
Mm-hmm.
I know some people might still feel hesitant or wonder if it's okay to sing,
but Sayurin always says 'Please sing along with us' before we start, right?
Since Kanon-chan says it, when she does,
I hope you'll just sing your heart out without any worries. Thank you!
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
It was so much fun.
It really was.
Moving on, this next one is from Liella! Radio name, Motocross.
Thank you. 'The first performance of "Orange no Mama de" at the 7th Live was amazing. Putting this song about the sparkle and fleeting nature of youth in the encore was just unfair. Especially on the final day, I couldn't even wave my penlight; I just stood there soaking in that happy moment.'
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Next is from Liella! Radio name, Amatta Neji.
Thank you. 'I attended every single performance of the 7th Live. Thank you!'
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
'"Orange no Mama de" is the perfect song for an encore.'
'I couldn't watch the part where everyone gathered to strike the same pose as the jacket art without crying.'
'Thank you for the best youth ever.'
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
I love it.
"Orange no Mama de."
I love it so much.
We all love it.
It really is a great song.
It's so good.
It's got those emotional vibes, but how should I put it...
There are parts where we can all get hyped together with everyone,
and the lyrics are just wonderful. We also put a lot of thought into the jacket photo, didn't we?
Yeah.
This one.
We adjusted the positions over and over, even by just a tiny bit, because...
the look changes depending on the angle, so we kept...
going back and forth with the dance teacher. "Tomo-chan, a bit more this way," or "You two, move your faces closer." We did so many fine adjustments. I love that one part.
Yeah?
The part where our hands are joined and then we slowly layer them... No matter how many times I see it, I love it, but it also feels bittersweet.
I get that.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
It's so good.
That part is adorable.
It really feels like "after school." Like a normal, everyday after-school moment, but also like a very important after-school for them. The lyrics say "Let's meet again tomorrow," and they probably will meet, but you never really know for sure...
Right.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
So I really felt the weight of those words, "See you tomorrow." It's just a fleeting moment,
Yeah.
but that's how it felt to me.
And for this...
for the jacket photo, I find myself imagining what made Kanon and the others—all of Liella—decide to take this photo at that exact moment.
I wondered who took it, or if they just set up a camera. It was so much fun thinking about that
while we were shooting.
This song feels like "the now that isn't forever." It's packed with that fleeting sparkle unique to school idols and student life. Our costumes were "Aspire" this time, but if they weren't, the vibe would be totally different.
True.
Definitely. Like if we wore school uniforms.
Man, if we did it in uniforms, I think I'd actually cry.
Oh, man.
You're right.
I'm already getting a bit teary just thinking about it. I think wearing the "Aspire" costumes is what's keeping me together.
You were looking a bit teary-eyed.
True, it was for the music.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
It really is.
Oh no, what if we performed this at a real school?
Ugh, that'd be too much.
I'd end up squawking like a bird.
What would I do?
It happened!
Well...
Part of me wants to do it someday, but another part of me really doesn't. Like, once we do it, it's over...
I get that.
No, I won't do it.
I'm not... I'm not doing it.
I won't. I...
No way, I'm not doing it.
I'd be a total wreck.
That's nice.
Yeah.
All 11 of us as one.
It's a song we all love.
We're so grateful.
Thank you.
Next, this is from Rieraji Name Romuromu-san.
Thank you! "Congrats on the 7th Live! (Thank you!) This was the first time in my life I was able to attend every single performance."
Thank you so much!
Thanks!
"The most memorable part for me was 'Universe,' performed at the Aichi show."
"The moment the intro started, and when the 2nd and 3rd years waved at me, I couldn't stop crying."
"I was so happy to be able to sing along with Liella and complete the live performance together."
"Thank you for such a wonderful and happy time."
"I live in Aichi, so I'd be very happy if you came back again."
Thank you! Next is from Rieraji Name Romatofu-san.
Thank you!
Thank you. "Congrats on all four shows of Liella! 7th LoveLive! FLY! Music World! (Thank you!) During the encore in Aichi, you performed 'Universe'."
Yeah.
"The five 1st-generation members used the whole main stage for their performance. I could feel the power and brilliance with my whole body, as if the 'Universe' was right there."
"Combined with the sense of unity from the 'Woah woah' calls, I love this song more and more every time I hear it live."
"I want to keep layering my voice with Liella's and make even more memories together."
That's what they wrote.
Thank you so much!
Thank you! Here it is!
It's here.
Everyone loves "UNIVERSE!!"
I love it so much.
It was so fun.
It really was.
The cheers were so loud, it felt like everyone had been waiting for "UNIVERSE!!"
I know, right?
Everyone loves that song.
We love it too.
Yeah.
Right.
How long has it been since we last played it?
Has it been a while?
It has.
That's right.
It feels that way, yeah.
It really does.
I was so moved by everyone singing along during the finale.
I even took off my in-ears to listen.
We extended the length of the "woah-woah" part at the beginning this time.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Hearing the voices get louder and louder was such a blast.
Yeah.
Right?
Man, that was great.
We got to sing on the sub-stage too.
How was it for the 2nd and 3rd gen members?
It was my first time!
It was so fun! We were so close that I could see everyone's faces clearly. Some people were having a blast shouting "woah-woah," while others were sobbing as they sang. Seeing that almost made me tear up too.
We were so close.
I think it's really amazing.
Moments like that remind me how amazing it is that so many people gather to share the same moment and give so much energy to Liella.
I'm so grateful we could get closer to everyone. It really means a lot.
Yeah.
I feel like as we grow up, we have fewer chances to cry or laugh with our whole hearts
compared to when we were kids. So seeing them show us those precious expressions...
it makes me so happy to think they trust us enough to let out all their emotions like that. That's so true.
Yeah.
I want to do it again.
I'm so happy.
Me too.
Right?
I want to do it.
Yeah, I love it.
The 7th Live really felt like we were creating the songs together with the audience more than ever before.
Let's do the "woah-woah" part again!
Yeah.
There were so many. So many.
We had so much fun too. We've seen so many people saying they had a great time,
um...
but we really had a blast ourselves too.
Yeah.
Right.
On Day 1 of the Aichi performance, people probably expected "Mirai no Oto ga Kikoeru" next.
Especially those who had been to the Kanagawa shows
and remembered the setlist.
They probably thought "Mirai no Oto ga Kikoeru" was coming up,
but then I asked the crowd if they could shout "woah-woah" again for the next song.
That was during Day 1 of the Aichi performance.
Then, everyone mistakenly thought "Open the Gate" was coming...
Well, it wasn't exactly a mistake.
A lot of people thought we were doing "Open the Gate" for a third time, so they were all ready to shout, but then "UNIVERSE!!" started.
Doing the same song three times would've been quite a memory,
and definitely something new!
And then, well...
A "woah-woah" song came out of nowhere, which was a surprise.
But "Open the Gate" also has a lot of call-and-response,
just like you were saying.
I'm glad we had so many songs like that this time.
Right.
It was so fun.
I hope we can perform them again. I really do.
Yeah.
Thank you! And thank you all for sending in so many emails.
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Now, let's introduce a mail for the "Lunch Time Request" segment.
Okay!
This one is from "Rieraji Name" Tetsuo-san.
Thank you. I'd like to request "Synshine Smile," which was performed during the double encore of the 7th Live Aichi Day 2.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I was so happy we could all sing it together with Liella!, so I'd love to hear it during lunch.
Thank you.
We got that request. Thank you. We read your letter too.
You know, for that double encore, I actually thought we were going to do "Open the Gate" again.
I was like, "Wait, are we doing Open the Gate three times this time?" but then I heard it was "Synshine Smile."
I thought, "Oh, I guess so. Three times would be a bit much," but...
You never know, though. We might do it three times someday.
That would be intense.
Anyway, please have a listen.
Liella! with "Synshine Smile."
Let's sing together
Connecting my heart
Let's make it shine, my
star of smiles
Even if I could go anywhere in the past or future, I'd surely stay right here, savoring this moment with you forever.
Small twinkles, one by one, meeting and adding joy, even through the pain...
...I learned the feeling of fun with my friends.
I'm dreaming.
I'm just so absorbed, I love it so much I forget to sleep. I don't need freedom
at all.
I realized it.
Even if a night comes where I can't see a thing, I'll find the courage to try and smile.
That sparkle is bound to reach
you.
Smiles sparkling.
Look,
Everyone's sparkling.
I wanted to tell you, so I let my pen glide, and the world smiled as if we were meeting for the first time.
I feel like I can grab even the smallest glow, so I reach out my hand.
It was kind of funny, so I burst out laughing.
It's always dazzling, no matter when.
I can do more, I can do more. My heart is pounding uncontrollably.
I won't be late.
Connecting
the joy, smiles sparkling.
Now,
Sparkling with you.
We've been put under a spell.
A spell called a dream that won't end even as time passes.
It won't break until it comes true.
No.
No one can stop us anymore.
That's right, we're dreaming.
Because I realized
I don't need freedom.
Even if a night comes where I can't see a thing, I'll find the courage to try and smile.
That sparkle is bound to reach you.
Smiles sparkling.
Look,
Everyone's sparkling, let's sing together.
Connecting my heart, let's make it shine
my star of smiles.
Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' High School Lunchtime Broadcast Station: Lieradi!
News from Love Live! Superstar!! regarding Blu-ray info.
On Wednesday, June 24th, we will release the "Love Live! Superstar!! Liella! 1st Generation Live & Special Live Blu-ray Box."
It includes the Revival Tokyo Day 2 and the Special Live.
Bonus footage includes behind-the-scenes making-of for both the Revival and Special Live.
Plus, it comes with a cassette tape of "Shooting Voice" live recordings (1st Gen and 2nd/3rd Gen versions)...
...and a cast booklet.
Also, those who pre-order at target stores by April 15th will receive a cassette-style acrylic keychain.
It's a memorial package where you can enjoy the Revival Live tracing the 1st Gen's journey and the one-night-only Special Live, so don't forget to pre-order.
Next is music info.
On Wednesday, July 8th, the "Liella! Connecting Project Mini Album" will be released.
We'll release five versions: Original, Photo, Team Children, Team Sports, and Team Green.
The Original, Team Children, Team Sports, and Team Green versions feature new illustrations.
The Photo version uses new photos of the cast.
It's scheduled to include 4 songs, including one new group song, plus off-vocal versions for a total of 8 tracks.
As a first-press bonus, the Original, Team Children,
Team Sports, and Team Green versions include member stickers, while the Photo version includes purikura-style stickers.
All versions include a lottery application ticket for the Love Live! Series 15th Anniversary Love Live! Fes Love Live! Superstar!! presale.
Plus, as a bundle purchase bonus, you'll get a Liella! sticker book.
Don't forget to pre-order.
To celebrate the release of the "Liella! Connecting Project Mini Album," we'll be holding handover events.
The dates are Friday, October 2nd and Friday, October 9th.
Those who pre-order or purchase the "Liella! Connecting Project Mini Album" at target stores
will be invited to the handover event via lottery.
The performers vary by date, so please check the application guidelines before applying.
Check the official Love Live! Superstar!! website for more details.
Next up,
is the merchandise information.
Pre-orders for the Birthday Present Season 5 Wakana Shiki Set are now open at the Yuigaoka Girls' High School Purchasing Department.
It features a new illustration of Shiki-chan in her Lillian outfit, from her solo song on the 3rd album Aspire, which was first performed at the 7th Live.
Pre-orders are open until 11:59 PM today, Tuesday, March 31st, the day of this Lieradi broadcast.
Alright, we have the illustration right here...
It's amazing. I'm buying it.
It really suits her.
She's so cute.
It looks great on her.
What do you think?
Mei-chan, what do you think?
Look at this, Mei-chan.
Wow... It's rare to see her in a dress that shows off her legs. I like her in pants too, but she looks like such a delicate girl here.
Ah, that's true.
True. What's with that face?
Definitely.
For sure.
She's got that soft, 'nun' vibe going on.
Mei-chan... Yeah.
As expected of you.
Should I try to express it like Sayuri would? How's this, Mei-chan?
Yeah, go for it.
What would she say?
If it were Sayuri...
'I love the emo vibes!'
That's all you ever say!
You literally don't say anything else.
But it's accurate. It's so accurate.
I'll just say it for now.
I love it.
Thank you.
Exactly. Because this is just so cute.
It's super cute.
I love it.
'I love it.' It's the real deal!
It really was the real deal.
She's adorable.
This is a made-to-order limited production, so only those who pre-order can get it.
Check the Liella! official X and the Yuigaoka Girls' High School Purchasing Department for details.
Next is an announcement from the Love Live! Series Official Card Game.
On Saturday, May 23rd and Sunday, May 24th, at TFT Hall 1000
and TFT Hall 500, we will be holding the Loveca Fan Meeting.
We'll have early sales of the Love Live! Superstar!! Cheer Up! Start Deck and the Royal Holiday Booster Pack, which officially release on May 30th.
We'll also have events and exhibits for those who haven't played Loveca yet, so please come visit us.
Latest info will be posted on the Loveca official website and X, so keep an eye out.
Now for appearance information.
Starting April 1st, Liella no Tutorial Season 2 will begin on Nippon TV.
Time Machine 3-go will continue as the program MCs from Season 1.
Catch-up streaming will be available on TVer and Nittele Tada after the terrestrial broadcast.
Don't forget to check it out.
To celebrate the show, the Love Live! Superstar!! Liella no Tutorial 2026 live event will be held at LaLa Arena TOKYO-BAY on August 1st and 2nd.
The official second lottery for tickets is currently open on Ticket Pia until 11:59 PM on Sunday, April 5th.
Be sure to check this out as well.
For details on all the info we shared today, please check the Love Live! Superstar!! Liella! official X
and the Love Live! Superstar!! official website.
That's all for the announcements.
It's almost time to say goodbye on Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' Lunchtime Broadcast Station: Liella!
Here is the information for the next broadcast.
The 267th episode, scheduled for Tuesday, April 7th, will feature Ohkuma Wakana-chan, the voice of Wakana Kinako, as a guest.
Yabu-chan, do you have a message you want to leave for Kuma?
Let's go out for a meal on your treat!
Oh!
Why?
In that case, Saku and I will just watch over you from the shadows.
I wonder what they'll talk about.
We look forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
So, how was today's broadcast?
Oh, the birthday.
Happy birthday! I'm so happy.
Congratulations.
Just a little bit.
Yeah.
I'm the first one to say it! Yay!
I'm so happy.
You really were the first one.
Yeah, I totally was!
LieRadio is always the first one to celebrate,
every single year. I'm so happy.
I'm so glad.
Thank you!
And that's all for this episode of Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' Lunchtime Broadcast Station Liella!.
Your hosts were Date Sayuri, the voice of Shibuya Kanon,
Sakakura Sakura, the voice of Onitsuka Tomari, and Yabushima Akane, the voice of Yoneme Mei.
See ya!