Good Need-vening!
This is Ruriko Noguchi, voice of Ichika Hoshino.
This is Carin Isobe, voice of Saki Tenma.
This is Reina Ueda, voice of Honami Mochizuki.
This is Yuki Nakashima, voice of Shiho Hinomori.
Well then, congratulations on Project Sekai's 5th Anniversary!
The four of us playing Leo/need
have gathered to record this video message for everyone!
It's finally happening!
We can finally touch each other!
This is the first time all four of us are together!
Wow, the first time?
Thank you, 5th Anniversary
Thank you, 5th Anniversary.
The four of us are really all together now.
I'm so happy.
Looking Back on These 5 Years
Let's start by taking a look back on these last 5 years of Project Sekai.
Anyone have anything burning they need to get out there?
Are we all like your students?
I'm too nervous to start
I guess Ichika is the one who should be starting us off.
Initially, Ichika tended to speak with a lot of "..."
Also lots of monologuing to herself
Like she had lots of things that she wanted to say but didn't know how to.
she kept a lot of things bottled up inside.
But now, after 5 years,
she's able to more openly express her happiness and joy,
and she can speak her mind to her bandmates more freely.
Like her love for yakisoba bread....
and when she goes off full throttle
At first I didn't really...
Yeah, I didn't really get that vibe from her at first,
But she's shaken that off more recently,
even if her love for Miku is so great,