Mei-chan, you've really become reliable lately.
Yes.
"It seems my sister trusts Mei-senpai quite a bit as well."
Na-Natsumi does?
It really doesn't look that way, though.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like Mei-chan naturally leads all the 1st and 2nd years,
or gives them a push when they need it.
Just as Kanon-senpai says, Mei-senpai takes the initiative to keep everyone together.
Well, that's...
If I don't do it, everyone just does whatever they want,
so I don't really have a choice.
It's impressive that you can step up without hesitating like that.
If it were me, I'd just leave the leading to Chi-chan or Ren-chan.
"Mei-senpai was also very reliable when we were heading to Music World."
"Oh, I heard about that from Margarete-chan."
You did a great job, Mei-chan.
Back then, I just thought I wanted to be a bit more like Chisato-senpai.
Well,
looking back now, I think I was a bit too tense.
"I think that's perfectly fine."
"Seeing Mei-senpai work hard has the benefit of making Liella more positive."
I totally get it!
It makes us feel like we can't afford to lose either.
Eh?
You and the others, Kanon-senpai?
No, no, no way.
There's no way you seniors would lose to someone like me.
Don't say that, Mei-chan.
You just said "someone like me," didn't you?
You have more power to move those around you than you realize.
Plus, you have the kindness to support others.
Yes.
"Margarete says that often too."
"I can't afford to lose to Mei-senpai."
Or so she says.
I can definitely imagine her saying that.
By the way, your Margarete impression is spot on, Tomari.
"I'm flattered."
"Anyway, Mei-chan, you're the driving force of Liella,"
so I'm counting on you from now on.
Driving force?
Well, that might be a bit of an exaggeration...
But fine, if it's just lighting a fire under the engine, I'll do it anytime.
"That's very reassuring."
"In that case, please go ahead and light a fire under my sister's motivation for the next exams."
Oh,
that sounds good.
Then light a fire under my baking, too!
Don't get carried away, you two!
I can't look after you that much!
Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' High School Broadcasting Station: Lieraji - Tomari, Kanon, and Mei!
Hello,
everyone!
"I'm Date Sayuri, the voice of Kanon Shibuya."
"I'm Sakakura Sakura, also known as Sakuchan, the voice of Tomari Onitsuka."
And I'm Yabushima Akane, also known as Yabuchan,
"the voice of Mei Yoneme."
Together, we are...
"Liella!"
"It's a pleasure to be here!"
Yay!
"So, this time we're bringing you the trio of Tomari, Kanon, and Mei."
Mei-chan's here too.
"Let's do this."
Welcome!
"Glad to have you."
"Thanks for having me."
"Today is March 24th, but coming up on March 28th, which is Sunny Pa Day..."
"It's the birthday of Hijirisawa Yuna's voice actress, Yoshitake-chan!"
That's amazing!
"Happy birthday!"
"Sunny Pa Day really is Sunny Pa Day."
It must be fate.
Right? It's too perfect.
Isn't it incredible?
It really is. Happy birthday!
"Let's all celebrate when the day comes."
"Please do!"
"We're counting on you."
"Now then, we've received some mail."
Yes. I'll read it.
"It's from Liella name: Kabo-san."
"Thank you so much."
"Thank you!"
"Congratulations on being confirmed to perform at LuckyFes!"
Thank you!
Seeing Liella perform in Ibaraki, the hometown of the Onitsuka sisters and myself, was one of my dreams.
"So when I saw the announcement, my emotions exploded so much I almost screamed out loud at work!"
Yeah.
Hitachi Seaside Park is a place where I have so many memories,
like going on school trips as a kid or having barbecues with my family and friends.
"I'm so happy to be able to make new memories there with everyone in Liella."
Mhm.
"I'm really looking forward to having the best time with Liella again this summer."
That's what they wrote.
"Thank you so much!"
"Thank you!"
"Next is Liella name: Takashi from Sendai. Thank you!"
"Thank you."
"Congratulations on your appearance at LuckyFes!"
Yeah, thank you!
Since it's a festival in Ibaraki, the home of the Onitsuka sisters,
"I'm sure it'll feel extra special."
Yeah.
It's a summer festival, so please sweep the venue into a whirlwind of excitement with your hot performance!
Mhm.
Also, I'm looking forward to seeing if you'll perform any songs that scream "summer."
Definitely. They also said, "I'd love to hear about your enthusiasm for the festival
or if there's anything specific you're hoping to do at a summer fest!"
That's what we received.
"Thank you so much!"
"Thank you!"
"That's right, Liella will be appearing on Day 2 of LuckyFes, on the 9th."
"It's officially decided!"
We're performing!
"Thank you!"
"Thank you so much."
"I'm so happy."
It's amazing.
It's great that it's in Ibaraki.
It really is.
It's exciting, isn't it?
Since it's the Onitsuka sisters' hometown,
we've always wanted to perform in Ibaraki someday.
I'm so happy it's coming true! And the other artists are so...
Incredible.
Right?
I was so surprised.
It really shocked me.
Yeah.
"We'll give it our all to show Liella!'s power and keep up with everyone!"
"We're looking forward to it."
"Please look forward to it!"
It'll be the middle of summer.
August 8th and 9th.
Make sure to keep your strength up...
and come see us!
Definitely.
Bring sports drinks.
Wait, are we performing while holding sports drinks?
Maybe we should do that.
The liquid might go flying everywhere.
Go flying, huh?
That'd be bad.
So sticky.
We'd be all sticky.
Even though it's a festival.
Even though it's a festival!
It's gonna be so hot.
Everyone, please come see us!
"We'll be waiting for you."
"Alright, please stay with us until the very end!"
"Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Broadcasting Station: Liella! Let's Superstar!"
"Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Broadcasting Station: Liella!"
"It's time for the Yuigaoka Girls' High School Suggestion Box, where we read your letters."
"Alright everyone, let's say it together! Ready, set... Suggestion Box!"
"Okay, let's get to the mail."
This first one is from Liella name: Miku.
"Thank you very much."
"Thank you!"
"I attended both days of the 7th Live in Kanagawa and watched the Aichi performance via stream."
"Mei-chan's solo song, 'Sky Linker,' started with her taking the baton from the club president, Chisato-chan."
Yeah.
"What was especially memorable was the part at the end of the chorus where she thrusts her fist forward."
I totally get that.
Since it happened several times during the song, the first time I saw it, I was moved to tears,
"and from the second time onwards, I was thrusting my fist right along with her."
Mhm.
It was a performance where I felt the full extent of Mei-chan's straightforward strength,
"encompassing her big heart, her kindness that embraces weakness, and her desire to protect. That's what they wrote."
Thank you so much.
"Thank you!"
"Next is from Liella name: Baron Ojipan."
"Thank you very much."
"Thank you!"
"Regarding 'Sky Linker,' the clapping with hands near the face during the instrumental break,"
"and the side steps that followed, looked like a traditional Spanish dance..."
"like Flamenco."
"Yeah."
Spain is often called the land of passion,
and I felt like the dance expressed the passion Mei-chan hides within her.
The moment I first saw it, I thought, 'Whoa, that's so cool!'
And with that... Ciao!
"That's 'goodbye' in Spanish. (Laughs) That's the letter."
Thank you very much.
"Thank you!"
Ciao!
"Ciao!"
"Alright, next is from Liella name: Red-haired Kana. Thank you!"
Thank you very much.
Seeing 'Sky Linker' on Day 1 of the 7th Live in Kanagawa was truly the best.
"Yabu-chan's dance was so cool I couldn't get it out of my head,"
"and it still leaves a strong impression on me now."
"The song and lyrics are great, and I listen to it all the time."
I'd love to see the 'Sky Linker' dance again somewhere! That's what they said.
"Thank you so much."
"Thank you!"
"Wow..."
I want to hear more about this.
"'Sky Linker' was seriously so cool."
"Right?"
At first, I wondered if she'd perform with a mic stand, just standing there and hyping up the crowd.
True.
I couldn't really imagine her doing an intense dance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I kept wondering how it would turn out, but I never expected Flamenco in the instrumental break.
Mhm.
Well, it was a really valuable experience for me.
It's not every day you get to do Flamenco.
That's true.
When I first saw the video of Mei-chan's choreography,
I was like, 'What kind of dance is this?!'
Mei-chan was doing a style of dance that none of us had ever done before.
I told her, 'Wow, this is amazing!' and when I heard it was Flamenco, I was so surprised.
I was like, 'How do you even do that?'
Yeah.
I couldn't do it at all at first.
No way, really?
It used a core that I'd never used before...
The whole foundation of the movement was completely different. I don't know much about dance,
but even I could tell it was incredibly difficult and confusing.
Mhm, mhm.
I practiced that instrumental break over and over again at home.
Wow.
But you were so good at it!
It was really cool.
It makes me nervous, though.
Yeah, I bet.
Since everyone does their solo choreography lessons separately,
we don't even know when the others are practicing, or even...
what they're doing in the first place.
Exactly.
So when I finally saw it, I was like, 'Whoa, she's doing Flamenco!'
It was such a shock.
We didn't really know if each other's songs would have dancing or not.
So, when I met up with the other members, I'd be like,
'Wait, are you dancing to Kanon-chan's song?'
or 'How much dancing is there?'
We had conversations like that all the time.
Then I happened to run into Yabu right after she finished Mei-chan's choreography lesson.
She muttered something like, 'It was kind of flamenco-ish...'
And I was like, 'Wait, what do you mean?' I was so confused.
I just couldn't wrap my head around the word 'flamenco'.
Like Yabu said earlier,
I pictured her standing tall at a mic stand,
with a fiery vibe. So when I heard 'flamenco'...
I mean, you don't really get many chances to see flamenco, right?
It's not something Liella would usually do.
Definitely not.
All of us doing flamenco together?
Probably not.
It must be hard when you don't even know what the 'right' way to do it is.
It looks difficult just watching it, so I think it would've been really tough to actually do.
It's incredibly difficult.
But I saw how much you were practicing.
Yeah, your moves were so sharp!
It was so cool.
That's why...
Like Miku-san said, that part where you thrust your fist forward feels so direct and so much like Mei-chan.
I love it.
Yeah, I totally get that.
It's technically a dance move, but it doesn't feel like one.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
It feels like you're putting your whole heart into that fist.
I found myself getting really emotional during that part too.
Mm-hmm.
That happens at the end of the first chorus, right? Or...
The end of the second chorus.
And you do it in the final chorus too, so it's the very last thing.
The movement is the same every time, but for the first,
second, and final time, the feelings behind it felt different to me.
Depending on the performance, what I'm feeling in that moment changes,
so I put all those emotions into my fist.
I see, I see.
That's so good.
Thank you.
I also really love the sound of the glass shattering.
Oh!
That part is so cool.
Right?
You can hear it even better during the live show.
Oh, definitely.
It really resonated. And the flames in the background...
matched Mei-chan so well, it was awesome.
Yeah.
And since 'Fanatic' was right after that...
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
We were getting ready, so we were watching Mei-chan from the wings.
Feeling that heat, the two of us were like, 'Alright, let's go!'
We felt like we had to keep that momentum going.
"It was really, really great."
"So cool."
"Thank you so much."
"Can I say something too? Kanon performs before Mei-chan,"
"and then there's a bit of time before Kanon's next turn."
"So I was able to watch Mei-chan as she was about to go on stage."
"From backstage, you know."
"And of course, before that too,"
"but I'd also see Mei-chan—I mean, Yabu—right after her performance."
"Every time she finished, she had this look of passionate fulfillment,"
"but at the same time, she always looked like she was thinking,"
'What should I do next?' She always had that expression,
Yabu did.
So, how do I put it?
She had her own sense of accomplishment from giving it her all,
but she also looked like she felt she still had a long way to go.
Backstage.
And that just felt so much like Mei-chan to me.
I was almost in tears while drinking my hot water.
"Just watching her."
"That's so Mei-chan."
"From our perspective, it was already so wonderful."
Everyone's going through it...
Like, what... what was it?
Your own what?
The wall is so high... no, no, no, that's not it.
Everyone's the same.
Everyone has such high aspirations and we all think that way...
That's why I feel like I have to work harder too, being inspired by everyone.
I might not have felt that way if I were alone,
but seeing and feeling everyone's performance made me think I could go further,
and that there's more I can do.
Yeah. That's true.
The solo songs this time really were a source of mutual inspiration.
Me too, everyone was, right?
Each other.
I was really happy about that.
Mutually, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Even though a solo song is for one person, I felt like I wasn't alone during those performances.
I felt like we were all building it together.
Oh, and the costumes too.
That "Girl Crush" look.
These are so good.
I've never worn anything like this before.
So cool.
If you told me they were private clothes, they'd be the most like that.
True.
They wouldn't look out of place walking around a stylish town.
Definitely.
Some people probably wear that.
Yeah, yeah.
"The fishnet tights were wonderful."
"That was a first for me in my life."
Fishnet tights...
Is it okay for people to see that?
I'm just full of gratitude.
Right.
We were worshipping them backstage.
I definitely was.
I was worshipping them.
Oh, and on the final day, I think...
During one of the last shows, it wasn't part of the choreo, but her hair...
got in her face, and while looking forward or casting her eyes down—
I forget which, but she brushed it away,
and the camera caught it perfectly.
How embarrassing.
That part was just too good, like, wow.
I would definitely put that on repeat.
Ah, the best.
Thank you, hair.
It was seriously so cool.
I was like, "Whoa!"
So cool.
Amazing.
Yabu-san doesn't remember it, though.
Yabu-san doesn't remember a thing.
But it was so beautiful,
"I loved it."
I'm glad.
Geez.
Everyone, please check it out.
Yes, please do.
Please check it out.
I bet some people are saying that.
Please remember it, everyone.
"Thank you."
"Next, we have a message from Liella name: Hajiketa Kata Popcorn."
"Love Live! Superstar!! Liella! 7th Live."
That was tough, wasn't it?
It really was.
All the 2nd and 3rd years were saying this,
but the choreography was really, really difficult. And yet, to the audience,
it's a kind of difficulty that's hard to imagine. From their perspective, it looks like we're having fun,
and the dancing looks effortless, but...
it was actually really tough.
It really was.
"Yeah, it was truly difficult."
"Yeah, when we first learned the choreo, we all felt like our souls were leaving our bodies."
"We were all so worried about whether we could actually sing and dance it at the same time, but the more we practiced, the more our breathing synced up. Eventually, that anxiety turned into pure fun."
"So on the day of the live, I felt more of a sense of unity with the audience than worry. How about you guys?"
Yeah, definitely.
Right. Ever since "High Motivation" was announced...
...everyone was so excited to see the performance. I felt a lot of pressure, but...
I also thought the choreo would be a bit simpler, or maybe have a "sweeter" feel to it.
I thought so too.
But it's a lot of dancing!
Why is it like that?
I know, right?
I was worried we wouldn't be able to express the fun of the song, but as the live got closer, our practice gave us confidence. We decided to just have fun...
Exactly.
...and show everyone that the 2nd and 3rd gen members can do this! We wanted to deliver that power.
Yeah.
In the end, we had fun, but at first, we couldn't even think about that. We were just desperate. When we first tried singing and dancing together...
Right.
...we were all like, "This is impossible! This is really bad!"
Even though there are fewer of us than the full 11, we couldn't even catch our breath. The formations were so difficult.
And the rhythm isn't just a simple 1-2-3-4 beat.
It's like, "Wait, we're dancing to those tiny little sounds too?" The choreographer really packed it in.
It really was something. But it turned out great!
Yeah, it did.
What part was especially difficult?
From our perspective watching you, like Saku said, you're hitting every single beat.
But since we're just watching, we just end up thinking, "Wow, that looks like fun!"
Right.
So, where was the struggle?
With other songs, I can usually point to one specific part that was hard.
But with this one, every single part was a little bit difficult, so it felt hard the whole time.
I see.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It was just... tough.
How do I put it? Usually, when it's not your turn to sing, you might just be standing there watching the others...
But there's almost none of that in this song.
You're always doing one or the other.
You're constantly moving, and the formations are tough. You just end up totally out of breath.
Yeah.
I get it.
I can say it now, but I was a mess during the choreo lessons too.
Really?
You were?
Everyone was basically crying while doing it.
Seriously.
I was crying my eyes out.
I really wondered what was going to happen.
"What's going to happen to us?"
But I thought, "Mei-chan would never cry..."
Yeah.
...so seeing her cry made me cry even more. I don't even know why.
No, no, that's not true.
Ah.
Well, I can talk about it now.
Everyone practiced so much at home. When we met up again, the quality had improved so much. I was so impressed.
Well, the lyrics even say something about "having changed," right?
Hearing this story makes me think that's exactly what it was about.
"I wasn't there since I'm a 1st gen member, but..."
"Even the title is "High Motivation.""
Um...
During rehearsals, the 2nd and 3rd gens would be like, "Alright!"
"High Motivation!" they'd say, pumping themselves up.
Seeing that just made me think, "That's so cool."
Yeah, you really can't get through a song like that without that kind of motivation.
But during the actual performance, everyone looked so happy.
You were all smiling, so I realized how much hard work must have gone into getting to that point.
Everyone worked so hard.
Because everyone gave it their all...
...it turned out great.
By the way, did you see Nako's impression?
Eh? What's that?
You haven't seen it?
You should have her show you sometime.
What is it?
Did you take a video?
No, I didn't, but she's always mimicking the "High Motivation" choreo.
It's so incredibly cute, so you should definitely ask Nako to show you.
I want to see it!
She mimics a very specific part.
Oh, really?
I've gotta see that.
Wait, what is it? What could it be?
"Thank you so much."
"Thank you!"
That's amazing.
Alright, we've talked a lot, but we're not quite finished,
"so we'll keep the conversation going next week."
Alright!
"Anyway, thank you all so much for all the emails."
"Thank you!"
"Now, let's read a mail for our Lunchtime Request segment."
Alright!
"It's from Radio name: Mizuki."
"Thank you so much."
"Thank you!"
"I'd like to request 'Sky Linker'."
"My favorite part of this song is definitely right before the final chorus,"
"during the 'Right now, I'll change it' part."
"Mei-chan usually has a lower voice, but she hits a clear high note there,"
"and I just love the gap and her soulful, scream-like singing voice."
That's the message.
Thank you!
You can really feel the soul in it.
"It's a very passionate song, so I hope you'll listen closely to the vocals and the backing track as well."
Please listen to it.
Yoneme Mei, "Sky Linker."
The reason you only notice the missing pieces
is because you know what perfection looks like.
But that's okay.
I'm far from a god who can end someone's hesitation,
but I'll stay in the rain with you until we find it.
My wish is in the blue sky, I'll take the hand that reaches for it.
I'll block out everything, yes, everything that's hazy.
I'll even protect you from fate itself.
Always,
yes, always, don't lose to this depressing world today.
Rise up
and fly over the many obstacles to reach our destination.
We've become what you call comrades.
When I pray for someone other than myself, I'll prove there's not a single cloud of doubt.
Dive into the blue sky; if you hold this hand, I'll do it.
Everything,
yes, everything—what's wrong with being weak?
If you want to cry, let's cry and scream, I don't mind.
Always,
yes, always, I'll accept any version of you.
Show me.
Even if you're cracked, I'll show you I can take it all without breaking.
If you want a tough vessel, if you want a clear present, I'll change it for you right now.
In that blue sky,
if you look up, I'll take you into the brilliant blue.
Everything,
yes, everything that's hazy, I'll block it out.
I'll even protect you from fate itself.
I'll support you; you have a place here.
Don't lose, ever.
Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' Lunchtime Broadcast Station, Liella!
Radio.
News from Love Live! Superstar!!
"Here is the music information."
"On Wednesday, July 8th, the release of the Liella!"
"and Musubu Project mini-album has been confirmed."
"We will release five versions: Original, Photo, Team Kids, Team Sports, and Team Green."
"The Original, Team Kids, Team Sports, and Team Green versions feature new illustrations,"
"while the Photo version uses new photos of the cast."
"It will include 4 songs, including one new group track, plus off-vocal versions for a total of 8 tracks."
"As a first-press bonus, the Original, Team Kids,"
"Team Sports, and Team Green versions will include member stickers."
"The Photo version will include a purikura-style sticker."
"All versions will include an advance lottery application ticket for the Love Live! Series 15th Anniversary Love Live! Fes"
"and Love Live! Superstar!!."
"Additionally, as a bundle purchase bonus, we'll be giving away"
"a Liella! sticker book."
Don't forget to pre-order.
To celebrate the release of the Liella!
"and Musubu Project mini-album, we've decided to hold a handover event."
"The dates are Friday, October 2nd, and Friday, October 9th."
"Those who pre-order or purchase the Liella!"
"and Musubu Project mini-album at participating stores will be invited to the handover event via lottery."
"The cast members vary by date, so please check the application guidelines before applying."
"Check the Love Live! Superstar!! official website for details."
"News from the Love Live! Series Official Card Game."
The Start Deck "Love Live! Superstar!!",
"featuring only Liella! members and songs, will be released on Saturday, May 30th."
"This product will include a special rarity "Secret Serial" card with a serial number."
"Each numbered card is a super-luxurious, one-of-a-kind item in the world."
"The Start Deck allows you to play LoveCa! immediately, so even if you haven't played before, please pick this up and get started."
"Latest info will be posted on the Love Live! official site and X, so keep an eye out."
"Appearance information."
"Starting April 1st, Liella!'s"
"ChuChu Liella!"
"Season 2 will begin on Nippon TV."
"Panshin No. 3 will continue as the program MC from Season 1."
"Catch-up streaming will be available on TVer and Nittele TADA after the broadcast."
Don't forget to check it out.
Furthermore, to commemorate the broadcast, the live event "Love Live! Superstar!! Liella!
no ChuChu Liella!
"2026" will be held at LaLa arena TOKYO-BAY on August 1st and 2nd."
"Official secondary lottery applications are open on Ticket Pia until 11:59 PM on Sunday, April 5th."
"Please check this out as well."
"For details on all the information announced today, please check the Liella!"
"official X account and the Love Live! Superstar!! official website."
"That's all for the announcements."
"Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' Lunchtime Broadcast Station, Liella!"
It's almost time to say goodbye to the radio show.
"Here is some information about our upcoming broadcasts."
"Episode 266, scheduled for Tuesday, March 31st, will once again feature Yabushima Akane, the voice of Mei Yoneme."
"And for Episode 267 on Tuesday, April 7th, we'll have Ookuma Wakana, the voice of Kinako Wakana, for a Toma-Kano-Shiki episode!"
"We're looking forward to your messages!"
"So, how did you enjoy today's broadcast?"
How was it?
Ding, ding, ding!
Wait, is it always like this?
Are you okay, Sakura?
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Saku... Sakura, you surprised me just now.
I didn't expect you to join in on that side.
I was thinking, "When did Sakura become like this?"
They're worried about you!
I couldn't think of a comeback, so I figured I'd just join in instead.
That's wonderful.
Yes, truly wonderful.
Yabushima looked so confused just now.
Saku... Sakura, they're worried about you.
Being pitied is the most embarrassing thing ever.
Anyway, how was it for you today?
Well, I got to share my thoughts in such great detail...
I mean, I talked quite a lot.
Was that really okay?
"Thank you so much."
Everyone wanted to hear it!
We'll be talking more next week, too.
That's right.
Yeah. I wonder how long we can keep talking about the 5th Live...
We're planning to talk about it for about three years.
Roughly that long, yeah.
We'll keep going until we've covered every single song.
Oh, then let's do every song!
We won't be able to start the Unit Live at this rate!
"I don't know about that."
"We'll push it back."
"We'll push it back! We'll push it back!"
"And with that, this has been Love Live! Superstar!! Yuigaoka Girls' Lunchtime Broadcast Station: Liella!"
That's all for this episode.
Your hosts were Date Sayuri, the voice of Shibuya Kanon,
Sakakura Sakura, the voice of Onitsuka Tomari,
"and Yabushima Akane, the voice of Yoneme Mei."
See you!
"Because I heard a \"see you\" in the breathtaking sunset."
"The breeze and you."