Natsumi-chan, you did a great job yesterday, didn't you, Natsumi-chan?
As expected of my big sister.
Ehe, I'm glad you're happy with Den-senpai's birthday celebration.
I can't believe he was filming a celebration video with everyone at Yuigaoka.
He cooperated with the first and second year students alone, and he kept it a secret from us, the third year students!
I told my big sister that it would be more efficient for me to get data from the students, but...
That's not a good idea.
And so, Oninatsu's突撃収録!
Would you like to say something to the student council president, Hazuki Rei-senpai, for his birthday celebration?
Please!
Eh? Me?
Ah, um...
Happy birthday, Ren-chan!
I always respect you for your straightforwardness.
Thank you very much!
I'll send this video to you, Ren-senpai.
Come on, don't film it all of a sudden!
I'm not used to that kind of thing.
You said you weren't used to it, but you did comment on it, didn't you?
That's right.
The way you look at the camera and the way you smile is perfect!
Ahahaha!
I was put on the good side of Natsumi-chan, and...
That's how you filmed everyone!
That's right.
That project couldn't have been possible without my big sister.
You're exaggerating.
I just did it because I was having fun.
Is that to celebrate Ren-chan?
Or is it to shoot a video?
Of course, both!
For my big sister, fun is the driving force.
It's the same as being able to continue with video streams and video editing every day.
Ah!
That reminds me!
W-What is it?
I'm sorry!
I was wondering if Sumire-chan and Mei-chan would release the congratulatory video on Oni Natsu Channel...
Natsu?
I said that Natsumi-chan wouldn't do that, but...
You two should confirm it just in case.
Big sister, I think it would be better to stop releasing the congratulatory video for the student president for the completely no-cut version.
Stop!
You don't have to say unnecessary things!
Natsumi-chan, the completely no-cut version...
Now, now, now!
It's time for the radio!
We'll have a fun talk for everyone's love and peace!
Love Live Super Star!
Yu-Gi-Oh! Lunchtime Broadcasting Station!
Rielashi!
Toma Kano and Natsu!
Everyone!
Hello!
I'm Onitsuka Tomori's role, Saku-chan, and I'm Satoko's Chakura.
I'm Shibuya Kano's role, Sayori, and I'm Tate Sayori.
I'm Onitsuka Natsumi's role, Emorin, and I'm Emori Aya.
We are...
Riela!
Nice to meet you!
We'll be back with Toma Kano and Natsu again this week!
Please look forward to it!
This is the last broadcast in November, so...
Everyone, there's only one month left until Christmas!
I'm so happy!
The town is sparkling!
It's been sparkling for a while, but...
Rielashi, I'd like to do something Christmas-like.
I'd like to do it.
Is it okay?
Call me!
Come on, Toyomori-chan!
I want you to call me, but I may not be in order.
I'll bring you home.
I'm sure I'll bring it.
I'm expecting to see you about three months later.
Call me while you're on the phone.
I'll look forward to it!
I'll look forward to seeing you in Santa Claus costumes.
It's the best!
Here you are!
It's like a performance.
Bring me presents!
Please call me!
I'd like you to call me!
Please!
Do you want to see it?
You want to see it, right?
I want to see it.
When Christmas comes,
this year will be over.
It's the end of the year.
We have started cleaning.
Is that your house?
My room?
Why?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Until October,
my house was in a terrible state.
It was terrible.
In November,
Riella's live performance was calm.
So I had some free time.
So I thought,
now is the time.
I started cleaning water.
That's great.
It's a little crazy.
I did the firework.
I rapped.
I cleaned the waste water tank.
I took a bath.
I have a house.
I want Santa to come.
It's a gift.
Hello, Sayulee.
Please come in.
I'm a fireman.
Fireman?
You're wrong.
I'm a fireman.
Let's do it.
I can do it.
Let's do it together.
Let's do it together in Santa's clothes.
I'm a master.
Please.
Thank you for watching.
Let's start.
Love Live Super Star
Yu-Gi-Oh! Lunchtime Broadcasting Station
Rie-Rajin
Let's start.
Cleanser
It is a song that conveys that this is also a card.
Not only the chosen people, everyone can shine.
I was pushed back by the lyrics.
I think I can have high motivation to try my best.
That's what it is.
Thank you very much.
Next, Rie Rajuneimu
I got it from Tomari no Sakusaku Ebi Fry.
Thank you very much.
I bought a CD of Open the Gate
I listened to High Motivation in full.
Before, Sakuchan said that there was a song like Tomari in No. 2.
I wonder if it's here.
I would like to hear it from Sakuchan.
Thank you very much.
I really like this.
Open the Gate's coupling song High Motivation
Full size has already been released.
Oh, good.
I want to hear it from the two of you.
Full.
Isn't it good?
I like it very much.
I also have a favorite part in the lyrics.
Where?
I want to be the only one in the first part.
This is Mei-chan's part.
Mei-chan's part.
I admire it.
It's a good place.
It's starting.
What about Aya-chan?
I'm really curious about the two of you.
This is ...
All the lyrics are really good.
Popcorn said that.
It's not just the chosen one.
The fact that everyone sings the lyrics that everyone can shine.
This is my favorite part.
This is the first time I've ever seen it on TV.
I can't write this lyrics.
I can't sing this lyrics.
We've grown up through various setbacks.
That's why we can sing together.
I like the background of the song.
The four of us are not the first four.
The four of us are just pulling our backs.
It was shocking to hear that.
I still remember it.
We're pulling our backs.
There was a saying that only the third-year students should come out.
Not only the chosen one, but everyone can shine.
We've grown up to recognize ourselves.
I don't think we should say that we did our best.
I want to say that we did our best because we couldn't find any other suitable words.
But I don't want to end with the words that we did our best.
I can imagine how much time and wall there was behind the words that we did our best.
It's a bright song, but I cry when I listen to it.
I know.
I know a lot.
I remember a lot.
I'm glad it's a melody like this.
It's a marching song, so I'm still crying.
If this was a grand song, I wouldn't be able to listen to it.
I wouldn't be able to listen to it.
But I really like it.
I feel a lot of things.
How about you, Saku?
I was listening to the song called Tomari no Sakusaku Ebifurai.
There are a lot of lyrics that are like lines.
There are a lot of tasks.
I didn't think there would be a lot of tasks in the lyrics when I talked about it in the anime.
It's a song that has a playful feel to it.
There are touching lyrics and backgrounds, but it also has a playful feel to it.
I thought I liked it.
Before the last chorus, there was a part where Toma Masako was singing.
I don't usually get that kind of heat.
I'm glad I'm singing a part that says, let's go more.
I love school idols and I feel motivated.
I'm glad I felt motivated.
I really like this part.
It's good.
It's a D-melody here.
The song is really falling.
I really like everyone's baton pass.
It's in the middle of the song.
Kyoko-chan, Mei-chan, Shiki-chan, Natsumi-chan, Maru-chan, Toma-chan are singing in order.
And the lyrics are linked to the members.
I think that's why everyone wrote it.
It's really good.
I'm really happy.
I've been watching the 3rd-year revivals.
I want to sing for the 3rd-year.
I want to show a positive feeling that says, look at us more.
It's a song that Ikisei made while he was working hard on the revival live.
It's like a cancer song.
When I listen to it after I know it, I feel like I'm going to sing it well.
Please listen to it a lot.
Thank you very much.
Next, we have a message from Rie Rajineimu Rose and Ushi-san.
I saw the Ushiku Sanpo Unadon Hassho no Chi, which was released on the official channel of Ushiku City, Ibaraki Prefecture.
Thank you.
Two people from Onitsuka-shimai ate the Unadon of Yasukawa-san in Ushiku, where the Unadon Hassho no Chi was released.
I went to eat it the other day, but the more the eel melts in my mouth, the softer it is.
The umami of the sauce and eel soaked into the rice, and I was so happy that I could feel that I could eat it all.
I'm full and full.
I want to eat it when I come to Ushiku again.
Thank you very much.
Next, we have a message from Rie Rajineimu Una-Una Time.
I saw the Ushiku Sanpo Unadon Hassho no Chi, which was released on the official channel of Ushiku City, Ibaraki Prefecture.
By the way, my sister was talking about Una-Una in the video.
Do you get teased by the members?
I don't.
The previous video was very rich and delicious.
That's right. I wanted to hear it.
I remembered it.
I was talking about Kuma.
I was teased by Kuma.
How was it this time?
I saw it.
This time.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
Akari-chan said it, too.
That's a bad word, isn't it?
I really said it.
Isn't it a bad word?
It's cute.
That's right.
Isn't it too much?
I think it's a little bit of a push.
Really?
It's cute because it's Natsumi.
If I did it, it wouldn't be cute.
This is important to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What's going on?
Why is it a little broken every week?
It was the same last time.
I have to get a new wind.
There's a typhoon.
When I talked to the bear this time,
When I was eating lunch at the academy,
I said I wanted you to do it.
I was saying that.
I remember it well.
It's very delicious.
When you're having lunch,
I'll do it.
Before that, I'll try eating lunch.
Try it.
You're going to be interested.
I don't know.
I'll turn the video around.
I'm going to play the video.
On the other hand, do you remember what she said?
I think I remember.
If you forget it and ask what you're doing, that's the saddest thing, right?
On the other hand, it might happen.
It might not happen.
It might happen to Wakana-chan.
It was so delicious.
It was delicious.
There are so many delicious things.
I think this hashtag will continue.
I think I'll eat it in the future.
That's good.
I think I'll eat it in various places.
I wonder how many times we can ask for deliciousness.
It's really just a reward for us.
That's good.
I spend a day as a reward.
Thank you very much.
Please try it.
Thank you very much for the many emails.
Let's introduce the request for lunch time.
This is from Marumaruchi and Tammy.
Thank you very much.
We are a couple and have been supporting Riella.
We were able to participate in the first time in Nihigata Park last June.
My wife is Nagi-chan and Ren-chan.
I wanted to arrange the clothes for my husband myself.
That's amazing.
We would like to request the song Prime Adventure that we listened to for the first time.
The memories of that time will come back.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of people who imitate the costumes.
There are also children who listen to it.
It's cute.
I'm glad.
Please remember the live performance of that time and listen to it.
Prime Adventure with Riella
Riella
Love Live Super Star
Yui-chan's Lunchtime Broadcasting Station
Geirashi!
Tell us what you think
Hamburg is also Agree!
Like Hanon-chan's Hamburg is also Agree
I think this is good
I might be the only one, but I like this
I will send you something
We are against that mail
Agree or Disagree
If anyone of us
If you judge it as Agree
The mail is approved as Agree Mail
The mail is approved as Agree
This is my first time
Do you think the first mail will be Agree?
I think the first one will be Agree
Then
Imoja will go
Imoja
Let's go
I got it from Pua Pua
I like it
Shinasina's fried potato is also good
Crispy fried potato is also delicious
But I'm a Shinasina
The taste of the salt that has been matured
And the gentle texture
It becomes a habit
I'm a Shinasina
I might get lost
I see
Shinasina's fried potato is also good
It's not Agree
Both are Agree
Let's go
This mail is
Agree
This mail is approved as Agree Mail
The first one is the best
Agree
It's delicious
Which do you like?
What about Imoja?
I don't know if it's right to say Shinasina
I like Hokuhoku
I see
It's a thick one
Rather than crispy
I like potato
Agree
I like that taste
What about you two?
I like the finished version
I think so too
Delicious
It's delicious when you eat it
The salt is
It's delicious
The fried potato talk
Imoja is delicious
Imoja
I heard for the first time
Then
Next is the big sister
From Yuuji
Thank you
I love you
I was very busy during school break
I was very noisy
I was very noisy during school break
The moment when the classroom is quiet
At my school
The angel said
Thank you
Can I say something?
It was very difficult for the first person to say
It was about 4 seconds
It was quite long
It was 4 seconds
It wasn't the amount of the first person
I felt like I was rolling it back from the middle
It became a little fun
What do you mean?
I understood it completely
Maybe it's break time
It's like that during class
Everyone was talking
We also have break time
Even though everyone was talking
It was just a moment
What happened?
I understand
I see
Did you decide?
This is difficult
Aya-chan
Aya-chan is lost
Aya-chan lost
Aya-chan was busy reading
I'm biting now
I'm chewing
Can you do it?
This mail is
Agree
It's dangerous
Sayurin is dis-agree
Since the two agreed
Agree mail is approved
I want to hear the reason for dis-agree
Yuji-san said
That the angel passed
At my school
It's like a ghost
I don't have a good impression
I grew up without it
I feel like
I see
Why do you agree?
When there was a moment like this at school
After the scene
Everyone laughed
It was fun
Good
What about Aya-chan?
Aya-chan
I don't have that song at school
Anyway
Everyone
It's a school that doesn't talk during the break
Everyone is studying for the short test
I'm serious
I don't talk
I don't remember that
Riela's makeup
I thought
At that moment
I like it
When music is playing
I like to hear only music
I like that time
I like that time too
Agree
Why is that?
I'm curious
What do you mean?
It's a break time
There are many classes
At the time of group work
The group
Each group is talking
For a moment
What is this?
It became very quiet
There was a moment
So fast
It's so good
I want to say this
Isn't it cute to say I like it?
I understand
I want to say I like it
I like it
Cute
Have fun at school
Have fun
Thank you
Please send us
What you like
That's all
Love Live Super Star
This is Riela
Riela
Love Live Super Star
Announcement
Blue Ray Information
Love Live Super Star
Fandisk
Hokkaido is a big movie
TV anime
Special part
Riela's song
Where are you going
Hokkaido
Riela's video
Please check
Seventh Live
Kanagawa Park Ticket
Fast forward
The application period
Until 23.59 on Sunday, July 7
Don't forget to apply
Music information
Seventh Live theme song
Open the Gate Riela version
It is on sale
Seventh Live Aichi Park
Fast forward
Please take a look
In addition, on official YouTube
MV of Open the Gate
Please check it out
Riela Club Information
Currently at Riela Club
Behind the scenes of the live
Behind the scenes of the MV
Content is being released
Digital photo frame
It is limited until the end of November
Please take a look
Goods Information
Riela's Happy Vol.2
Official Kanbatch Vol.5
The reservation is being accepted
Birthday present
Riela's Happy Vol.3
Seiza Motif
The reservation is being accepted
Today, November 25th
Tuesday, 23.59
Please take a look
Cute
Adults
Happy
It stands out
People who take pictures
It's a festival
It's cute
You can wear it in the venue
Happy
It's cold on the way
I'm wearing an outer
I can change it in winter
It's light and good
It seems to be easy to carry
Cute
This is a limited production
Only those who have reserved can get it
Please check the details
Love Live series
It is an announcement from the official card game
Booster pack Sapphire Moon
It is on sale
From Riela members
Sumire-chan, Ren-chan, Shiki-chan, Tomari-chan
As a new illustration card
It is recorded
Please get it
And next year, February 28th, Saturday
Love Live series 15th anniversary
Booster pack anniversary
2026 will be released
This product
February 21st, Saturday
It will be held on the 22nd, Sunday
It will be sold in advance at the Love Card Gratification Festival
Please get it at the venue
Also Love Card Gratification Festival
On the stage on February 21st, Saturday
From Riela, Date Sayari and
Sakakura Sakura will be on stage
Please look forward to this
Next is the performance information
This week, November 29th, Saturday
From 23 o'clock
Riela will be on NHK Venue 101
It is the first appearance as 11 people
And open the gate
It will be the first time to show on TV
Everyone, please pay attention to the costumes and dance
Do not miss
Next, next week, December 2nd, Tuesday
From 18 o'clock
Radio Nippon Rokumaru Tribe
Chisato Arashi, Nako Misaki
Yui Na, Yuin Margarete
I will perform live
The performance is scheduled at about 19 o'clock
Please check it out
The details of all the information announced this time
Love Live Super Star Riela
Official X Love Live Super Star
Please check from the official homepage
That was the notice
Love Live Super Star
It's time to say goodbye
Here is the next broadcast information
Next time, December 2nd, Tuesday
The 249th broadcast scheduled for Tuesday
The guest
Pei and Naomi
I will welcome
How was today's broadcast?
Sister
How was it?
It's been a long time
Second time
It was very fun
Christmas
Will you really call me?
Oh no
I still remember
I remember
Do you want to exchange presents with Riela?
I want to
Valentine and Halloween
I was doing it for a while
I was doing it
By the way, Rieha was wearing it
On the day of shooting
Everyone brought sweets
I was doing it
I want to do it again
Will you do it?
Will you call me?
Natsumi-chan can plan
On the contrary
Natsumi-chan
Everyone is involved
Oni Natsu channel
As a YouTube project
I want to do this
I want to do it
Please
Cute
Please come
Thank you
This time Love Live Super Star
Riela-chan is here
The opponent is
Shibuya Kano Yaku Tatesa Yari
Onitsuka Tomari Yaku Sakakura Sakura
Onitsuka Natsumi Yaku Emori Aya
See you
Thank you for your viewing