Note: there's really bad audio lag for the first entire half of this stream.
Not much I can do about it, sorry :/
Welcome to ProSeka AfterTalk "This story continues with hope" Edition!
Was that alright? Sorry, I bumped the mic a bit.
Good evening!
"Kon-more!"
This is Mayu Yoshioka, voice of Haruka Kiritani from MMJ!
Thanks for having me on.
In this edition of ProSeka Aftertalk,
we'll look back at this event while covering messages you, the fans, have sent in.
This time, we'll be covering the "This story continues with hope" event.
Have you been enjoying the event and the story, everyone?
What do you all think?
I've personally been really looking forward this one too.
Today, especially, since I get to hear everyone's thoughts.
We've gathered your comments for this Aftertalk sent through email as well as the submissions channel on the Discord .
Thank you to everyone who mailed in.
We'd like to go over some of them in our program today.
We got so many, but unfortunately due to time we're only going to be able to cover a few,
but we do appreciate each and every one.
Also, if you have any thoughts on today's program,
please post them on X with #ProSekaAftertalk.
We'll also be watching the YouTube chat.
Please keep all the messages coming.
I'll also check the Aftertalk hashtag after the program today.
so please make sure to post there as well. We'd appreciate it!
Alright then, I'll be sure to keep up with the YouTube chat,
but we've got a lot to get through today.
I also came with a lot to talk about, but—
〣 ( ºΔº ) 〣
I brought my notebook for today, but I forgot it in the green room!
Guess I'll ask one of the makeup artists to help me get it later.
Okay, we'll start off by talking about the "This story continues with hope" event story.
How did you feel about the story, everyone?
Let's revisit the highlights of this story together while going over some of the messages you’ve sent in.
First up, from "Mirin"-san?
Thank you for the message, Mirin-san.
"Yoshioka-san, 'kon-more'". Kon-more!
"I loved your firm yet clear voice."
Thank you.
"I feel like this event showed a lot more of the deliberation than usual."
"This time, MMJ were working together with the other idol groups like Cheer Day towards the same goal."
"And by working together—"
Mindblown emoji
It's here!
They brought it over for me. We'll go over this later.
Sorry for interrupting your message.
"This time, MMJ were working together with the other idol groups like Cheer Day towards the same goal."
"Being able to see everyone talking things through, exchanging ideas, and going back and forth on different approaches,
"and through it all, Haruka-chan taking charge to get things done was really cool to see."
"This was another great chance to see Haruka taking the initiative."
"It was fun to see her work together with all the other idols."
"Do your best at the LumiGra finals, MMJ!"
Thank you for the message.
I guess that's the abbreviation, "LumiGra".
Shortened from "Lumina Grand Prix."
I think that's the first time I've seened it shortened like that.
Have I seen that?
Either way, thank you very much.
Appreciate you writing in, Mirin-san.
That's right, we are at a really important point in the story. This is the stage right before the finals.
This is the stage where we finally get to see everyone's votes.
I know everyone had big expectations for this moment.
Like, I did see lots of people saying "oh boy here it comes..."
But in the end,
I feel like they're in great shape to tackle whatever comes next.
"I want Haruka as my boss."
Oh yeah.
"First time seeing 'LumiGra—'" oh, interesting.
Looks like that's how some are saying it.
Actually yeah, that does sound like what people might call it.
LumiGra sounds right. Makes sense.
Alright, we have one more message to go over today.
From "Yukki"-san, thank you. That's "Yukki" in katakana.
"Kon-more, Yoshioka-san!"
Kon-more!
"I felt like this story represented a culmination of MMJ's recent efforts."
"Seeing the formerly competing idol groups join forces,"
"not just to impress the viewers,"
"but prioritizing bringing hope to their audience, was really moving."
"On top of that, we saw Haruka confronting some of her past trauma as a way of getting through their challenges."
"I thought that was extremely cool."
"And at the end, they were able to get 2nd overall in qualifiers,"
"and I was yet again moved."
"Yoshioka-san, I'm looking forward to all the ways you'll continue to portray Haruka-chan."
Thank you very much.
Yeah, definitely. I so relieved they managed to get 2nd.
But waiting for that announcement was really nerve-wracking, wasn't it?
Hearing everyone else get announced.
Actually, isn't them announcing the number of votes before the group super realistic too?
Isn't it kind of interesting how everyone gets two votes for this event?
You just have to choose just one, you can go "these guys" and "these guys".
That's a very forgiving system, and seeing the number of comments too,
it really allowed them to see exactly how much attention they were actually getting.
Makes for a pretty interesting event.
In real life, you don't really see too many of these kind of nation-wide idol competitons,
I found myself thinking "what would this look like if it happened in real life?" a lot.
"I voted for MMJ and ReLight! (jk)"
Ah, who would I vote for?
Yeah, I mean, there were a few units mentioned that didn't directly show up in the story.
I liked wondering what those groups might have been like.
I think someone mentioned, you can't use both your votes on the same unit.
Think it was mentioned somewhere in the story.
Oh yeah! "The moment 4th place was announced, someone knew they were going home."
Hearing that not everyone in their group was making it through must have been tough.
I get that...
That other unit "Aimu" did end up passing.
I wonder what they're like...
Getting 2nd is huge win for them.
In the first episode, before the event, Haruka talked about how MMJ should expect a certain position based on the current online rankings.
I totally get that, trying to get a feel out how the final rankings might end up.
MMJ were definitely checking out all the rankings and predictions on the internet.
All of that might have an influence on their production direction after this event
Proactively seeking out all that information online, and then deciding on a strategy from there;
isn't that really mature of them? Especially since they're high schoolers!
How the heck can high schoolers be that smart?
Thank you so much for your message, Yukki-san.
We only got to read these 3 messages,
I have so much I want to talk about too, so I'm going to take over a bit now.
Alright, here we go.
The Lumina Grand Prix was,
for all you ProSeka users, it must definitely feel like it's been going on for a while!
After all, the story is shown just bit by bit.
I totally get people saying "When are we gonna get to the finals?" or "I wanna see what happens next!"
But actually, I kind of want to just stay right here in this little gap right now,
after all the hard work in the qualifiers,
right between passing the qualifiers and before the finals start.
Even I was really nervous about the qualifiers.
So when I heard this would be a Haruka focus event, I was like "ahhhhh"
I'm covering this part of the story as a Haruka focus?
And especially for Haruka,
we'll go more in depth later,
but it's very obvious that there's a big wall between Haruka and Hiiragi-san, ReLight's producer.
Something Haruka can't really ignore.
And the fact that she has to come face to face with home once more...
Last time she...
fought with him? Not quite "fought", but...
Last time she confronted him face to face,
it almost felt like this standoff between grown-ups in the corporate world.
After which, Haruka had this really down look,
like "I don't know how we're going to get through this..."
but I think she grew from that. And so when she went to face Hiiragi-san again,
I was wondering what exactly the confrontation might look like this time.
But considering they're now working with ReLight in the stage right before finals,
I'm really glad she got such reassuring advice.
That feeling of security and strength from know that Hiiragi-san has their backs.
Knowing he's this big, influential figure...
She must feel so relieved knowing "ah, Hiiragi-san has our backs."
You could feel that coming from each and every word that he said.
I think Haruka does truly have respect and admiration for him,
but at the same time, she knows that someday, she'll have to beat him.
That acknowledgement, I feel, was more or less the focus of Episode 6.
He's scary, that Hiiragi-san.
It's like, the more you rely on him, the more he feels like he's going to be a threat later on.
So it makes me really wonder, what kind of team was ASRUN back when Hiiragi-san and Haruka were working together?
So Haruka's main battle was with Hiiragi-san,
but that's wrapped in the wider context of preparing for the event for the cram school students.
And all the other teams going to their own various locations.
Arisawa-san's...
ideas? As a former idol.
Hearing her perspective on "this is what I wish I could have done for them".
Even if she's retired, she sees the idols of today and thinks,
"I want ensure this generation has that strength to deliver hope."
Ensuring the idols of this world have that... "allure?"
I think that's awesome.
I mean come on, having that kind of expectation from this legendary idol,
you guys sure have your work cut out for you.
"The story got me really fired up."
Yeah that one was good—
"Kiritani really is dangerous, getting me fired up like that."
I really like that line.
For event recordings, we usually only get to see the script.
We don't usually record together, so I only get to see the full conversations in-game.
But even just looking at the script, I knew that scene with Hiiragi-san and Arisawa-san was going to be great.
That was just...
that was too much.
I was actually going through the story mostly to get to that part.
Of course, I did want to see the rest of MMJ's scenes too.
But that scene was specifically one I wanted to burn into my memory.
Ah. Looks like the audio's a bit out of sync so we're going to pause the stream momentarily.
Please standby while we fix the issue.
Alright then, we've been talking a lot about Chapter 6,
but let's talk about what happens in the other chapters.
Like the excursion live.
Two whole weeks for that— if you think about the fact that the whole Lumina Grand Prix leading up to this was less than that,
isn't that pretty crazy?
They've all had to shuffle teams,
and then learn each others' songs,
and if you think about the fact that they could do that in just a few days,
you can tell everyone's gotta have a really young memory.
It's amazing how fast these practice parts go.
Especially with how fast they must have to learn new songs.
Minori's mentioned that she's good at imitating choreo,
but for other members who aren't so good at that having to learn so quickly—
not just the choreo, but the singing parts, the rest of the formation,
and bringing their own originality while keeping respect for the original?
Isn't that way too much to think about?
Aren't they just so talented?
I need to start learning from them.
They're super impressive.
Actually, there's one thing I saw that I couldn't stop laughing at.
The comments. For all the recent MMJ events, you sometimes see the stream viewers' comments pop up.
Are you sure you all aren't the ones writing them?
Actually I think I've seen them before,
but I feel like there's actually a writer specifically for those comments.
"They're always really accurate."
People are probably like "wait, did they steal that from my tweet?"
"You got me." Hahaha.
Like, are they just taking those comments from online,
or are they recruiting the actual commenters?
I always find it super funny to think about how accurate they are.
Hmm, but I think that's just one part of how realistic these stories have been feeling.
In each story, I always like thinking about,
"which comments are the ones I'm most likely to have said?"
Of course, there are also times where those comments are actually spoken in the story.
Any time the fans themselves show up.
Like, for some of the lines from MMJ fans or Cheerful＊Days fans, you'd think;
"Ahh, I'd definitely say something like that."
Ah, and you know, I'm glad we don't hear this as much nowadays,
we don't see it as much, but earlier,
there were lots of comments like "MMJ? Who?"
Especially for Minori...
people saying things like "I've been following the other members, but..."
there were... there were some pretty tough comments out there.
But if you compare it to now, don't you think they've come so far?
All the comments are like "Go MMJ!"
I'm so happy for them.
"The comments are so much nicer now."
Yeah, not only nicer, but...
they must be so glad that they're really well known now.
Like they've even been featured on TV now.
"Comments do have real power, don't they?"
"It's their hard work". 100%, it's MMJ hard work paying off.
Everyone's feels super welcomed by the comments now.
They're not worried reading them anymore.
Actually, nowadays...
I feel like if MMJ was to solo stream,
the comment section would have a pretty different vibe.
Of course, there were fans who have been with them all the way since then,
and I feel that part wouldn't change,
I bet there'd be lots of comments like "Hey, I'm new here!" Hahaha.
"I just came from learning about MMJ at the Lumina Grand Prix!"
Yeah, that'd be great.
"I'm originally a Cheerful＊Days fan, but got interested in MMJ, so I joined their stream!"
Something like that hahaha.
Hahaha "Newbies! Welcome!"
Everyone'd be like "Welcome!" "Welcome!" Hahaha.
"Oh, you're a first-timer?" Yeah I could see people saying that haha.
"Welcome all first-timers!"
All the veterans might say that too.
Oh, yeah. "I came from watching the LumiGra."
Wait, what if LumiGra actually becomes term official staff use?
Just kidding. It's just me calling it that.
So with that...
That was a bit of a recap on the story as a whole,
but now,
let's set aside the Chapter 8 discussion.
There's actually a specific scene I wanted to watch.
I've chosen a scene I wanted to discuss.
As you might expect, it's from Chapter 6.
Please enjoy.
I was thinking Chapter 8 too,
but I would start crying if we watched that.
Alright, that was Chapter 6 of the story.
I mentioned it a little before we watched, but that conversation between Haruka and Hiiragi-san...
I thought the bravery Haruka showed to directly confront him one-on-one was absolutely incredible.
Knowing that they already faced off during Haruka’s previous focus event, but even then...
still going to meet him again like that...
it shows that she has a very different mindset now.
I thought that was really cool of her.
For that confrontation scene, we actually...
we actually did two takes.
I think they ended up using the second take.
After going through the first take—
I mean, for Haruka to go up to Hiiragi-san, this really distinguished producer,
she would definitely have some nerves. Maybe feeling like "I don't know what to do next".
So I talked with more of a wavering, unsure tone, like she was kind of just casually going to ask for advice.
But they said, "no, this is—"
"Let Haruka fight for this."
"With Hiiragi-san."
Like, "To get that advice out of him, you need to go in there and hunt for it."
But that means you really need to approach him like that.
"Fight him on this; say that we need to cooperate in order ensure we pass."
I got that direction,
and I was like "wow, sounds fun, let's try it."
And so that's how the second take turned out.
Of course, I feel that one focal point point of this story is Haruka taking these small steps forward on her journey as a producer herself.
I really hope that came through clearly in this scene with Hiiragi-san.
That's right.
The sound producers and directors have all this time,
little by little building this character of Haruka alongside me.
So hearing them say more things like, "Maybe it's time for Haruka to show a bit of her strength here," makes me really happy.
That particularly comes through in this Chapter 6, so I really wanted to watch it with everyone here.
Yep.
That's how I felt.
Sorry, my earring fell off.
So with that...
Right, so we'll leave the Chapter 6 discussion at that, and
time for the card art, right?
Ah, is that right?
We're gonna talk about Chapter 8.
Chapter 8...
I mean...
first and foremost, congrats on passing, MMJ!!
Big congrats.
Honestly, I thought that just making finals would be great,
but to get second place? Aren't they so amazing now?
So 1st place was Cheerful＊Days,
and MMJ got 2nd.
After 3rd and 4th were announced and there were only 2 teams left, hearing Haruka not wanting to give up—
I was gonna cry.
She was so cool in that scene.
Even as the other members were losing hope,
she was like...
ah, I'm gonna cry.
But yeah, that was just so good.
Seeing her say "We can't give up" like that...
And then her being the first to go up and say "Thank you" as their representative....
That "Thank you" honestly made me burst into tears.
Of course, this is all Haruka. I’m just speaking as her,
but man, everything about this scene just makes me just so glad.
Man...
For that "Thank you"... let's see,
I think we ended up doing two takes.
For the first one, I felt like I had to stay composed and speak very straightforwardly.
But they said, "Maybe it's okay let a little more emotion out."
"This is a big moment in the story after all."
I thought "You're so right!"
So I went for it again, and it came out amazingly.
I was like "I'm crying again even the second time around?"
It really was a "thank you" from the bottom of the heart.
Ah, right, Hikarin.
She got a respectable 5th place,
but only the top 4 moved on from the qualifiers,
so unfortunately that means this is the end of Hikarin's dream, at least for now.
But she said she believes that everyone will continue to shine their best in her place.
Actually, I think Hikarin's unique style really helped everyone in this stage.
Especially Minori.
Seeing her leave even after building that bond with everyone is definitely sad,
but seeing everyone's hopes and dreams come together,
that really made this stand out as a "team" effort for this final qualifier round.
Also, on a personal note, I was so happy when Hikarin’s character visual was finally added!
I've always been super curious about her.
I had an idea just based on her voice,
but finally seeing her, she's just super cute, right?
There's just so much going on in her design.
I really just wanted to learn more about her.
"I hope they get to perform together again one day!"
I’m also curious about what kind of songs Hikarin actually sings.
She's so cute...
So, we'll move on to card art discussion in a bit,
and in Airi's? Yeah, in Airi's card, Hikarin shows up a bit.
Yeah, I get it. When you build up a "persona" too much, it gets really tough.
Keeping up a persona is definitely a lot.
She'll definitely get over it one day.
But it's because she overcame that struggle that we can see Hikarin as she is today.
I'm really rooting for her too.
And as for what lies ahead in the finals...
it's finally coming. Remember, this has all just been the qualifiers.
It's only gonna get tougher from here. Just four teams left standing.
I'm excited to see exactly what's in store for them going forward.
So with that, let's move on to the event cards.
Alright, then, to start us off...
Haruka-sensei...
Here it is.
This was super cool, wasn't it?
When her banner event was announced,
I felt like I needed to fix my posture
and stand up straight.
I remember grinning to myself, like "nah, she'd win."
Hiiiii!
I was like "Hiii!"
Thank you for the art.
Yeah, guys, look at this.
Hiiii!
I mean come on...
Oh, you can't see what I'm pointing at.
These gloves. They're the kind that aren't— full?
They don't come down all the way.
What do you call those?
I mean, these were like—
These look amazing on our Haruka-san.
These are great.
Gotta remember to talk about the whole costume
after these little detailed parts.
And those sparkles are also so pretty.
Gotta keep moving on. Else we'll be here all day.
Alright.
Yeah, this is the one I was talking about.
Hikarin and Airi in the cram school.
These two were also really cute~
Kind of looks like they're part of a talk show.
Definitely looks like they're
ready to liven the atmosphere.
So cute. Actually, when I first saw her character sprite, Hikarin was a bit shorter than I was expecting,
but I think that makes her cuter.
Airi's also really good here, isn't she? And then...
So pretty here too...
Like this?
Yeah, try rotating her straight up like this.
Think it looks really good.
Lighting is so pretty, too...
And the illumination from the back, like
Kasaaa. So good, right?
So detailed.
Right, gotta keep looking forward.
Otherwise you'll only get a view of my hair.
Ah, Len-kun too.
This was so good!
Oh look, there’s a little penguin on her notebook.
So cute.
We know Haruka loves her penguins.
She even has one here.
Wait a sec, I think she even has a penguin thing
on her pencil case.
Actually, I think Len's sprite has...
his old costume? Can you call it that?
The one he started with.
But seeing his new outfit in a card art like this is great.
And here's cool Len.
Beautiful. Fantastic.
It's too much, I can't even look at him directly.
Hiii!
Moving on...
Ah this was also so goodー
wait a sec, is this really only a 3-star?
Just a 3-star?
Ah, so cute, so pretty, just as always.
She's so dazzling. Thank you.
And the trained. Are you sure this is a 3-star?
Is this really a 3-star?
I don't even know anymore.
And finally Minori-chan.
So pretty.
So for this set, the card arts have this night sky theming.
They're wearing mostly black,
and in this card, you can really see the outfit's outline more clearly.
And I'm really glad to see the green under the outfit.
MMJ's color. Nice.
Looks beautiful.
Alright, so that was all the cards.
We also have a comment about the outfits from the
card illustration production team we'd like to read.
"In this story, MMJ had to work together with the other idol groups to face a new challenge in an unfamiliar environment."
The story revolves around Haruka taking active role
for the sake of her team's success.
Drawing inspiration from the joint live from the story,
and laser-focusing on our design,
we aimed to portray a striking MMJ against a midnight sky.
To achieve this, we chose a black fabric as the base,
adorned with star-shaped accessories for a simple yet eye-catching design.
The design comes together for a "starry night" theme while remaining distinct from those of Leo/need.
Since the outfit is composed of 80-90% black fabric,
to avoid looking tacky, we used velvet and satin textures to create a high-end luster.
And with lots of detailed accents, we wanted to give MMJ a new, more grown-up impression with these outfits.
Ah, I see. You know what velvet is?
It's what those really nice-feeling carpets are made of.
The ones that you feel like want to keep touching.
Using that kind of stuff to make idol outfits is...
Velvet's pretty common in winter-style clothing,
It works especially well around now like in December.
it's looks really lustrous and high quality when it catches the light.
Same with satin.
Satin gives off more of a really nice, bright sparkle when the light hits it,
but velvet has this surprising sense of weight and depth to it.
It has this really nice way of taking in the light and reflecting it out.
But wait, isn't it amazing how they're able to portray specific fabrics through just the art?
Right?
This right here is where the attention to detail in MMJ outfits really stands out.
Oh whoops, we're a bit over time.
Are we good to go?
Aaaaahhhh I'm gonna cry~
It's time to watch the 3DMV.
The...
even if you've just listened to the song, seriously, watch the 3DMV too.
Do it.
I mean, I guess we're watching it right now.
So moving on, let's watch the 3DMV created for this event's song thanks to the work of Karasuya Sabou-san.
and then take some time to talk about the song itself.
So without further ado, onto the video.
Enjoy.
So good...
That was Polar Star.
So good!
I love everything about it!
Eh, ah, umm, yeah right here.
Right here, their expressions each change one by one.
And this is from the side of the stage, fans normally can't see them from there.
But RIGHT HERE THE SHOT FROM BEHIND INTO THAT LOOK
Right?
Right there!
This is what everyone's talking about, right? That part right there.
So that's what you all mean.
Yeah yeah, right there.
Ahhhh way too good.
I mean come on. The quality of the MVs nowadays is just so good.
Right? They've come so far.
Look look, right here.
Hold up— right here—
Hahaha!
They look so good in sync like this—
yeah this part!
THIS PART TOO
Ah, the night sky scenery, so pretty. Beautiful.
The— ah! Look at the shooting stars! So good.
And wait for it— this part!
Right here!
Hahaha!
And then they change formation,
yep.
Now each of them looks up, it's like the steps—
Then here—
Look, look, it's really subtle.
Come on, come on...
And then they all as one—
Fantastic.
Hahaha!
This part was so good!
The first time I watched the video, I was like "What's that up there?"
Back when the 3DMVs were just the on-stage dancing,
they did a great job of showing what the whole performance might have looked like.
I definitely loved those back then,
but the recent ones are incredible!
I mean, they're like whole music videos now.
They tell more of a whole story around the song and lyrics.
And that helps you understand
The lighting was incredible in this one too.
We saw the same thing in the card arts too,
but the illumination from the shooting stars,
plus that thing shining from behind? The halo?
What exactly was it?
It looked amazing!
The whole thing was amazing!
I'm just so hopeless.  I could just watch this forever.
Next time you watch this,
make sure to watch out for Airi blowing you a kiss,
and Haruka's wink.
Anyone oshi-ing them, do check those out.
Ah, so pretty.
The MV makes— the outfits look great in the MV as well.
Ah, I'm done. Watched too many times. Thank you.
Right, we should move onto talking about the song itself.
So speaking of "Polar Star",
Haruka’s evets have definitely had a streak of "cool" songs lately.
So I excited to see what kind of song we'd see this time around.
Looking at the last two songs, I realized that "cool" can come in many varieties,
so I thought, there's a lot more to explore within the range of "cool".
And so I saw this song as representing "cool through beauty".
It was this very refined coolness that felt really fresh.
It blew me away the first time I heard it.
Especially since—
'Haruka's previous songs have very beautiful harmonies.
That's one thing.
But those parts everyone comes in one by one, layering harmonies on top of each other,
All the small steps MMJ are taking in recent events,
leading them to success and seeing real results;
I think this song captures all of that really well.
The harmonies throughout the song are also so good.
They layered together so many different vocal lines to create those.
Both in the parts where they sing individually, and going into each chorus,
Try going back and listen closely to all those different vocal layers.
As for recording, what I tried to keep in mind most during recording...
well first of all, was trying not to cry!
Trying to keep composed during those parts—
We're idols, so our job is to deliver hope.
So we ourselves mustn't cry.
But this is a song reminiscing on all that they've been through,
as well as reaffirming their drive to keep pushing forward.
So there's a balance being struck between this cool, noble feeling,
while at the same time portraying an emotional nostalgia.
That's what makes this song so wonderful.
That's what I wrote. Here in my notebook.
Alright, and also,
there's also going to be a 2DMV.
Says here.
So it'll probably also be a full version.
That'll include parts that you don't see here in the 3DMV,
So try listening to both and seeing what's different.
Specifically, the singing in last chorus might give you a bit of a different impression from the rest.
So please do try listening to it.
On a personal note,
I, Mayu Yoshioka, have actually written lyrics for a song themed around the North Star before.
"Polar Star" meaning the same thing as the North Star.
But "idols" and "stars", especially the North Star,
have this natural connection to each other.
When I was writing those lyrics,
I thought of it taking the meaning of a landmark, as a guiding light for someone.
You know, North Star, the brightest one in the night sky.
And using its meaning as guiding light,
that represents this feeling of "just watch me" or "find me" really well.
That's the North Star.
And that—
For MMJ's story, especially in this Lumina Grand Prix arc,
That really resonates with finding the image of what an idol should be.
I thought, "Yeah, that's part of their story". Think I mentioned this before.
It's part of an idol's storytelling. That story an idol creates together with their fans,
that guiding light is a huge part of it.
The lyricist definitely—
you feel the same thing from the lyrics—
Yeah, definitely emotional.
Sorry for ranting on about a personal experience like this,
but knowing "ah, I wasn't alone in those feelings", it felt really validating.
I'm glad I trusted in my feelings back then.
My feelings towards idols, the way I think about them, and of course everything that Haruka has taught be about me about being an idol—
knowing I wasn't wrong in any of that,
and where MMJ goes from here...
Being able to reaffirm that all to myself all my thoughts on what it means to be an idol,
I think this song really helped me to do that.
I'm grateful we had such wonderful lyrics written for us.
The "stars" theming has been mostly Leo/need up to this point, right?
For ProSeka, they're kind of the owners of that.
I think the other users have all been kind of avoiding the overlap in theme.
But this time