Hi everyone! I'm Misaki Nako, and I play Arashi Chisato
Hi hello! I'm Yabushima Akane, and I play Yoneme Mei
Hi I'm Ookuma Wakana, and I play Wakana Shiki
So, since today, December 30th, the day this video goes out, is already the end of the year...
So fast!
We are doing this as a "take it easy and chat" kind of segment
End of the year?
"End of the year" it said
It's over tomorrow
Liella! Roundtable Memo
There's only 1 day left in the year
"It ends tomorrow" it said
"It ends tomorrow" it said, how do you feel about that?
By the way, what's with this gathering today?
I'm glad you asked!
Yeah
We're gonna keep this pace today, okay? You all good?
Liella! Roundtable Memo
This time, we're taking it easy
Just keep up with me
So us Liella!, about a month for now, January 21, 2026
Love Live! Superstar!!
on sale Wed, Jan 21, 2026
We will be releasing the 6th Live Tour Blu-ray!
And then, just two weeks after that
Love Live! Superstar!!
2026/2/7 (Sat) – 2/8 (Sun) Kanagawa, Yokohama Arena
2026/2/28 (Sat) – 3/1 (Sun) Aichi, Aichi Sky Expo Hall A
Two weeks later??
We'll be holding the 7th Live!
It’s back to back. I can’t believe it.
This time, we're gonna take it easy and look back on our 6th Live moments,
This segment's plan
While we take it easy and look back on our 6th Live Tour memories,
we will get you excited for the Blu-ray release, and then come to the 7th Live keeping that same energy!
get everyone excited for Blu-ray release,
and then have you come to the 7th Live keeping that same energy!
The name of the segment is...
Liella! 6th Live Tour Blu-ray Release Commemoration!
From 6th to 7th:
From 6th to 7th: A Laid-Back Roundtable!
It really is laid back
True. We even wearing our tracksuit now.
Usually for stuff like this, we wear our school uniform and look all proper
Being proper, right?
Doesn't mean we're usually improper or anything
How is it? The comfort of it
The comfort?
But I think some people already have these, right?
Maybe there are people watching this in the tracksuit, too
Yeah, I thought we'd be in our uniforms today...
Liella! Roundtable Memo
We are sorry about this.
So it's tracksuits, huh.
The way you said it, that tone, kinda cracks me up
Apparently, it's already been half a year since the final show (of 6th)
That's right
But it also feels like it's been longer even
We had Revival Live, and day 3 "Connect the Stars" right after
So maybe that's why it feels like time flew by even faster
Dassen: off-topic/tangents
And for this roundtable, some great news!
Going off-topic is totally fine!
Yay! That's how it is
That's unusual
We might go off-topic more than usual,
With tangents and all, we hope you stick with us to the end
Thanks in advance
Please do
Alright then, let's start with our first segment
"So, how was the 6th Live Tour?"
So, how was the 6th Live Tour?
"How was it?"
Are we calling this a "segment"?
We all have plenty of memories from the 6th Live Tour, but...
Segment 1
Following the topic we draw from the prompt box
We'll take it easy and looking back on the 6th
Live Tour as a whole
We'll take it easy and looking back on the live as a whole
And looks like we've got a prompt box, so...
And by doing that, we can chat about it too
Alright then, first up...
Okay, I'll draw one
We have to remember it first
Step one: remembering
What?
"What was the tastiest thing we ate?"
The tastiest thing we ate?
Wait, where did we go first?
Exactly
Right?
I can't remember where we went
Same
Fukuoka
Miyagi... we went there
We went to Miyagi
Uhhh...!
And... that's a wrap
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Miyagi. The End.
We're done here
We're so sorry!
Miyagi, Fukuoka, Tokyo, Aichi?
Osaka?
Osaka was last?
Osaka was the last one
We didn't go to Aichi
Was Tokyo first?
We go there?
We did x 3
"We did," they said
Oh no!
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Correct
Answer
Tokyo Aichi Miyagi Fukuoka Osaka
But wait, I remember about Osaka
In Osaka...
The catering was super fancy every single time
Oh you mean the one where they had hot snacks that kept warm, right?
It was like a convenience store, like-
They had pork buns and tons of stuff--
Takoyaki!
for example... hmm?
Ah! The one where they cooked the takoyaki for us?
Yeah, yeah
Was that in 6th?
Yes, during 6th
Wanaka, right?
Yeah! It was so good--
Ah, takosen!
T/N: Takosen: Osaka street snack where takoyaki
is sandwiched in a big crispy shrimp/rice cracker
(senbei/ebi-sen)
That's right!
Everyone was like, "Wakana! Wakana!"
The takosen keep sold out, it was so popular
Almost all the time, it's already gone before you know it
They prepare a lot of it, but...
Everyone's like "So good! So good!"
Then it's gone in no time, and it happens a lot.
That was my first time ever in my life eating takosen
Never had it at a festival or something? Like a food stall?
Maybe because I'm from the countryside, we didn't have it
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Familiarity in Kanto Area:
weak
What do you mean?
Yeah, we don't
Huh, you didn't?
No, no.
Yeah we don't, right?
Takosen is pretty rare, you know...
Like, that kind of thing is usually...
Yeah, I mean...
Not really something you get at the actual venue
What about tamasen?
T/N: Tamasen: a Japanese festival snack where
a fried egg (tamago) plus sauce/toppings like tenkasu
are put on or sandwhiched in a large cracker (senbei/ebi-sen).
Tamasen?
What is arimasen?
Huh??
Um, it's like--
Takosen is like, that big cracker with it sandwiched in, right?
tamasen
But tamasen is where they plop a fried egg right on top of the cracker
And then sauce--
So the egg is there-
Yup!
With sauce and tenkasu and stuff
It's called tamasen, and it's hard to eat
Nuance: It's messy and quite hard to eat
Apparently you can't really get it there
We don't!
They don't have it
Sounds good, though
Then, what do you have at festivals in your place?
Like in Nako's Kansai Area you've got takosen and tamasen
T/N: Hashimaki ("chopstick roll")
There's also hashimaki
What is hashimaki?
Like, it's wrapped around chopsticks
Let's move on
What do you two even have, then?
Wrapped around chopstick?
Wrapped... *giggling*
It's kinda like okonomiyaki but wrapped
Not us being wrapped, though
Wait, am I wrong?
Hashimaki
No, you're right! You're right!
So it's like "wrapped okonomiyaki"?
It's rolled up like, swirl swirl swirl
It's like okonomiyaki, but on a stick
No, we don't have that in Saitama
We don't!
I honestly thought hashimaki and tamasen and takosen were everywhere in Japan,
so it's surprising to me
Nope!
They actually might not be that common
You just assume things that you have are "normal"
They really don't have it at all--
Baby Castella
They do have that
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Baby Castella (nationwide)
See? Exactly
Baby Castella do exist there. Yeah, sorry.
We have baby castella, okay
Sorry. They do, yeah
How about some sweets and stuff? You like them?
Sweets?
Yea
Go ahead, eat. Ah-?
Huh?!
Ueehh...
Liella! Roundtable Memo
What kind of reaction is that?
Ueehh... Seriously?
For New Year's...
Yeah
Feels very winter-y
This is like, peak winter, isn't it?
Ah, this, this one
This one is good. It melts.
You're gonna say "melty," aren't you?
Yeah. Like, it melts in your mouth like snow, right?
Alright, moving on.
A story that you can only tell now, a happening
T/N: Happening (ハプニング) a common word used in
Japanese variety show. It means "incident" or
"mishap"
"unexpected moment".
Do you remember?
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Asking-it-like-a-question style
You asking us?
Because it's "now"
"Something that we can say now"?
"Something that we can say now"
But you know, about this "happening"...
On "Dazzling Game", which we performed on center stage around the middle of the show,
depending on the venue, there were times when,
while taking it off...
I feel like every now and then, I'd take it off too late, or I'd end up leaving the outer attire on the stage
But like, no one totally failed to take it off, right?
Nobody couldn't take it off
There were just tiny delays, like a split second
Honestly, I still think it's a miracle we managed to pull that off
That moment is pretty nerve-wrecking
Very, very nerve-wracking
Like, "I'm definitely taking this off"
Weird thing to say, but in that moment, all I'm thinking about is taking it off
Like "Here it comes, here it comes!"
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Performance < Taking it off
If you only hear this part, it sounds kinda weird
Hmm anything else?
You know, sometimes there isn't even time to drink water, but... I saw others drinking a ton too
Ah, I get that
Right? You get it
Liella! Roundtable Memo
The other members chugging water
You can't see clearly
You can't see clearly, the name (in each bottles)
Right!
So I’m like, “Whatever, I’ll just drink for now.”
That's fine
Yeah. it's better to just drink
They were drinking so much
And honestly, Shiki-chan,
you know how you put those name stickers on top of the bottle caps?
Isn't it kind of hard to tell? Like, the colors...
I can't see anything
There is like a tiny bit of light on stage when you get a chance to drink water
It's lit when you can drink, but
with lighting that dim, you can't tell the difference between those colors at all
True
Mine's red, so that's why it might be easier to tell
Oh, it shows up really clearly
Yeah, it shows up clearly
But in that darkness, Kanon, Kinako, and Chisato look like the same color
Yeah they all look the same
Maybe it's just that, you know...
Maybe we were lucky and there were not too many similar ones
Huh, what about Natsumi?
But red and pink are pretty different.
Pink is lighter, though.
Oh, really?
Okay, last prompt
Let's do our last one
"Something you did especially to prepare for this live"
"Special"?
Something you did specially...
Something special you did?
I didn't even cut my hair, so I got nothing "special"
Didn't cut it. Yeah.
You said you were gonna cut it, right?
Right?!
Huh? You two are so close
Ever since I said I'd cut it, I still haven't
Still haven't been able to set a date, so I 'm still "planning to"
Right. Wasn't that a while ago when you said it?
Huh, so you want to cut it?
I do!
I want to, but the timing...
I'm very professional, you know
Not many say that about themselves
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Professionalism (high)
Probably nobody
If I cut it on some random ordinary day, it might feel different, you know?
"Random ordinary days," huh
Like, you know
It's better if it's for something
Yeah, like if there's an event or something, it feels right to cut it then
Yeah, at this point, yeah (like showing your milestone)
Then later, when you see it in photos, you're like, "Ah!"
Otherwise, it won't feel the same
True, I also think about the timing a lot too
But you know, when I am gonna be out in public, I do care about that timing
But when it comes to cutting my hair, once I feel like it, I'll immediately go the next day
Ah but but but I'm the same type, the same
Just go! If you've decided
Right?
I've got a hairstylist who always does my hair,
and they're like, "You absolutely should not cut it"
Eh?
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Her hairstylist strongly refuses
Then you're done for
They're seriously like, "Don't cut it"
It's gotten so long, though, right?
"Don't you dare cut it!!!" they said.
Hold on, you are a hairstylist, right?
By the way, they said that to me too
They do?
I want to go short
I really want to cut it
And they're like, "Nah, don't do it~"
Liella! Roundtable Memo
"Don't do it~"
While touching my hair
I get it, they also said it to me
"Don't do it~" they said
I guess longer hair just has that,
"shine" to it, a kind of lovely and beauty, too
They probably already like, admiring it, you know?
They love it so much to let you cut it
Still, if you ever feel like it, you could just try doing it
Might change your mood, too
True, when you get that sudden urge
"Any routine,
or something you
always do
before live?"
Do you have any routines, or anything you always do before live?
So not just this time, but in general, right?
I don't have one
Hey, that was fast
You just read it (already answer it)
I'm just saying, lately, I don't have one
Every time? I always fix my bangs. Always.
Ah right!
At the very start of the live, your bangs are always perfect
Especially lately. They have grown a bit, though.
Just trimming it around here makes me feel focused
This is my "switch"
Liella! Roundtable Memo
ON-bangs > Nako Switch
Of course there have been live where my bangs is not perfectly on-point
but, as we done more lives
It makes my everyday life easier, but on stage, my view feels clearer somehow
But it's probably not a huge difference, though
It's cute!
It suits you
Thank you. That makes me happy.
What about you, Wakana?
ROUTINE
You know, I'm not really good at doing the same thing every single time--like routinely
Yeah… I can’t do the same thing every day.
Liella! Roundtable Memo
Every day is a bit much…
Every day...
Every day, huh
That's a bit much
But you know how people often say,
“Before every live, I always do this,” right? A lot of people have things like that
I used to think maybe it's better if I had one too,
but after thinking about it a lot…
I realized I’m better off not deciding one
It feels more natural to just go with the flow in that moment
In the end, I didn’t have one
But, you know
It’s not like it’s “bad” that I don’t have one
It’s more like, “Yeah, this works for me.” For my own self
If that works for you, then that’s fine
Also, if I decided “I have to do this,” and then I couldn’t do it, I will be in total panic.
Like it will throw my rhythm off
I totally get that
But I think it's totally fine if someone does have one