The next morning
You two! You did your best this morning! You're great!
Huh? Thank you, Kanon-senpai.
I think it was the same as usual this morning.
It was great because it was done as usual!
I found out later, but the train was late because of the heavy rain, right?
By the way, it was a pretty hard morning.
It was a little late, but I'm glad I didn't get late.
On this day, the Onitsuka-senpai-only high-movement Ushiku-movement machine that Shiki-senpai made was useful.
And the most efficient full-speed travel course that Tomari prepared!
If possible, I don't want to do it again!
Natsumi-chan, you were in a daze, right?
But it's too late, but you two are going from Ushiku to Yuigaoka every day and participating in the morning training!
You're great!
To be honest, it was strange why my sister was in a daze before I entered Yuigaoka.
No, it's actually strange for me, too.
Natsumi-chan, you've been participating in the morning training since you were in the first grade, right?
Hmm...
When I feel like I want to grow more and more as a school idol, my eyes naturally wake up in the morning...
I know! You want to go to school and meet everyone as soon as possible, right?
...
I'm sure that's it!
By joining Riera, my sister started to chase after her dreams with everyone, not for her own sake.
It's a little embarrassing to hear you say that again...
No, it's not embarrassing at all!
It's a wonderful thing to chase after your dreams with everyone!
Yes, I want to make my dream come true with my sister.
...
Yeah! It's fun to dream with everyone!
When I heard what Natsumi-chan said just now, I was moved!
Let's run together right now! Towards that sunset!
...
Did you suddenly say something like Chisato-senpai?
I don't think Chisato-senpai will say it either. And it's noon now, so there's no sunset.
Anyway, let's all start the radio!
Yes!
The Live Super Star!
Riera Shin, Toma Kano, and Natsuu!
Hello, everyone!
I'm Sayarin, the voice of Kano Chibuya, and I'm Sayari Tate.
I'm Sakuchan, the voice of Tomori Onitsuka, and I'm Sakura Sakakura.
I'm Emory, the voice of Natsumi Onitsuka, and I'm Aya Emory.
We are Riera!
Nice to meet you!
This time, my sister came, so I'll see you in another summer!
It's been a long time!
It seems that it's been four months.
The last time I came was around July.
I woke up in the fall and came in the winter.
It's nice!
It's nice to have a winter from summer!
I hope you have a good time!
Let's have fun!
Thank you!
This Sunday, November 23rd, is the day of the labor camp.
There are three classes on the weekend on Monday.
It seems that there are two classes on November.
That's great!
I wonder if everyone wants to go somewhere.
Please take Riera's members to the camp!
Let's go!
Where do you want Natsumi to take you?
I want Natsumi to take me to the camp!
It's been a long time, so I'm going to the camp!
I'm going to the camp!
Did you overcome your fear?
I'm still a little scared.
If everyone takes me there, I may be able to overcome it.
It's no doubt!
What about Kano-senpai?
Kano-senpai...
Kano-senpai!
In the place of the bag...
What's the place of the bag?
Bag cafe!
Please go out as much as possible.
Outdoor!
I'm not going to be in the video, so please take Kano instead of me.
What about Tomo-chan?
Tomo-chan is like a aquarium.
I like it.
I'll be happy if you show me your jellyfish.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next Monday, November 24, is Hazuki Rin-chan's birthday.
Happy birthday, Rin-chan.
I hope you can celebrate it on that day.
Thank you.
Thank you for your continued support.
Love Live Super Star, Yuizou Lunchtime Broadcasting Station, Rie-rashi. Let's Super Start!
Love Live Super Star, Yuizou Lunchtime Broadcasting Station, Rie-rashi.
This is the corner of Yuigaoka Girls High School, Toshibako.
Let's do it together.
Toshibako!
Let's introduce the questions.
First, we have a question from Rie-rashi name, Noppiki-san. Thank you.
Rie-rashi's 7th live theme song, Open the Gate.
We've listened to it a lot.
Thank you.
It expresses the feeling of expectation and anxiety before you take a step because you like the intro.
From there, it opens the door with the band sound that cuts in and jumps into the next world.
It's exactly Open the Gate. Thank you.
Thank you.
Next, we have a question from Rie-rashi name, Paraport-san. Thank you.
We've listened to Open the Gate.
There's a lyrics that makes me want to cry.
It's about aiming for a happy end rather than a happy now.
Happy end is already a positive word, but there's a word that goes beyond it.
There was a shock that turned the fixed concept.
It's still a Rie-rashi-like lyrics that goes on. It's very nice. Thank you.
Thank you.
Next, we have a question from Rie-rashi name, Hanakaneko-san. Thank you.
We've listened to the full version of Open the Gate.
Thank you.
As the title says, it's a song full of excitement that opens a new door and challenges.
There are a lot of adventure words in the lyrics.
When I listened to it when I went on a trip or a concert, I thought it would be twice as exciting.
Thank you.
Once again, on November 5th, Rie-rashi 7th Live theme song Open the Gate was released.
Thank you for listening to the full version and listening to the song.
I'm happy.
I'm reading this letter right now, but there's a lot of new discoveries.
I thought that Paraport's positive lyrics were the way to aim for Happy Now rather than Happy End.
Oh, really?
Happy End is positive, but Happy Now is even more so.
I thought that it was also Rie-rashi-like lyrics.
When the lyrics came out for the first time, I thought the lyrics here were really nice.
Happy Now is Rie-rashi-like.
I thought it was a high schooler who could run through the present.
I was looking at your comments on the hashtag.
I saw a lot of people saying that they really like this.
That's right.
It's impressive.
I want to see your mouth.
After all, Rie-rashi-like is a group that has cherished their songs.
I'm so happy that everyone is singing and making their voices sound.
I wonder how far it will go.
I think about it many times.
I can't stop it.
It's going to the future.
That's right.
Isn't this going to cross the axis?
To the 4th dimension.
I want to sing to the 3rd dimension.
I might sing to the 4th dimension in the future.
How did you record the recording?
How did you feel about this song?
Memories?
Did you record this part?
When I recorded it, it was a song that was playing all the time.
Rie-rashi-like was a cool song when it came to Aspire.
I felt that this song was full of youth.
When I was thinking about the meaning of the lyrics as Kanon,
Kanon's solo songs have a lot of blue sky.
I thought it would be refreshing if it was Kanon.
There is also a part where the instrument behind falls.
I thought I'd sing it gently.
If it was the current Kanon, I'd look forward to it more.
Rather than being kind, I thought I'd sing it more.
If it was the previous Kanon, it was like this.
This time it's like this.
I think it was a song that changed my way of thinking and sang it.
A new song that opened up Kanon-chan.
Kanon has a smile more than a smile.
I like it!
I want to hear the two of you.
It's a story about me.
When I received the materials for this song,
I was depressed and didn't have much energy.
I was encouraged.
It's a song with a love live feeling.
I love the love live series and Riella.
It's a song that gave me a chance to think again.
I have a lot of memories.
I was encouraged by this lyrics.
I was able to sing happily.
I think it was a song that could be recorded naturally.
I love it.
It's good.
You can get a lot of energy.
How about you?
It was like opening the gate.
Open the gate.
It was like I was kidding.
When I received the materials for the intro,
I stopped it for a while.
I stopped it!
Wait a minute.
I thought we were going to start the musical.
I stopped it for a while.
Wait a minute.
The title has a star on it, but it's so grand.
I started listening to it.
The drums of the band are like this.
Suddenly, the love live sound started.
It's like dancing the raspberry at home.
What is it?
It's like a gal.
It's been a while since I heard Riella.
How did you say it?
I don't know.
If it's fun, it's okay.
It's a great song.
It's a happy song.
I'm aiming for a happy song.
I love the love live sound songs.
I love it.
I thought it was coming.
Thank you very much.
It was a great show channel.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
I love you too.
I love you.
The love channel was opened.
I'm looking forward to the live performance.
I understand.
I thought there would be a lot of unison.
I thought so from the recording time.
There are many parts that the audience can sing together.
I haven't said I'll do it live yet.
It's a theme song.
It's called a theme song.
I think it's about 99.9%.
When you perform live,
I want you to sing together.
Please listen to it many times.
Thank you very much.
Let's continue.
I got it from Tempura Ice.
It's the best.
Thank you very much.
The release of the 7th live theme song Open the Gate.
Congratulations on the release of the music video.
Thank you very much.
Everyone who dances on the school's roof in new clothes is the youth.
I feel very cheerful.
At the last chorus,
The three of them gathered in the center.
Thank you very much.
I got it from Onimaro.
It's the first live music video in Open the Gate 11.
I'm very happy.
What I felt from this song was the sense of achievement and expectation.
I feel like I've grown up so much.
At the same time, I feel like a parent.
I was able to shine my eyes like a child.
Thank you very much.
I got it from Curry Rice.
At the end of the MV of Open the Gate,
At the scene where Kanon and the others appeared,
I cried.
It was a great MV that made me feel deeply that I was a real man.
Thank you very much.
I got it from Izumin.
My favorite scene in the MV of Open the Gate is the scene where I write a wish and watch it with everyone.
Especially, I was touched by Kanon's wish to cheer everyone up with her song.
Thank you very much.
I got it from Rie Rajinem Daikyojin.
I watched the MV of Open the Gate.
I would like to see the details such as wearing a bandana with a member color.
Also, I had a different hairstyle than usual.
I was able to see the appearance of the new member cast.
Personally, Aya-chan was cute.
Thank you very much.
This is Rie Rajinem Daikyojin's first MV.
I was able to shoot it on the roof.
It was fun.
I'm glad it was sunny.
It was a rain forecast.
I think it was the first forecast.
The weather forecast was cloudy and then it rained.
Sometimes it was cloudy.
It was sunny when I took the scene on the roof.
After that, it started to get cloudy again.
I thought Rie Rajinem Daikyojin was wearing a bandana.
The sky was clear.
It was clear.
Which MV do you like?
There are so many MVs.
Just one MV.
Do you have to squeeze it?
I like the 2nd generation MV.
Thank you very much.
What is that?
It's a little bit.
It's like a movie.
The 2nd generation is the drama scene.
I love it.
It was precious.
There are a lot of flashbacks.
There were a lot of things.
It's life.
Rie Rajinem Daikyojin is life.
There were a lot of flashbacks.
I remember it.
I really like it.
The feeling of each member coming together.
The drama scene is also coming out.
I'm glad.
I want to do it.
What do you mean?
I talk to Yui a lot.
When the 2nd generation is encouraging each other.
They look at each other in the back.
They are next to each other.
They look at each other a lot.
I want to see the bond.
I want to see it.
I want to do it.
I didn't miss it.
There is a scene where everyone is running on the roof.
Maru and Tomari like to look at each other for a moment.
I really like it.
Thank you very much for taking that scene.
Thank you.
It's a moment.
I really like their bond.
I'm glad.
There is a way to draw a bond.
The 2nd generation started with something that couldn't be done.
The members are very colorful.
I don't have to draw the 3rd generation.
The moment I found it.
I really like this moment.
I love it.
I like it.
When Yui and Maru do it together.
I wonder how much they communicate.
They look at each other and laugh.
They don't laugh at each other.
They look like they're smiling.
They always talk to each other.
I want to hear more.
If you don't think about it, you'll end up with Sakura and Yui.
It's difficult.
With the members.
On the contrary, the 3rd generation.
They look at each other and look at each other.
They are on the side of the other.
I agree.
There is a scene where the engine is assembled.
In the MV.
There are five people.
On the contrary, there are five people.
There is a bond of five people.
I want to go with a smile.
Of course, there are scenes like that.
Sometimes there is.
In this MV.
I wonder if there is a position to watch over the 2nd and 3rd generation.
I'm watching it with a smile.
There was a scene of Kinako.
I was able to dance.
I love it.
I know.
That's what I mean.
I'm watching.
I'm not just watching.
The expression of watching.
Because there was such a thing in the past.
I can express this kind of thing now.
Of course, it's a new scene now.
I was able to feel the past at the same time.
It was very fun.
It was also very fun to watch.
That's good.
I'm glad I got a line from Sayori.
The last scene where Kanon is surrounded by white light.
I love that scene.
Really?
I want to make it a
Sayori is like a Buddha.
It was made with a very shiny feeling.
It was drawn very harmoniously.
I made it.
It was the last scene.
I thought I made it poorly.
I haven't done it yet.
I've never seen it before, so I love it.
When the music video was released,
Sayori sent me a line.
I'm glad.
I was able to make Kanon cute.
I was grateful.
The members came out.
It was amazing.
I got it this time.
The costumes and the hairstyle were different.
They were different from the usual.
It was cute.
It was fresh.
There were many other girls.
Can you see this live?
I wonder if it will be seen.
There are few live performances.
I'm glad I can change my hairstyle.
I made it straight.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I changed my hairstyle.
If you are interested, please come to Seven Slives.
I extended my hair.
What is that for?
I don't know why I extended my hair.
It's about 20 cm.
I saw the moving figure.
I wanted to extend it.
I have no choice but to go to Seven Slives.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your emails.
Let's introduce the email request for lunch time.
I got it from Satori-san.
Thank you very much.
After the release of Open the Gate,
I have been oniri-pi.
From the intro that feels the greatness,
to the fun of the whole song,
to the sound of wow wow,
I'm looking forward to listening to it live.
I can't stop my excitement.
I want to listen to the song again
after listening to your recommendations.
This time, I received a request for this song.
Thank you very much.
It's just after the release.
If it's a song,
let's listen to your recommendations.
Let's listen to everyone's recommendations.
After all,
I want you to be surprised
at the intro again.
I want you to feel like you're listening to it for the first time.
Please reset your memory once.
I'm always surprised
at the drum sound from the intro.
Certainly.
Please listen to it.
Open the Gate
Let's see it together
Let's go open the day
Come on, let's adventure
If you feel like it's fun
I can fly
I can feel the wind in my chest
Like a happy ending
A happy moment
Our hearts are connected with excitement
Come on, let's sing
Don't let it echo, everyone
To the world
Wow wow wow wow wow
Open up
All the things I can't shake
I'll pack it in my bag and take it
Let's take it out at a fragile time
Let's fill it up with light
If one thing comes true, it will come true again
The next thing I want to achieve will come out
So I can't stop forever
Now is the starting point
Let's send it
Let's pass through the sky of pleasure
Let's see the sun of the journey
Let's cross the river of tears
If we're together
It's the best adventure
Let's open the day
Come on, let's adventure
I want to do anything
I can go to the energy
The dream we are seeing will never wake up
Love Live Super Star
New以上ランチタイム放送局
リエラジ
From Love Live Super Star
Announcement
It is blu-ray information
Love Live Super Star Fan Disc
Hokkaido and Dekkaido are on sale
1st to 3rd TV anime
Special part of the main story
All 30 songs of Riella are recorded
Where is Riella going?
Hokkaido short film
Please check out the video of Riella that can only be seen here
Also as a bonus
7th Live Kanagawa Park ticket
The fastest priority ticket application is also sealed
The application period is until Sunday, December 7th, 2359
Don't forget to apply
Music information
7th Live theme song Open the Gate
Riella version and Nisan Kisei version are on sale
7th Live Aichi Park
The fastest priority ticket application is also sealed
Please take it by all means
In addition, the official youtube
MV of Open the Gate is also on sale
Please check out this too
Riella Club information
Currently in Riella Club
In the autumn harvest festival
Live behind the scenes
Behind the scenes of MV shooting
Content is being released
Also digital photo frame
Because it is limited until the end of November
CD of your hand
MV scene
Please enjoy shooting
Love Live series
It is an announcement from the official card game
On Saturday, November 22nd
Booster pack
Sapphire Moon will be released
From Riella members
Sumire-chan
Ren-chan
Shiki-chan
Tomari-chan
It is recorded as an illustration card
Please get it
And next year on Saturday, February 28th
Love Live series 15th anniversary
To commemorate the first anniversary of Love
Booster pack anniversary
2026 will be released
This product is on Saturday, February 21st
On Sunday, February 22nd
Love is grateful
Pre-sale will be implemented
Please get it at the venue
Also Love is grateful
On Saturday, February 21st
From Riella
Date Sayori and Sakakura Sakura
Please look forward to this
The latest information will be delivered in order
Love official site and Love official X
Please pay attention
Appearance information
Encore and real sound
Web interview is being held
Peyton Naomi
Yabushima Akane
Okuma Wakana are appearing
Open the gate
About high motivation
I'm talking a lot
Please check it
The details of all the information introduced
Love Live Super Star Riella official X
Please check from the Love Live Super Star official website
That was the notice
Love Live Super Star
This is the launch time broadcast station Riella
It's time to say goodbye
Here is the broadcast information after the time
Next time on November 25th
The 248th broadcast scheduled for Tuesday
On the 25th
I will continue to welcome Natsumi Onizuka
I will welcome Aya Emori
And further
The 249th broadcast scheduled for Tuesday, December 2nd
I will welcome Peyton Naomi
I will deliver it in Tomaka Sumi
Everyone is waiting for the message to pay
How was today's broadcast?
How about my sister?
It's been a long time since Riella-chi
What kind of air did you do in Riella-chi?
It didn't really come out
It's okay
It was full of Aya World
I thought it was okay
It was really good
I am often told
Emori is too unique
Sometimes I don't know what I'm saying
I'm told
I don't know what I'm saying
Recently
I've gotten used to Emori-goroku
I'm getting used to it
I'm lonely because I'm getting used to it
It's a bit like Kamatte-chan
It's cute
I think that was fully expressed today
Riella-chi has a new wind
BGM also says it's going to blow
It's true
Emori's small wind
Thank you
Please look forward to the next time
Please let the wind blow
Please
This time Love Live Super Star
Riella-chi is up to here
Jibuya Kannon role
Onitsuka Tomari role
Sakakure Sakura and Onitsuka Natsumi role
See you