We have Sumire-senpai on for this radio episode.
Thanks for having me, Tomari!
What's up, Tomari? You've been staring at Sumire
Isn't it obvious, Kanon? With this amazing honors student before her very eyes,
she can't help but fall in love!
Gosh, don't make her say it out loud!
Wrong🤓
Looks like you got it wrong. Too bad.
*Struggling noises* Fine, whatever.
Then what was it?
Ah, are Natsumi and I gyala-overlapping again?
You can just say "overlapping"...
Indeed, Sumire and Aneja are similar in their energetic personalities.
They both enjoy streaming,
and furthermore, they share in their sensitivity to the latest trends.
Now that you mention it, they do seem close in a lot of areas.
From my gathering of Sumire-senpai's knowledge, I have come to identify several areas in which she differs from Aneja.
Ara? You've been studying me?
So that means... you've become a fan of mine?
Maybe such a cute junior wants an autograph of mine!
No, thank you.
Guess she's not so cute.
Come on now Sumire, pouting in front of your junior isn't very mature of you.
I'm not pouting!
So Tomari, what _did_ you study about me then?
I learned you had several roles as a child actor, but it seems didn't land you found any as a lead.
Ugh... this girl went right for my weak point...
Be that as it may, your failures never stopped you from pursuing the performing arts.
That's right!
I didn't really know what you were going through back then either.
I felt your approach was very different to my Aneja,
who put herself through various challenges with starry eyes.
This isn't, of course, to appoint one as the better approach.
Tomari...
Yeah! Natsumi trying so many different challenges and Sumire's perseverance with getting a lead role are both cool!
Cool...
Indeed. Aneja really is cool.
You too, Sumire-senpai.
Ueh?! Ah...
Now that you say that, I feel a little embarrassed...
Aneja is also that way when I compliment her.
Hahaha! I can see her saying "You're making me embarrassed!"
Alright, alright! Enough with the chit-chat, we've gotta start the radio show!
Sumire-chan! You're turning red!
S-s-shut up!!
Everyone,
good afternoon!