Thank you.
Let's say hi to everyone before we leave.
Ah!
Ah, we got the stamp!
Let's use it.
Need to use it. Need to use it.
Need to use it x2
"Let's stay together", everyone.
We're pretty buried under all the other stamps,
but I really am using mine!
Well then, everyone, thanks for watching with us!
Time to leave.
See you~.
Thanks for watching with us.
Thanks so much everyone!
The Afterlive was so good, wasn't it? The song too of course.
That and the talk segments, I was so glad to see everything getting back to normal.
Thanks for watching with us, everyone.
Thank you.
So that was the first Afterlive performance of "Yoka ni Mitorete",
so I think there may be a few first-time listeners here,
as well as maybe some who've already seen the 2D and 3D MVs that've been out since yesterday.
Come on. It's just so good, isn't it?
Just simply a wonderful song.
"Yoka ni Mitorete"... For Ena, I think...
this song represents the words she's facing Mizuki and saying.
Like the lyrics say, she's just holding onto Mizuki...
Holding onto Mizuki...
so gently, and on the verge of tears.
N25 songs often have lots of painful or negative emotions in their lyrics,
but now that everyone is moving forward little by little in their own journeys,
they can voice more than just that.
That's why they could sing this song.
So actually, keeno-san was able to participate remotely in our recording sessions.
They supported each of us in our four recording sessions by voice.
But weren't they such a warm and gentle person, just like their song?
I thought, "Makes sense that such a gentle person was able to make such a gentle song."
And then we were able to watch the 2DMV and 3DMV for the first time yesterday.
We were able to see Bouno-san's wonderful illustrations in so many different ways.
You can really tell how much respect for the story they put in the MVs.
Please do watch them, everyone.
Please watch to the end.
They're both flower-themed.
They are.
"Yoka ni Mitorete",
"Admiring the Late-Blooming Flowers"
and "Bake no Hana."
"Monstrous Flower"
During our recording sessions, we asked if they coordinated that,
but it was actually completely unplanned that both titles would have the word "flower".
We always provide a— what is it— a story prototype with basic details to the vocaloid producers,
and both ended up coming up with a song about "flowers".
I think that was incredible.
Definitely.
They didn't connect the titles like that on purpose,
Of course, there's a reason for it, but it's not like they coordinated this.
Complete coincidence.
It felt like it was almost a fated coincidence.
One that made a wonderfully connected story.
We got so much reaction to "Bake no Hana" too.
Even the singing distribution was— how to say—
it reminds you a lot of the story, doesn't it?
Even the fact that Ena has relatively few parts might have some grounding there.
It did, didn't it? Yeah.
It did.
Please, do listen to both songs if you haven't already.
Please do listen.
So once again, both the 2DMV and the 3DMV are available to watch here on the official ProSeka YouTube channel,
so maybe after this Aftertalk, please watch as many times as you like.
Both are really good in their own ways.
So please do if you have the chance.
Moving on!
Alright then, we also have 5 new cards to introduce as well today.
Have you already seen the card art and side stories, everyone?
Alright...
Hinata will show us the cards and I'll go over them.
First up...
we'll start with Ena Shinonome.
It's Ena~.
Untrained.
We saw this art in the story.
Such warm colors.
And next, the trained.
So good.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Shall we move to the next one?
Next up,
Akiyama Mizuki, untrained.
This one also appeared in the event.
In that beautiful scene.
And this is the trained.
I want to line them all up on my wall.
Yep.
Now for MEIKO.
Untrained.
MEIKO really did work hard in this story.
Endlessly grateful to her.
So grateful.
Man,
just so good.
Haha indeed.
Next up is the trained art.
So good we get to see so many different angles.
Long-hair MEIKO is so pretty too.
So pretty.
The flowers look so good on her.
They do.
Next up...
Let's move to Kanade, untrained.
Uhh... untrained.
You can do it~
She's eating her cup ramen.
She is.
That's Kanade's untrained, next we have the trained.
Her hair is so beautiful.
So true.
Note: Yes yes yes yes please go watch it if you haven't.
By the way, if you haven't checked
out Kanade's side story yet,
I think you might enjoy the story more if you read it.
If you've been playing the event
and have points saved up,
I think you can still exchange for her up till today,
so please do get this card.
Next up,
Ah!
Mafuyu.
You long press it.
Whoops.
Mafuyu-chan.
Mafuyu also helped out a lot this story.
Right? I was really glad to hear
such warm words coming from Mafuyu.
I always really like her expressions in these.
Please admire every detail, everyone.
Please do, everyone.
Aren't these so good?
They are.
Last time's illustrations had
a lot more of a muted palette,
but these ones feature a lot more vivid, yet warm and gentle hues.
Both have their good points,
but I feel like this gentler style really fit the progression of the story.
Alright, so with that, it was just a short time,
but that's all for the ProSeka Aftertalk "With Our Wounded Hands" Edition.
What did you think, everyone?
Thank you for watching, and for all the warm comments.
With that, we'll each make some closing remarks about today's stream.
Take it away, Hinata-chan.
Thank you so much for watching, everyone.
Right. For me, I think that the best way I can "face" Mizuki is through my acting,
and while I think it might be a bit presumptuous to say that I fully met her feelings with my acting,
I did all that I could to put my absolute everything into recording in that booth that day.
And you know... for voice acting in games like this,
you have to leave pauses between lines for the player to tap through.
That's... a pretty common sense way of doing it.
The editors would have to cut out each line.
Yeah, they'd have to cut out each line.
That'd normally be the case, but for these performances with lots of crying—
how to say—
you can't really cut yourself short.
So I asked Colorful Palette if it'd be fine to record this all in one continuous take.
Like, "could you cut this part out?" or "could you cut my crying or sniffling here out?"
That way I can keep the emotions flowing.
And they were very understanding.
And when I saw the final cut, I thought they did an amazing job following through with those.
I could tell that Colorful Palette edited it all together giving lots of care to the emotions I put into my acting.
So— how to say—
Though I am watching over Mizuki as the one voicing her,
there's still a lot lying ahead for all the N25 members,
like their careers, songwriting, and other challenges they'll continue facing.
And even if I'm not directly helping them,
maybe from the shadows, I hope I can continue to quietly support the N25 members.
Thank you very much for watching today.
Over to Minori-chan.
Ehh, thank you very much everyone for watching all the way to the end today.
For this story— this story and the previous one, especially both Chapter 8s,
we received so many comments from those who watched the story and were—
were moved, or how it really gave them pause.
But truly, those moments could only happen because of the long journey these characters have walked to get here.
We only watched Chapter 8 today, but if you start from Chapter 1,
the characters are always grappling with issues or challenging themselves.
That’s what makes everything possible.
Ena and Mizuki being able to move forward together is, after all,
only possible thanks to their bonds and interactions with the other members.
So I really hope everyone watches every single chapter without skipping,
to truly feel what the characters are going through.
As for Ena's growth, after all this time,
Ena was able to get through to Mizuki— maybe not completely yet,
but Ena was able to play this role because she's continuing to challenge herself by facing her painting.
Thanks to all the growth she went through in all the previous stories,
she's mature enough to see things through someone else's eyes,
and that's what helped both Mizuki and Ena move forward in this story.
N25 were able to face one of their problems together,
but for Ena personally, with her painting,
she hasn't quite reached her goal yet.
In Ena's last focus event story,
there were some comments saying she's gotten over her issues,
but personally, I don’t see it that way.
I feel like this is just the beginning of an endless road towards the artist she's striving to become.
So, thank you, truly, to everyone who supports her on that journey.
I’ll continue from here forward taking responsibility for Ena’s life,
and do my absolute best to carry her life forward as an actor.
Alright.
So with that...
Yes.
that's all we have for today.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Bro if you haven't watch Ena5 yet what the heck are you doing here
Those of you who haven't watched the story, once the next event starts,
it'll be on—
YouTube?
On YouTube?
Ah, in-game?
You can watch it freely in-game, so please do so if you couldn't unlock it.
It should also be uploaded to YouTube,
Please do.
so please watch it there if you'd like.
So with that, we're at the end of our program.
Do you think it's too early to say "Happy New Year?" For Project Sekai?
"Happy New Year"...
Well, the staff still have a lot of recording left to do.
Yeah, all the staff we're seeing here.
Staff members,
thanks for the continued support. Maybe more fitting.
But for everyone watching, we wish you a happy new year.
On SekaRaji, I said the same thing, thinking it was too early.
We just recorded it today.
Well, either way, have a happy new year, everyone.
Happy new year, everyone.
We look forward to another great year with you.
See you again next time!
Goodbye!
Bye bye~