asfasfasfasfasf
Hello everyone! Kon-needo!
This is Ruriko Noguchi, voice of Ichika Hoshino.
In these ProSeka Aftertalks,
we'll look back at this event while covering messages you, the fans, have sent in.
This time, we'll be covering the "Kimi to Tsunagu Heart Beat" event.
Did you like the story, everyone?
The story this time was a pretty happy one, wasn't it?
When I first read the script ,I was like "is it really okay for so many good things to happen?"
So many good things. I was really happy going through it.
This story made me realize the warmth and importance of bonds between people.
We'll go more in depth in the story later, so please stay tuned for that.
Also, Aftertalks have had a bit of a mini-renewal!
We've gathered your comments for this Aftertalk sent through email as well as the submissions channel on the Discord.
Thanks for all the messages everyone.
We'd like to go over some of them in our program today.
so please look forward to that!
Also, if you have any thoughts on today's program,
please post them on X with #ProSekaAftertalk.
We'll also be watching the YouTube chat.
Please keep all the messages coming.
Already seeing lots of "Kon-needo!" Thanks everyone.
"I just finished the story!"
Thanks for rushing to come here.
Right then, let's get started.
We'll start by talking about the "Kimi to Tsunagu Heart Beat" story.
What did you think of the story, everyone?
Let's look back together while going over some of the messages you've sent in.
First up, a message from "Misora"-san.
"Good evening, Noguchi-san!" Good evening!
"Thanks as always providing us with such a wonderful voice for Ichika."
The pleasure is all mine.
"Seeing Ichika-chan pour her all of her love for Miku into a new song in this story was really moving."
"I couldn't stop smiling and feeling warm inside."
"That last serious look from Shiho-chan has me a bit curious."
"But regardless, I'm just happy that Ichika-chan is so happy."
Thank you for the message, Misora-san.
So this time, Ichika wrote a new song "with" around the theme of "What Miku means to me",
putting in feelings of everything she's been through with Miku.
Then when she uploaded it, that creator Aoi-san reacted out her,
asking to make an MV together. It got so many views and just kept blowing up from there.
I mentioned this at the beginning, but I just kept thinking "wow is it really okay for everything to work out this well?"
Just so many good things happening for Ichika in this story.
I'm really glad that Ichika was able to accomplish one of her goals of connecting people through music.
It may be just a small first step for now,
but I really think is a story where one of her wishes came true,
I couldn't help but have a huge smile the whole time I was playing her.
Oh yeah, and they mentioned that last scene with Shiho's serious look...
what do you think of that, everyone?
How did that make you feel?
Shiho— she—
she said that she was really happy for Ichika at the end there...
but to me, it looked a little like,
yeah... she definitely looked a bit unsettled there.
You know, we haven't really seen Shiho like that.
I can't help wondering what's making her feel that way.
But yeah, Shiho-chan...
her being so serious about this band—
everyone is, but amidst all that Ichika,
yeah, making Miku songs on her own,
I wonder if Shiho has any feelings about that.
And I wonder what kind of story that will lead to?
Even I have no idea,
buuuuuuut,
maybe that's just how bands are, aren't they?
But, I mean,
there are plenty of folks who make Miku songs solo but are also part of bands, aren't there?
So I hope that Ichika can also do that and continue pursuing her happiness further.
I just hope that she can continue doing her best as part of Leo/need,
and that she can continue creating songs with her beloved Miku.
I'm not sure what the future holds for her, but let's keep watching over her warmly.
Alright. Now let's move on to the next message.
A message from "YMMK"-san.
"Noguchi-san, kon-needo!" Kon-needo.
In this event story, Ichika composed a song "with", pouring her feelings for Miku into it.
"but it seemed like Ichika wasn't really thinking about what to do after she finished it."
Yeah.
"There was a scene where she seemed happy just to show the completed song to the rest of Leo/need."
"Noguchi-san, are there any times where you also felt satisfied just by doing the task itself?"
Thank you for the message.
Right, Saki-chan was the one who actually suggested uploading the song after Ichika show it to them.
But yeah, "things I feel satisfied just by doing"?
Let me think...
The other day, I tried making curry.
I just felt like trying making it one day,
I did feel satisfied doing it... but it was annoying to eat all of it.
I made so many portions!
Listen,
I made way too many portions.
But it's like,
I really was proud of myself.
I was happy with what I made.
I feel like eating food you cooked yourself doesn't really have the same allure, does it.
You just cook stuff, then eat it normally.
You do it just for the sense of accomplishment, you know?
This is kind of unrelated,
but I don't actually have a knife in my place.
I'm not even sure how.
I definitely did have one before. I did.
But somehow it suddenly vanished. Isn't that scary?
I needed to cut some carrots, but I couldn't without a knife.
So I ended up cutting them with scissors.
I had to cut them like "krhhhh."
That was really satisfying.
Putting in the work to cut the carrots like that.
I thought I wouldn't even have enough energy left to eat what I made.
Just kidding. I did end up eat all of it later.
Don't worry.
Was was I talking about again?
I completely forgot.
Thank you very much for the message.
Let's get back on track.
I've selected some of my favorite scenes from the story for today, so let's watch them together!
Here it is!
Hmm. That's a very Ichika way of thinking.
Thanks for the video. That was Chapter 8 of the story.
So as for why I chose this particular scene,
when Shiho asks Ichika about the song she put so much of her own feelings into going viral,
and if she was bothered by strangers creating covers and their own works form it,
I thought it was memorable how Ichika says "no, I'm actually really glad."
Maybe some creators out there say things like "my song should sound like this,"
but Ichika isn't like that.
Instead she thinks "it's awesome that my song is helping connect many different people"
That's a sign of how strong and wonderful she is.
I see everyone's saying that they're a bit restless.
Yep, does looks like everyone has lots of thoughts on this.
Saki-chan— like some of you mentioned—
really likes being close with fans on a personal level,
while we see Ichika's seems to enjoy her music spreading to all sorts of places,
Everyone in Leo/need seems to have their own desires...
I do wonder a bit on how things will play out going forward,
but having the song she created out of her feelings for Miku spreading so far,
Ichika must be so happy.
This is supposed to be a happy story,
so I just hope Ichika is able to continue creating songs like this.
Thank you for the comments, everyone.
I see people going "What's gonna happen?"—
Ah!
Someone says "their musical direction is drifting apart."
Is something going to happen? I don't know either.
I don't know what's gonna happen next...
But at least things are still happy for now, so let's leave it at that.
Not yet, not yet. We don't know what's coming next.
I really don't know what's next. I just want to see Ichika happy like this.
As the one playing her, I just want her to keep doing what makes her happy,
I'm just praying that things work out for the best.
Anyway, thanks for looking through the comments with me.
Alright, then, moving on.
Let's take a look at the card art together.