Yes.
Right.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
I see.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Right, right.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Right, right.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hm.
Yes.
Right.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Right.
Right, right.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
Mhm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Right, right.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay.
Right, right.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
Right.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Right.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Right.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Right, right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Right, right.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Right, right.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hm.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right, right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right, right.
I see.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
I see.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
I see.
Yes.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
Yes.
Right, right.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Okay.
Yes.
Mhm.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
ProSeka AfterTalk, "This Story Carries Hope" Edition.
Was that okay just now?
You hit your hand, didn't you?
It was a pretty solid hit, wasn't it?
Good evening.
I'm Mayu Yoshioka, who plays Haruka Kiritani from MORE MORE JUMP!
I look forward to it.
So, this ProSeka AfterTalk is
a program where we look back at the event while introducing
the messages we received from all of you.
This time, it's the "This Story Carries Hope" edition.
Right.
Everyone,
did you enjoy the story and the event?
What did you think?
Well, I myself was really looking forward to it,
so I'm really looking forward to hearing everyone's thoughts
today, including this broadcast.
So, we were previously collecting messages
for AfterTalk via the official ProSeka Discord
and email.
Thank you to everyone who sent them in.
And today, we'll be introducing the messages we received during the program.
It seems we really received a lot of them,
Also, your thoughts on the event and this broadcast,
please post them using the hashtag #ProSekaAfterTalk.
Right, I can see the YouTube chat here as well.
So please, keep on writing!
I'll be checking the hashtag after the broadcast ends,
so please tweet a lot.
Please do.
Alright, so, while I'll be looking at the comments,
I want to keep things moving along.
After all, I came here today planning to talk a lot.
I brought my notebook today, but I forgot it in the dressing room.
I'll ask the makeup artist to get it for me later.
Alright, then,
let's immediately talk about the story of this event, 'Carrying Hope'.
So, everyone, what did you think of this story?
While introducing your letters, we'll look back at the story together.
Alright.
First up, from Mirin-san, I believe?
Thank you so much.
From: Mirin-san. Yoshioka-san, Kon-more.
Kon-more.
I love Yoshioka-san's strong, clear voice.
Thank you.
I felt that this event's story depicted the process of reaching an answer more subtly than usual.
Here it is.
A note arrived.
I'll introduce it shortly.
I got a bit slow.
Everyone discussed and exchanged opinions,
and the way they thought, debating 'this way or that way,' was clearly depicted.
Haruka-chan, who moved efficiently among them,
was very impressive.
Haruka-chan's initiative became even clearer,
and it was fun to see her interacting with various idols.
Good luck to everyone in Momojan in the LumiGra finals!
Thank you.
So it's abbreviated as LumiGra.
Lumina Grand Prix is the common name, but this is the first time I've seen it
abbreviated with four characters.
Has that happened before?
Right, thank you.
Mirin-san, thank you again.
That's right. It was a very significant milestone story, being the one right before the finals.
Everyone's reactions...
Right, the feeling was, 'Are they finally coming?' I got that from the messages I received beforehand,
and there were many such impressions.
Right, I heard there were many people who were really bracing themselves.
But in the end, it felt like they were in a really
good state to move on to the next stage, didn't it?
I wish I had a boss like Haruka-chan.
I get it.
When I first saw "Rumigura," I thought,
"Oh, so that's what it is." It seems like it's being abbreviated.
Indeed, it feels like it's going to become a common nickname
in the world. It's likely to be abbreviated as "Rumigura."
Makes sense, makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay, so with that, I'd like to read another message.
Uh, is it Yukky-san?
Thank you very much.
Yukky-san, in katakana.
Uh, Yoshioka-san, konmuha desu.
Konmuha desu.
This story felt like a culmination of sorts for Momo-chan.
Working together with the girls they'd fought alongside during the Lumina Grand Prix,
they prioritized delivering hope to the people in front of them, rather than focusing on audience numbers.
I was deeply moved by that decision.
Also, the way Haruka and the others tackled their challenges, as if confronting their past selves,
and the different shades of Haruka that Yoshioka-san shows us through her voice, I'm looking forward to them in the future.
Thank you very much.
Right, that's right.
They safely passed in second place.
The moment the results were announced, my heart was pounding.
Little by little, one group at a time.
And also, the total number of votes being displayed as a number, isn't that incredibly realistic?
Something interesting about the Lumina Grand Prix is that each person gets two votes, you know.
It's not just one vote per person, so you can choose 'this one and this one,' for example.
That's kind of nice, and also, when you look at the total number of votes,
when you look at the numbers, you realize just how much attention it received,
and I really feel that.
It was that kind of format, you know.
Mm-hm.
I think it's such an interesting project.
In the real world, to decide an idol that gets the whole of Japan excited like that,
a participatory event like that is pretty rare.
I found myself constantly substituting and wondering what it would be like if it happened in reality.
I voted for Momo-chan and Rewrite.
Haha, on the broadcast.
Oh, where would I put my votes, I wonder?
But there were also units that appeared by name, even though they weren't in the story,
I wonder what kind of team they are,
and imagining that was really fun.
Right, two votes per person, but someone said you can't vote for the same place twice.
Someone said it in the story.
Exactly.
By the time 4th place was announced, it was already confirmed that someone would be pushed out, you know.
And realizing there that not all four groups could advance, I totally get it.
Right, the group called 'I'm' advanced, but...
I wonder what kind of unit they are.
I'm curious about them.
You know, that unexpected second place was a big deal, wasn't it?
Beforehand,
it was predicted differently online,
Haruka-chan mentioned something like that at the beginning.
Like, what rank do you think it would be,
based on your gut feeling?
They're watching, thinking it's real, right?
Momo-chan, with the online vote counts and predictions...
They use all of that as a reference for their future productions.
They really take all the hints they can get,
and then think about what to do next. I thought that was really mature of them,
because they're high schoolers.
I don't think high schoolers can do something like that.
Well then, thank you very much for all your messages.
Thank you, Yukki-san.
Well, we only received these two messages,
but I really want to talk a lot,
so please let me
take my time and talk.
You know,
for ProSeka users, the Lumina Grand Prix
must have felt like it took a really,
long time,
didn't it?
They kept releasing it little by little, and you wondered when the preliminaries would finally end.
I had this feeling of wanting to see what happens next quickly,
but then again, I also wished it would never end.
When I was right in that in-between state, at the moment it went from the preliminaries to the finals,
I was incredibly nervous, you know?
And what's more, when I realized it was Haruka's banner, I thought,
'Wait, is this story going to be told from Haruka's perspective?'
Right, especially in Haruka's case, as I'll talk about a bit later,
there's a clear wall: Hiiragi-san and Rewrite,
you know?
That existence she can't help but be aware of.
And she has to confront them again, you know?
Last time, when she fought with Hiiragi-san—well, 'fought' is one way to put it—
when they confronted each other one-on-one and talked,
it depicted something like a battle with adults in the real industry,
and Haruka's expression was very dark.
So, it was a growth amidst thinking, 'Oh no, I might not be able to overcome this wall.'
So this time, again, I wondered,
'Wow, what kind of battle will she have with Hiiragi-san now?'
And when that happened, before the finals, the advice she received from Rewrite,
who had become her comrades, her team, I thought, 'Is it really this reassuring?'
When you make them an ally, that reassurance, that strength, that overwhelming presence...
And the sense of security that 'if this person is here, it'll be fine,' all of that
was conveyed from every single word of Hiiragi-san. This is probably
where Haruka respects, where she wants to aim, and also
the big thing she has to overcome.
I really felt like there was a wall,
you know.
Was it episode 6?
I think it was around there.
It's scary.
Hiiragi-san's presence is just...
the more dependable she becomes, the more I feel the threat of what's to come.
Right?
And it makes me even more curious about what kind of team Aslan was,
the one Haruka was in with Hiiragi-san back then.
Speaking of Haruka, it's Hiiragi-san, but...
looking at the bigger picture, I think other teams went to various places for events,
starting with cram schools.
But, you know,
Arisa-san's...
Her thoughts,
from a former idol's perspective,
were 'I wanted to do this, but I can't now.'
But she wants to entrust that power to these new kids.
The idols in this world, their... influence?
It's insane, I thought.
What is that?
I really felt throughout the story that you guys, being entrusted by these legendary idols,
are truly amazing.
Yeah.
Right.
It's fine.
Yeah, you know, Kiriya's just too much.
I absolutely love that line where she says 'I was struck'.
When I was recording, I, of course, only received the script.
We weren't able to record together, so the finished product...
I hear for the first time when I play the game. But the scenario...
...was already so good, you know?
Oh, that scene with Arisa-san and Hiiragi-san.
That one was just incredible.
I kind of played just to see that scene.
This time around.
Of course, I wanted to see all of Momo-chan's scenes,
but I especially wanted to engrave that one into my memory,
so I made sure to watch it.
Yeah.
Oh, it seems there's an adjustment happening, so the screen will go dark for a moment.
We'll make some adjustments, so please wait a moment.
So, just a moment.
Ah,
I'll keep talking, you know.
I guess I'll wait for the next comment to come in.
Hm.
Can everyone hear me?
Oh, can you hear me now?
Okay.
I've confirmed that everyone's comments
have returned, so let's talk.
Right.
Ah, um, there are 8 episodes in total.
I've been talking about Episode 6 this whole time, but let's talk about the other episodes too, okay?
The traveling Team Live lasted two weeks.
When I realize again that the previous Lumina Grand Prix events were held over much shorter periods,
I thought what they were doing
was incredible.
You know, even before, they'd switch with other teams and shuffle songs to perform, but...
to think they were doing that
every few days... everyone's memory,
Wow, they're so young, that was my honest impression.
The sense of speed is just amazing,
for active idols to learn songs.
Well, there was talk about Minori being good at free copying,
but even members who aren't like that still have to learn other units' songs,
learn the songs, learn the dances, think about formations,
and perform them originally, and so on.
And they have to bring out their own strengths too.
That's too much to think about, isn't it?
They do it so well, don't they?
I really want to learn from them.
It's really incredible, isn't it?
And, you know, the thing I found most interesting and couldn't stop watching was...
...the comments.
Every time, the comments from viewers...
...that appear in Momojan's event stories.
Don't you think everyone writes them?
I think I've seen them before, though.
You know, I feel like there's a dedicated writer for those comments.
They're so spot-on every time.
I bet there are a lot of people who think, "Oh, I feel like I've tweeted something like this before."
Heh heh.
They've been found out.
Oh, right, so either they're pulling comments from somewhere, or they're hiring someone specifically for them.
They're so real every time.
It's really interesting, yeah.
I feel like that's one of the things that makes it feel so real, you know.
Yeah.
And every time, I'm a little curious, you know, in this story...
...what's the comment that I thought, "Oh, I'd probably say that myself," right?
Well, of course, sometimes they're lines of dialogue, but there are also depictions of fans, aren't there?
So, like Momojan's fans...
You know, oh, right, it's a blessing that we don't hear that much anymore, compared to how it used to be.
It stopped appearing, but back then, when people would say, "I don't know Momojan," you know...
Especially Minori.
The other members were already doing their thing, but back then,
there were some really harsh comments.
Yeah, there really were.
Thinking about it that way, the current environment is really great, isn't it?
It makes me so happy that everyone says, 'Yeah, Momojan!'
Right.
It's gotten a lot kinder, hasn't it?
It's not just that it's gotten kinder, but it means Momojan has
become known to everyone, I guess.
Like appearing on TV and stuff.
Mm-hm.
I really think the power of comments is amazing.
It's all thanks to their efforts, isn't it?
That's right, Momojan's efforts.
Yeah.
Now, everyone can look at the comments and feel welcome, right?
So you can watch them with peace of mind.
Yeah, really.
But now...
If Momojan were to do a stream by themselves, the chat section
would probably change quite a bit, don't you think?
The vibe, you know.
Well, but there are probably fans who've been supporting them since back then,
so that might not change.
They're new, saying they just came
from watching the Lumina Grand Prix.
Oh, that's nice. You know, originally...
Ah, first-timers, right?
Oh, that happens, that happens.
Oh, really?
Like, 'Hello, first-timers!'
I'd actually blurt it out in reverse.
Oh, that's right. Like, 'I came from Lumigra.'
Oh, what if 'Lumigra' gets officially adopted? What would I do?
Just kidding.
I'm just the one saying it.
Right.
Anyway, I've already done a general recap, so now...
Right, let's put Episode 8 aside for now.
I want to show you a scene I personally want to talk about. As you might guess, it's from Episode 6.
Please watch.
Here it is.
Okay.
I actually considered Episode 8, but if I watch that, I'll just cry my eyes out.
The current ranking prediction for Rewrite is Hiiragi-san...
Fifth place, or fifth place.
They're right on the border of making it to the main competition.
That's right.
That's a good rank.
Isn't it great that you can still get a good rank?
This event isn't fully taking shape yet.
I'm not even going all in.
And isn't it great that even without going all in, you can still say you got a good rank?
Ah, she's here.
Kiritani.
Mm.
Sensei, it's been a while.
I didn't realize I'd crossed my arms.
Yeah, you're right.
I get nervous,
just seeing Hiiragi-san.
But this time,
it doesn't seem like we just ran into each other by chance.
She's too mature.
Yes.
That's right.
Because I heard from Tsubaki-san and the others that Hiiragi-san would be here today.
They're too nice.
What do you want?
I came to ask a favor.
You're so cool, Haruka.
A favor?
That's right.
It's surprising, isn't it?
I was surprised too.
Hiiragi-san,
could you please give us some advice
for our event that we're holding at Lumina Time this time?
This time, wasn't it supposed to be a project you yourselves came up with?
You're absolutely right.
The rules stated that we should think of everything, including the setlist and staging.
However, there's no problem asking for advice on the overall concept and production policy.
I made a preemptive move.
I also confirmed with the management.
Yes, I confirmed with them.
So it's perfectly fine.
Confirmed?
But in this Grand Prix, you're Rewrite's rivals, aren't you?
Why ask me?
You're asking, but you already know, don't you?
It's because I believe there's no producer who has aimed to deliver hope and actually done so more than you, Hiiragi-san.
You're the one who can put it into words. Besides, we and Rewrite are on the same team right now.
This time's results will also affect Rewrite.
Rewrite's projected rank is currently 5th.
Even if I don't lend a hand, their chances of winning are high.
But it's from here, from this point on.
Even if that's the case, it's not 100%.
Then there's also a possibility of them being eliminated.
I want to increase our chances of winning.
Don't you think so?
Can high schoolers even use 'angle' like that?
I still can't.
Here it comes.
That's cool.
So please, I beg of you,
Hiiragi-san.
To win,
and to deliver hope,
please give us your advice.
They specifically chose the phrase 'to deliver hope' here, didn't they?
That's so cool.
What do you want to ask?
Right now, we're struggling because we lack a clear criteria for how to narrow down the ideas we've come up with.
Please look at this.
Oh, show me that document.
This is a list of the event ideas we currently have.
That's amazing, so well-prepared.
Yes, it is.
I think all the ideas themselves are good,
but how should we organize them for the event?
It's about whether you can create a path.
A path?
That's right.
So, the question is whether we can create a path
for those who find it difficult to move forward to believe in a story of hope again.
That will be the criterion for judgment.
A story of hope...
I knew it.
I couldn't breathe just now.
Huh, we're back.
Hiiragi-san gave you advice,
didn't he?
I was really surprised by this.
I never thought you'd go talk to a producer
from another group. I was really surprised.
As far as I know, he's the one who can view these kinds of events most objectively, so I thought he'd surely give me good ideas.
You really see him as a person, don't you?
When you first asked us for Hiiragi-san's schedule, we were surprised too.
Sorry for making such a request.
I wanted to sort things out in my head, so I wanted to talk to him directly.
It's quite alright.
Hiiragi-san is a reliable person, after all.
Thank you.
So, the advice I got from Hiiragi-san was to...
build the entire event with our rivals and become a bit more open with them.
That's what he said would be good.
Could you take a look?
Of course.
We're streaming it.
Knowing what happens after, I guess this could work.
But even for Hikari-san,
this wouldn't make for good streaming, would it?
You know,
I really like the 3DMVs from the early days,
where they'd just dance on stage and perform across the whole stage,
but now...
the recent MVs are like, actual music videos.
Right? They really feel like music videos.
They've evolved into 3DMVs where you can better understand the world of the song, including its lyrics.
And for this one, the lighting is also amazing.
You know, there was the card illustration, but this lighting from the tunnel stars,
and the five lights shining from the background?
What are those?
They're good.
They're consistently good.
Oh, no, I can't stop watching.
It's really not good.
Yeah, exactly.
You should definitely check out Airi's blown kiss and...
Haruka's wink with your favorite character.
Airi's beautiful.
And when you watch this MV, the impression it leaves is really great.
Ah, I'm done for.
Thank you, thank you again and again.
Thank you so much.
Oh, sorry, I'm talking about the song, aren't I?
Yes, well, it's a song called "Polaris".
Haruka's songs have always been cool, haven't they?
And this time, I was really looking forward to what kind of song would come.
And I learned that there's a range even within "cool" from the last two songs,
I realized that,
I see, I see.
There's still a different kind of idol cool, isn't there?
And this time, my first impression was that it was beautiful and cool.
The refined coolness really struck me as fresh and impactful; that was my first impression.
And especially, there are a few past songs, but this is one of those with beautiful harmonies.
I think it's one of them. Everyone sings in unison,
and then layering scales like climbing stairs,
how Momojan's recent story shows them gradually growing,
definitely achieving success,
and getting results.
I feel like that really links up with this song.
And that kind of harmony, the whole song is just wonderful,
in terms of harmony.
They layer so many notes.
And there are parts where each person sings individually, and parts where they're in the chorus,
so please listen to that a lot.
I'd really like you to compare them.
When we recorded this song, what I felt most strongly was,
songs like this inevitably make you cry.
There are parts where you want to sing as if you're about to cry,
but because we're idols, we have to deliver hope to everyone.
So, we absolutely can't cry.
But it's a song about remembering the past, feeling nostalgic,
and reaffirming that we'll work even harder now.
So, while retaining its preciousness and coolness,
it became a song with a strong sense of nostalgic
emotion.
That's what I wrote.
Yes, that's what I wrote in my notebook.
Right.
And, uh,
the 2DMV will be released too, right?
Since it says that, the full version will probably be released too, right? That's what it means, right?
Right, if you listen to the full version, I think you'll see parts
that aren't in this short version.
I definitely want you to compare it to the short version.
Specifically, I think the way the last chorus is sung gives a different
impression than previous choruses, so please listen carefully and distinguish it.
And this is a personal story, but
I, Mayu Yoshioka, personally wrote lyrics for a song with the North Star as its theme before,
Polaris, you know, it means something like the North Star.
Idols and stars, especially the North Star,
have a really high affinity.
And when I was writing it back then, I thought, you know, it's a landmark or a guide for someone.
Among the stars in the sky, it's like the brightest, the first star.
So it's used as a guiding star.
It really links to the idea of 'look at me, support me, find me'.
The North Star, that part of it...
This story, especially, you know,
the image of an idol as seen through the Lumina Grand Prix,
it really links to that. I was like, 'Yeah, that's right.' And the story, you know, they were saying...
The story of idols,
when you're creating a story,
it's absolutely necessary in a story that you create with the fans.
This guiding principle, I really felt it,
you know, in these lyrics, in this poem.
Yeah, it was really emotional.
Well, you know, I'm sorry this is a personal story, but...
Looking at this poem, looking at this title, I felt like I was really praised,
like, 'Oh, I wasn't wrong'.
I really felt like it was good to believe in this path.
And my thoughts on what an idol is, what I already had,
plus what Haruka taught me,
I realized it wasn't wrong. And from now on, Momojan...
And it was a great opportunity to reconfirm my thoughts on what an idol is,
and I'm really glad they wrote such a wonderful song for us.
You know, up until now, the theme of 'stars' has always been associated with Leoni
in ProSeka, and other units have avoided using it as a theme.
But I heard on-site that at this point, when things have settled,
they wanted to challenge themselves by making 'stars' a theme.
So, at this important timing, Haruka was entrusted with this challenge.
Yes, it made me genuinely happy, simply put.
I have so much more I want to talk about, but the main point I want to emphasize
is the difference in harmony and the chorus towards the very end.
So please check out the full version and the differences with the 3DMV.
The 3DMV is uploaded on ProSeka's official YouTube channel.
Because I talked too much, it's already public.
Right.
So please make sure to watch that part.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
Oh, and everyone, the stage decorations
in the 3DMV are really great too, aren't they?
Well then, time flew by, but
this ProSeka AfterTalk, "This Story Carries Hope" edition,
is almost at its end.
I think I'll take a look at everyone's comments one last time.
Right.
Sorry, I'm not very articulate.
And the opportunity to watch the 3DMV together with all of you was really fun.
You're all giving comments in real-time like this,
right?
It was truly enjoyable to share this time and connect with everyone.
Yeah.
Sorry for my otaku rambling.
I'm sure there were many parts where you couldn't understand what I was saying.
I'm really sorry.
Right, Haruka's so cool.
She really is, Haruka is cool.
She'll probably become even more
unbelievably cool from now on.
I want her to be like that, and I hope so too.
As a producer, at this point,
I think they've become even more established.
Yes, even more established.
I don't know why, but when I read Momojan's recent stories,
they're not scary at all.
The excitement of what's next,
of what's going to happen,
is stronger, and I have no worries.
I really don't have any concerns.
I think that's probably because everyone in Momojan has always stuck to their core principle
of giving hope to their fans, without wavering,
and kept moving
towards their goal.
I think it's because they've been steadily progressing, but you know,
it's really something.
When I look back, the thrilling and heart-pounding moments
I used to feel are already nostalgic.
It's like,
now,
I can now see it from the perspective of, 'What kind of hope
will they give us next?'
I truly feel that's a sign of growth.
It really is growth.
Momojan is truly wonderful.
They're just amazing.
Momo-chan is just the best, you know.
Momo-chan is the best.
Right?
So, yes, as you all know,
it was announced the other day on the ProSeka Broadcast Station,
that this episode will be the final AfterTalk.
It's ending.
Was it really okay for me to be the last one?
I mean, I've been talking so much, and my inner fan came out. Was that alright?
But you know,
as I've hinted at, being able to talk with all of you,
about what's good here, what's good there, this line,
that scene, this artwork... it was truly a happy thing,
wasn't it?
How many years did we do this for?
Around three years?
Or two?
Five years? Four or five?
Was it really that long?
Well, if we're talking about the AfterTalk series specifically,
we've been doing it for quite a while.
I mean,
it's certainly sad that we won't have these opportunities to look back every time,
but I'm sure there will be other ways
for us to interact with everyone, and those opportunities will increase.
Personally, if you call on me anytime, as much as you want,
I'll talk if there's a place to discuss things like this. And well,
I'll talk not just about Haruka's banner, but about Momojan as a whole.
You know, even if it doesn't happen every time, maybe at some point for a summary,
I hope there'll be a chance for us to talk
together again. I'm just thinking that to myself.
No, it's fine.
I just want to talk about all the 3DMVs, for now.
They're all good.
Even if it's not Haruka's banner, I'm always told it's okay to watch all of them.
They always say it's fine.
Thank you very much, truly.
So, please watch the past AfterTalks many times.
As for today's, I'll watch it on my own and reflect.
I'll talk about it anytime, so I believe that timing will come someday,
I'll pray for it, and for that time, I'll write down various things
in my notebook again.
Oh, right, the short video content will also be increasing,
and they're putting effort into it, so please
look forward to that as well.
So, for the event story, "This Story Carries Hope,"
if there's anyone who hasn't finished watching it yet,
once the next event starts,
you'll be able to read all of it from the event story section.
Well, I don't think there's anyone who hasn't seen it, but...
I've spoiled so much up until now,
but please watch the story first.
And please rewatch it again.
With that, thank you very much.
Everyone, let's meet again.
Bye-bye!
Thank you all so much.
And I'm sorry for my lack of vocabulary.
It was really fun to have the chance to watch the 3DMV together with everyone,
and to get comments in real-time like this,
right?
It was really fun to have this time where I could empathize with everyone.
Yeah.
Sorry for my otaku rambling.
Yeah, I'm sure there were many parts where you couldn't understand what I was saying.
I'm really sorry.
Haruka's so cool, isn't she?
She really is, Haruka is so cool.
She'll probably become even more
unbelievably cool from now on.
I want her to be like that, too.
As a producer, at this timing, you know, like...